Go for it, Rebecca!
Okay!
Get the hell off of this planet!
Take this!
-Don't give up!
-Shoot!
I won't let you get past me!
We'll kill you instead!
Air force?
They'll be a big hassle.
Leave it up to me!
Drop them and wash them away.
It's like flushing a toilet!
You're so funny!
He's insulting you.
PRELUDE TO THE AOI WAR
It's a large ship!
I've confirmed numerous missiles!
Are they trying to burn down this city?
This is bad!
I'll go!
He grabbed it!
He threw it!
Wow, your boss is amazing.
Yeah, he's the strongest!
I'm surprised too.
Rebecca, you're able to fight, huh?
Just a little.
I like you even more now!
Boss! Enemy reinforcements
in the West Ward!
What?
This is not good. There are no
fighters in the West Ward.
Let's go.
No, it's too far from here.
What should we do?
My mom lives in that area.
I altered it to run faster!
Weisz!
You getting in?
Those kids...
Enemies are approaching us from above!
There are so many of them!
They exploded!
That's...
It's Jinn and Kleene!
We'll take down the air force.
That's right!
Moscoy!
Screw Moscoy!
This is Edens Zero.
We've got you covered!
We'll make way for the Lord Demon King.
That's right! Go!
Thanks for your help everyone!
Everyone on this planet is a rebel!
Kill them!
Orc,
the Maelstrom is set in place.
And the East Ward?
There's strong opposition from the rebel
army, so it hasn't been set up yet.
Those idiots are getting in the way
of the great purge.
But that's fine.
This alone is enough.
It's the super concentrated
Ether particle bomb, the Maelstrom.
In the name of Poseidon Nero, I swear
that this will blow up half this planet.
Orc, the rebel army has entered
the West Ward!
That's...
He's not the rebel army!
He's that kid...
Why is he here?
Blow away, little brat!
-Take that!
-Wait!
-She sliced...
-The armored car!
Shoot!
Leopard Claw Frenzy!
Watch out, watch out!
This car is equipped with a minigun!
How persistent.
Take this!
That's the last one.
What a breeze.
That's it.
Master, I detect a high Ether signal
around your two o'clock.
Lord Demon King, can you hear me?
There is a large bomb
installed somewhere near you.
A bomb?
It's a nasty one! It's powerful enough
to blow away half this planet!
-We have to stop it!
-I'll help!
I sent the map to Pino,
so head there right now!
-Roger!
-That way!
Orc! Few from the rebel army
are headed this way!
It's those brats again!
Make sure to stop them!
Master, we can see it now!
Is it that tower?
More and more keep on appearing!
-I just need to destroy that?
-No!
If you apply too much outer force,
it might explode!
Place Pino near the tower.
I'll use the network to stop it.
-Got it!
-Master!
Riddle them with bullets!
Homura!
Go, Shiki!
We won't let you!
Weisz!
Turn around!
Sure thing!
Shiki, leave things here to us!
Okay!
You...
You're the one I met in Foresta!
Are you planning to disturb
my purging mission once again?
Well, I'm not the same person I was
back then.
As an O-Tech, I can update
my abilities by retrofitting body parts!
He's much stronger
than the last time I saw him.
Please be careful, Master!
In the name of Poseidon Nero,
I will purge you along
with this entire planet!
Whoa!
That's some power!
I can already see the moment
you will blow into pieces!
But...
What?
I'm not the same person I was
back then either.
It's a completely different gravity
from before...
-Pino!
-Yes, sir!
Connection is set.
I've received the data. Hacking now.
You bastard... I can't fail my mission
for the second time!
Please stop, Orc.
If you press that now...
In the name of Poseidon Nero...
Oh no.
The bomb has been activated.
That's...
It's the West Ward.
What?
That doesn't look good.
-Pino, get away from there!
-Master!
Master!
-He's...
-Stop it! It's too reckless!
-Shiki!
-What is he planning to do?
What the hell?
Isn't that Laguna's friend?
You idiot! Let go of that thing!
Even if you're Demon King,
that bomb will definitely...
Please!
Make it in time...
Shiki!
No!
Master...
Shiki.
No way...
Oh?
Look. Something's falling.
Master!
That was close!
I threw it somewhere far away.
Oh geez.
I wasn't worried at all.
We believed in you.
I was able to reduce
the power of the bomb.
You reduced it by 90%.
Good work, Hermit.
That made me nervous.
Enemies have been cleared out.
It's perfect.
We did it, Brother.
Moscoy Parade!
Edens Zero?
Edens Zero, as in Demon King's
battleship?
You guys are the ones who beat Drakken,
one of Oración Seis Galáctica?
I'm impressed that you know.
That information isn't public.
Rebecca, you took down Drakken?
It wasn't exactly me.
In a sense, it's all thanks to
Rebecca's power.
Boss, if you team up with them,
you can win
against Nero.
That kid!
I'm so glad he was okay.
Stay still.
The empire cuts ties with all prisoners.
We won't be of any use to you now.
But we still won't kill you.
We'll let you go
once this battle is over.
Once the battle... is over?
You really think you can win
against the Empire?
You're insane.
How many of our comrades died?
Sixteen!
Sixteen of our
comrades were killed by these bastards.
We lost a lot on our side too!
You idiot! Don't provoke him!
We're all on the same boat!
You're right.
There's no good side or bad side
to a war.
It's just a clash of will
that produces death.
But even so, we can't stop as long as
the Empire keeps extending its reign.
Because each time they do,
millions and tens of millions die,
and we lose our freedom.
The reign brought upon heavy taxes,
oppression, and censorship.
They wreak havoc in the Aoi Sea
as they please.
I hate the Empire!
I hate the Empire,
but I don't hate you people.
That's why
when this war ends,
let's have a drink together
and watch a B-Cube concert.
He's a big man.
Yes, obviously.
No, I'm referring to his heart.
In that case, Master is big too!
We're all friends!
Hey!
What the hell?
He sure is.
PLANET NERO 66
I'm so bored. There's still three days
until high tide.
If you're so bored, spend more time
with me, Prince Shura.
No fair. He's mine tonight.
Fabiano should've come too.
We don't need that old man.
He's the former Oceans after all.
It's understandable that he can't agree
with the newer generation like us.
Callum, you should join us for a swim!
Not interested.
Shura, are you sure that Ziggy
is really going to come?
What he wants is the All-Link System,
and it's right here.
He'll definitely come here.
Prince Shura, we have uninvited guests
to deal with first.
The government army is headed towards
Nero 66.
This is an unexpected opportunity.
Once the government army arrives,
there will be a shootout.
We'll pass through their defense
and get inside.
Okay.
We will take down Shura,
and destroy the All-Link System.
Will you come with us?
Yeah.
Let's fight together.
In order to save Aoi Cosmos
and the androids!
-You bastard!
-Ibaraki.
How've you been?
About Boss...
I'll team up with Edens Zero.
But Laguna,
you're a whole different story.
You betrayed our organization,
so I don't see you as a comrade.
He says that,
but inside, he's not that mad.
You aimed a gun at me
the moment you saw me.
If I really wanted to kill you,
I would've shot you already.
Boss has to save face
in front of his men...
I know. Plus,
it's true that I left the organization.
But you came back!
In order to fight against Nero!
You never change, Ibaraki.
Everyone's doing well.
By the way, I've noticed that...
I haven't seen Princess.
Don't tell me!
Dammit.
She went to rescue some friends
that got caught,
but Shura killed her.
It was so bad that Princess's
beautiful face was unrecognizable.
That Shura is a psycho!
This is a battle to avenge her death!
Let's defeat him, Laguna!
Yeah.
Rebel army, and Princess...
Is this like some fantasy story where
she's the princess of a ruined country?
She's the daughter of the former leader.
She was bright and strong-minded.
After her father died,
she continued to support
the organization with
the current boss, Goodwin.
You lost a great member.
It's none of your business.
Wait.
Was taking down Nero
your objective all along?
That's why you got close with Drakken
who was also in Oración Seis Galáctica.
Then you approached us.
Witch is the one who invited me.
You were planning to contact us
even if Witch didn't invite you.
Or maybe it would've been Elsie?
Either way,
you've been searching for organizations
that can take down Nero.
You should join the government instead.
I might have, if I had education.
Don't drag us into
your personal vendetta.
Even if I wasn't here,
Shiki would've joined the fight.
If any of my crew
happens to die during this battle,
I will kill you!
Couchpo.
Wow, Rebecca! Looking good!
You look ready for battle!
Now's your last chance to get off.
This ship will soon enter battle mode.
Why are you telling me to go?
We're friends!
But...
Of course, I can't fight
like Shiki and the rest,
but I can protect this kitchen
and the smiles this place provides.
You just said that you can't fight.
If it's to protect my food,
I might awaken some kind of power!
What kind of situation is that?
Being on a ship together,
means living together.
I chose this ship myself.
Getting off whenever
things get dangerous
isn't exactly living together
with all of you.
Couchpo.
This ship will soon enter
the battle zone.
All members please gather at
the wheelhouse.
All right, let's go!
Once this battle is over,
let's all eat together!
Yeah!
Currently, the government army
and Shura's army are engaged in battle.
We will go past that,
and enter the planet.
Yet, there are no clear paths.
We will not be able to avoid a fight.
We'll cause a diversion.
With Edens Zero's speed,
you can get past the diversion.
Master.
What's the matter?
Those lights... are they explosions?
I wonder if people are dying,
every time there's a flash.
People are killing each other,
when they can possibly become friends.
Shiki.
You're a nice guy. But...
I know.
We'll move forward.
We'll take down Shura, and end this war.
The ocean above and below
are close to each other.
It's almost high tide.
Moscoy.
Brother, will you fight with us?
Honestly, I don't want to place
you in danger.
But I can't allow this ship to go down.
We did it, Mosco!
-Moscoy!
-Watch it!
-Enemy ships up ahead!
-We've been waiting!
Let's go, everyone!
Make a path for Edens Zero!
Show them what Maine Coon's firepower
is capable of!
-Dylan.
-Furena.
We're off!
Let's go, Russo!
Lizarre is taking off!
Gomakichi is off!
Ibaraki is taking off!
Wow.
But there's one that's obnoxiously loud.
Now's our chance to head to Nero 66!
Let's go at top speed!
Enemy next to us!
Fire the scorpion missile!
We're rushing in!
Prince Shura, there is a battleship
that passed the defense.
That's not a government army ship.
It's Ziggy's ship...
But what I'm sensing... is not Ziggy!
Who the hell is this black gravity?
Let's go!
The fierce battle called the Aoi War
has finally broken out.
This will end up being a difficult,
sad, and fierce battle
for Shiki and his crew.
What will be the outcome of the battle
involving the government army?
Will Ziggy and Edens One
end up showing themselves?
And the clash between
Gravity Ether Gear users,
Shiki and Shura.
But let's save all the excitement
for the near future.
Of course,
I know exactly when I'll get to
see you guys again.
Please look forward to that day.
Good day.
Edens Zero!
Charge forward at full speed!
Let the battle begin!