In the '90s,
when soda was good and marijuana was bad,
mortals sealed their love story
with a list of songs
they recorded on a cassette.
THE SOUNDTRACK TO OUR STORY
Each song represented
a unique moment in their story.
But the years went by,
marijuana was legalized in some places,
and soda was shunned,
and that cassette... was forgotten.
Five hundred years.
My first vacation in 500 years,
and this is what they do to me?
Damn. Watch out.
I'm sorry.
- Sorry, I didn't realize you were...
- What?
Blind?
No, I can see perfectly.
You're the one with problems
with his vision.
I don't have time for this.
- What? Is there a problem?
- Lots of problems.
Instead of being on a safari,
I'm here because of you.
But anyway, let's do this quickly.
This is yours.
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
Hello.
No music in this house
means no music in this house,
I thought we were clear on that.
Red Post-it means it's yours.
Green Post-it means it's mine.
Wow. How very fair.
You said you didn't want anything.
"I don't want anything
that reminds me of us"
doesn't mean
"I don't want any of our possessions."
For a lawyer,
you don't make things very clear.
For a musician,
you've got bad hearing, no?
Cheers.
Wow. Did I hear that right?
- You finally accepted that I make music?
- Yes.
Look. Clause three.
The house is yours, like we agreed.
So that you can make your music.
What was it called? Your little band?
- The Skates.
You weren't bad.
At least for weddings, and parties.
No, in fact, we were pretty good.
Could you let me finish reading this?
Thanks.
- Can I say something?
- Sure.
There's nothing more annoying
than your obsession
with chewing ice all the time.
- It annoys you?
- I've had it up to here.
This whole time you said it was cool.
Well I lied. Happy? I can't stand it.
There are all kinds of things
I'm sick of too!
Like what?
- The ham slicer is mine.
- You gave that to me.
Seriously? Out of everything in the house?
Just this?
What do you expect me to do
with a fucking lemon squeezer?
Make lemonade.
MANÁ
WHERE WILL THE CHILDREN PLAY?
That's yours.
You wanted it, right?
Remember?
You paid for it.
Carlos, this is ridiculous.
Can't we talk about it?
I think we've done too much talking,
and it's clear.
We made a mistake.
You think?
Because... I did fall in love.
- You were so...
- Handsome?
Interesting.
You were a whole new world for me.
It seems only like yesterday
that we went to that concert and...
I don't remember anything
about the concert.
I just remember you.
Looking at me.
You were... You are different.
Wow. That's by far
the nicest compliment I've ever gotten.
I was looking for something different.
What do you mean?
- Different from what? From whom?
- It doesn't matter.
But that day, at the concert...
Well, Cupid got it wrong, right?
Fucking Cupid.
Seriously?
This is how you want to do things?
THE SOUNDTRACK TO OUR STORY
- Was it you?
- How could it have been me?
- Then someone's in the house.
- There's no one here.
I just turned off the stereo.
Of course you did.
I promise you I just turned it off.
There's someone here...
- Carlos, someone's in the house.
- You think?
Do you see anyone?
Are you expecting someone?
Take anything you want. Anything!
You?
- But in formal attire, dude.
- You know him?
I just saw him on the street,
but I'm calling the police.
- Where's my phone?
- Here it is, darling.
How is that possible?
How do I know? I was born this way.
I've done it for thousands of years.
Who is he?
So worked up just because
I dropped in unannounced.
This is how you treat guests?
You think I'm a burglar, right?
What would I even steal?
Take whatever you want with a red Post-it.
It's clear you're not familiar
with Cupid's Code of Honor.
- Whose?
- Cupid's.
Cupid!
- Did he say Cupid?
- Yes, he did.
- Say my name once more and I'm gone.
- Cupid.
- I'm still here.
- Cupid doesn't exist.
Well, we do. There are a few of us.
I'm the one you got.
But we come in all shapes and sizes.
Black, blond, tall, he, she, they.
The baby in a diaper
with a bow and arrow, that too.
But no, Charlie, we don't exist.
Here I am, look.
Appearing and disappearing in your house,
drinking your cheap whisky.
- Who are you and what do you want?
- I don't want anything.
Cupids give. We give love.
That's what we do.
We're not harming anyone.
But could you?
Of course, but that's not the point.
My first day of vacation
and I'm stuck here with you.
Why?
Because you thought, you decided,
for some fucking reason, I made a mistake.
And I, Cupid, am never wrong.
I don't get it.
Let's suppose that out of pure chance,
life's circumstances, twists of fate,
past mistakes, pain that destroys love,
it was actually the both of you
who messed up, or rather, fucked up.
Couldn't you be the one who fucked up
from the beginning?
So you really think he's Cupid?
I don't know, but if he is,
I want a refund.
What? Is something funny?
Let's see if it's funny
when I call the cops.
No, Charlie. This isn't a joke.
- It's an offer.
- And what are you offering?
- Seriously?
- I don't know, we've got to ask.
I'm offering you to never
fall in love with each other.
What do you say?
Happy Valentine's Day.
What happened?
- I don't know.
- Carlos, this cube was...
So, what do you think?
Get in, darlings, let's go for a spin.
Not a chance,
first explain how the fuck...
Did we get in the car?
- Carlos, what's happening?
- I don't know.
Let's get something clear.
I don't owe anyone explanations.
Least of all mortals.
And the car? Have some respect, dude.
It's a classic.
My mom gave it to me.
I'm Cupid. What did you think?
I'd take you on the subway?
Get ready for the ride of your lives,
little ones.
- Not so fast, please.
- Elenita, it's not that fast. Relax.
Eyes on the road, please.
My eyes are always on the road.
The question is, what about yours?
Carlos, what's happening?
Where are we going?
To the past.
- Where's the seatbelt?
- There isn't one.
What?
- A car!
- Where?
- Concentrate on what's important!
- I'm doing just that.
I don't make mistakes.
I don't get it wrong. Understood?
Me neither. And then there's this.
I twist this side
and it fucks up the other.
I twist that side and fuck up this one.
- Concentrate on driving now!
- Hey, mortals.
I'm going to give you
the benefit of the doubt.
And I've got lots of them.
I'm going to give you
the extraordinary opportunity
to prove that I was wrong,
which isn't the case.
And if I'm wrong, I'll fix it,
which isn't going to happen.
So please, relax already.
Elen, get that look off your face,
for the love of God.
Charlie, relax, please. You're panting.
You're gonna have a panic attack.
Breathe in and out.
In and out. In and out.
Hold on tight
because we're headed for the past. Yeah!
THE FUTURE IS HERE
We're here, darlings. Thank you.
Where?
- We're here?
- Yes.
- In heaven?
- You guys? Yeah, right.
- Where are we?
- Are we... dead?
No, honey, you've still got...
a few years.
- The car... The car is...
- Adapted to the time period, Elen.
We have to blend in, right? Lame.
That's Cristina's house.
It's the party where...
Okay, guys, pay attention,
both of you, okay?
When the soundtrack to our story ends,
kaputt, finito, okay?
We'll go back to your sad reality,
or whatever.
So you only have five songs left.
Capisce?
No, I don't "capisce."
Fuck!
Again.
Bye!
Watch out!
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry. I didn't see you there.
Well, I was looking where I was going,
but then you came out of nowhere
and I couldn't stop.
- Are you okay, sir?
- Elena.
How do you know my name? Ma'am!
- Is she okay?
- She just needs air.
- I'll get water if you like.
- No, it's fine.
- It was my fault.
No, it's fine.
- I scared her.
- No, she just needs air, that's all.
Air. Okay.
How's it going? Is this where the gig is?
- She's fainted.
- Hang on.
Awesome.
We don't know what to do.
- What are you doing?
- Damn, I swear I dreamed that...
Gabo?
Gabo.
Whoa, hi, do we know each other?
Sorry, we've had a really long trip.
And with the time change and the jet lag,
it's been a long time.
Time traveling is complicated, but...
Paco, Beto, Memo. I can't believe it.
Wow, bro, she's psycho!
Eleniux, your mom is a psychic.
- No, my mom's dead.
- Oh, yeah.
You're The Skates, right?
- Yeah!
- Wow, we're famous.
We know you from Instagram...
- From where?
- Insta-what?
- What's that?
- Is that a bar?
- Aren't you going to be late?
- No, but how do you know us?
We're music managers.
We manage lots of small bands
that we're...
We're a band!
We're always looking for new talent.
- We look for new bands, help them grow...
- So they really take off.
- That's crazy.
- And we saw you in Gatopardo yesterday.
- Yes.
- And we liked what we heard.
You were at the gig?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
And you really reminded me of myself
when I was young.
Well, we're going to play again
in a bit, at the party.
Yes, we want to watch if we can.
Sure, in fact, we have to go.
It's our turn.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Okay, see you in a bit.
Pleasure to meet you.
Hey, later you'll have to tell me
where Instagram is. Sounds cool.
- Yeah.
- Sounds up-and-coming.
Up-and-coming...
Right, if today's the party,
tomorrow is the Maná concert.
In 24 hours.
- Tomorrow is when we...
- Have our first kiss.
And the rest is history.
What if we never went to the concert?
We don't have our first kiss.
And we don't fall in love.
And we change the plot of our story.
We came to pick up our son. Excuse us.
Careful, there's a cable here.
Where's Charlie? Over there?
- I'll see you a little later.
- Chickless.
Maybe people shouldn't walk
across as much.
Dude! Found you.
- Excuse me. How are you?
- You're a legend, Chickless.
No, no. Get your own. They're over there.
I need these two, dude.
They're called Goodbye, Shame
and Hello, Courage.
Courage for what?
For the hunt, man.
I'm getting me a girl, dude.
I'll believe it when I see it.
You couldn't hook up with a coat hanger.
You're "chick-less".
Bro, I won't say anything to that
because you're...
Well, you were my wingman.
Don't be an ass, Chickless.
I'm not an ass.
- Photo, boys? For the magazine.
- Yes, please.
Please.
- There. One more.
- Of course.
Another pose.
Look serious.
- Thanks.
- Cool.
Look, man. There's our prey.
Go ahead.
I miss you, Charlie. I miss you, man.
We were like Maverick and Goose
in Top Gun.
But you died on me.
We don't go to war together anymore.
- Wait, hang on.
- Yeah?
Am I Goose?
Of course. Only I could be Maverick.
I'm just like Tom Cruise.
Right. Tell me, who drives your Ninja?
- Just you.
- That's what I thought.
Charlie!
- Cristi...
- I want one too. Thanks for the drink!
- Should we take a picture?
- Yeah.
Thank you so much.
- She took away your shame, man.
- I've still got plenty of courage.
Cheers, my love.
Cheers.
I'll go get Disappointment and Loneliness.
- New friends?
- New drinks.
Well, are you ready?
- Seriously?
- Of course, sweetie.
I'll give them to the girls,
and you to the boys, okay?
- Really?
- Yes. Happy Valentine's Day, sweethearts!
Come on.
Thanks for coming. Enjoy. You're so cute.
Come with me.
- Happy Valentine's Day, sweetie.
- Here you go.
Charlie, keep some candles for the cake
for tomorrow's dinner.
What dinner? Happy Valentine's...
My whole family is coming to celebrate
my grandma turning almost 90.
My uncle, a top lawyer,
is also going to be there.
He negotiated NAFTA and all.
And guess what?
I told him about you.
Cutie, you're in shock.
You know, it's better to know who
than to know how.
But Cristi, tomorrow is the Maná concert,
I already have the tickets, remember?
Charlie, how many birthdays do you think
my grandma is going to have?
Cristi, but... they're VIP, I bought them
ages ago and they cost a fortune.
You bought them last week in...
A photo for the magazine. Nice and close.
- Is that a camera?
- Yes.
- What magazine are you from?
- Eres?
What are you doing?
Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day, everyone!
Sofi, you look lovely. Enjoy.
My love, when did you ask me?
Because I have no memory of
wanting to see...
Maná, Cristi. Maná.
But, why would I go and see them?
I don't like their music,
I don't like the vibe.
I don't feel like going.
Enjoy! I mean, if it were
Luis Miguel, I'd think about it.
- But Maná? Really?
- Cristi, it's live and VIP.
This dinner could make your life
VIP forever.
Get it?
My love, I can't go. My parents
will kill me if I'm not at the dinner.
But I promise you'll have
an incredible time with me.
I went to the concert, but not with her.
Anyway, it's showtime.
If anyone here still believes in love,
Happy Valentine's Day.
A candle.
- To sing to love.
- Right.
- Charlie!
- What's up?
I'll see you in my dreams, sweetie.
What an amazing woman!
She's just very pretty, that young lady.
You're very lucky to have her.
- She's your future. Trust me.
- Okay.
- And buy dollars.
- Dollars?
Thanks so much for coming.
It's time to sing our tribute to love.
So, light your candles
and grab your other half.
Charlie!
It's nice to be talked to like that.
- Come up here, sweetie.
- Go on.
- Sweetie, come up here!
- Go for it.
- Come on.
- No photos. Seriously.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
This is Charlie, the sweetness in my life.
Everyone!
I'm here
So in love
With you
The night lasts a little longer
The cry of a city
The humidity can be seen on our faces
I'll be by your side
For longer than life
I swear I'll love you more up above
- Bravo! Bravo!
- Thank you.
Charlie.
I love you, sweetie.
Will you light my candle?
Okay.
Hurry.
Happy Valentine's Day, sweeties!
We're the best.
The candle. Hey!
I love you.
What's happening?
Fire.
- Fire?
- Fire.
- Where? What's happening?
- Excuse me.
- Fire!
- I'm gonna die! Put it out!
Put it out! Put it...
Cristi, wait!
- Chickless! Chickless!
- It was all down to Disappointment.
Maybe it's best
to blow out your candles, please.
Chickless is so brave!
Right, well,
after that beautiful performance
by the princess and her sweetie,
we're going to play a few tunes.
We're The Skates!
And tonight we have a very special guest.
Katy Berry.
Can you hear me? Yes.
Hi. Good evening, everyone. Hello.
I'm really happy to be here today.
Thanks for the invite.
It's going to be great.
One, two, three, four!
It's a bad idea to raise my blood pressure
To squash my ambition
Carry on and you'll see
I look at my watch
It's much later than yesterday
I would wait for you again
And I won't do it
I won't do it
Where is our mistake with no solution?
Was it my fault or yours?
You can't change me, no one can
A thousand bells play in my heart
It's so difficult to say sorry
Stop.
Go, you never understood me
Sorry.
- Are you crazy or what?
- I'm fine. I'm fine...
You've got a screw lose.
- Hey, but who's going to pay us?
- The console's fucked.
Hey, hey. Calm down.
It was an accident and everything's fine.
Calm down?
Your psycho partner ruined the show.
Chill, don't be like that.
Damn it.
Are you okay?
Did you get burned?
Yes, but I'm fine.
Can I see?
- Yes, it looks worse than it is.
- Yes, it does feel...
Sorry.
- No, it's fine.
- Hold it there.
Okay.
Give me your hand. There.
There.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- Better?
- Yes, thanks.
- Carlos!
- What?
- Fucking do something!
I'm going to fall in love.
You dropped these.
No...
You're going to see Maná!
- In theory.
- What do you mean "in theory"?
You're joking, right? I was dying to go,
but I couldn't get tickets.
You're... a big fan.
Totally, I love them.
The thing is, I'm from Guadalajara,
Maná is practically my ZIP code.
- Right.
- What are you doing?
Nothing.
Sorry.
I've got this obsession
with chewing ice when...
It's really annoying, right?
No, it's cool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
See? You always said it was really cool.
With you looking and smiling
at me like that, what was I going to say?
I was handsome, right?
You were.
I don't understand how you can have
the tickets in your hand and not go.
I'm being a bit intense, right?
- What's your name?
- Too intense, definitely.
I hate that fucking smile of yours.
Not yours, his.
What's your name?
Elena. Yours?
- I...
- Sweetie, right?
I'm Carlos. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Carlos.
No, where is everyone?
Charlie!
- Charlie!
- She's looking for you.
I have to go.
- Good luck.
- But...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yes.
- Wait, tomorrow? Why?
- Charlie!
Charlie!
Cristi, are you okay?
I wanted to say sorry for...
Where is everyone?
What happened to the music?
- Aren't you angry with me?
- Aren't you listening? Do something!
I can't believe it!
- He gave me his ticket! To see Maná. VIP!
- Wow.
And he's so handsome, right?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
I don't know, not really.
I mean, he looks like
he's got bad intentions.
What? No, not at all.
What's up?
You won't believe what just happened.
What?
Me? Bad intentions?
- We've got to...
- No, I'm a gentleman and you know it.
We have to do whatever's necessary
to change our future.
Of course, you and I are like...
like the Terminator.
We've come from the future
to change our present
and save our fates.
- That's so cheesy.
- But it's true.
The console's fucked.
Everyone left, we can't play.
We don't need that to play.
What do we do?
I don't know, we have to make sure
they don't go to the concert.
Thanks, Einstein, that much was obvious.
I don't know. We take her ticket.
- Steal it?
- No, that's a crime. We just take it.
He met her at 15
That's my song!
He opened the blue door
Fell in love
Dreams in the air
Diamonds fall from the sky
Not enough to live on
Again and again
He stayed in her arms
Kneeling at her feet
He fell
Seduces like a heart
Leads to fragility
This story's worse than the original.
I think it's better.
That's why it's worse.
The beginning of the end.
A blue door
Should never be opened
The nightmares are very long...
Tomorrow he takes her to the concert,
they fall in love and...
A few years later we're sticking on
red and green Post-its.
A blue door shouldn't even be touched
It's better to leave it
I know that look.
Great song!
Amazing!
The locks never worked.
Hey!
You had a gun in the van?
We worked at night. We had to be careful.
Hey, hey!
- I'll take it.
- In your dreams.
You don't know how to use it.
The question is, where are we going
to corner your mini-me?
Why my mini-me and not your mini-me?
Because I'm not missing that concert,
and I've got the gun.
If the past hasn't changed yet,
I know where to find me tomorrow.
Perfect.
Fuck!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, fine.
The safety wasn't on.
There are two left.
- Two what?
- Two songs.
If this goes well and we get
a second chance,
I hope you don't waste it.
I can't believe
you're still on about that.
I don't know if you've really got
the talent to be a musician.
I do know you think
that's your true passion, and it's not.
Your passion is being a mom,
and that's the truth.
That's enough.
Being a mom and living my dream
are not mutually exclusive,
they never were.
But it was impossible for you
to understand that, and I gave in.
- Don't get so worked up about it.
- I will if I want to.
But you know what? I'm not angry with you.
I'm furious with myself
for having stayed silent.
Because if what happened hadn't happened,
I'm sure I still would be silent.
You were holding back, then.
- Let's get this over with, okay?
- Yes.
- You don't even know where we are.
- Of course I do.
It's that way.
That way, that way.
After what happened with Cristi's hair,
I highly doubt...
she'll throw another party.
The thing is... Thanks. I turned around...
- and she was standing there.
- Who?
- Elena.
Singing amazingly.
She skates great.
And when I saw her eyes, I froze.
It was like...
- I'll swap you Higuita for Stoichkov.
- Sure.
Roberto Baggio. Italian.
He's a machine. Never missed a penalty.
Are you listening, man?
Of course not.
But anyway, you saw her, boom,
she captivated you, boom,
and here we are.
I'm hungover, you're sober,
you've got a girl, I've got a drink,
same as ever.
ICE CREAM AND COFFEE
Got Batistuta?
- I don't know...
- Have a good look.
Let's go.
- Here he is. What have you got for me?
- Hang on.
Table for two?
- We're with friends, thanks.
- Great, come in.
- Dude... Ramoncito Ramírez.
- Give it here.
Katy Berry?
You? Have you brought the photos?
Easy, or my partner will
put a bullet in you.
Move over.
Relax, we're not bad people.
- We're good at doing bad things.
- Really good.
What do you want?
The concert ticket.
What are you talking about?
The ticket that's in your wallet
next to the photo of Brooke Shields.
- Oh, man, I'll give you all my money.
- You don't have any.
- Take my watch.
- It's fake.
- I knew it.
- I'll give you my car.
Your car? Your GTS Turbo?
Just so you can go
to the concert with her?
- Seriously?
- Really?
Your mom is called Valeria
and your dad, like you, is Carlos too.
You're an only child,
you have hay fever, according to you.
You've actually got
a bit of a gluten problem.
- What's gluten?
- You wear underwear with cartoons on.
You support Dallas.
You bet on the Super Bowl.
Your girlfriend is Cristi,
you've been together for a year,
and you'd be stupid to let her get away.
- Your cologne is expensive, right?
- You use a shitload.
Your turbocharged Shadow GTS,
with detachable stereo
and JBL speakers that rock your world...
That's the stuff you love most
in life, right?
Sorry, excuse me.
CALL ME - MOM
My mom. Continue, please.
Hey.
I know everything about you, don't I?
Dude, this is next level intelligence.
I've read about cases like this.
The next step is torture with water.
We don't have all day,
so put the ticket on the table now.
Okay, okay. Chill, chill.
Run, Charlie.
No! Don't torture me, please!
Calm down, calm down.
- Give me the ticket and I'll go.
- Why me? Why this ticket?
I'm you from the future.
Can't you see that? Well, I'm a bit older.
I'm like the Terminator, I've come from
the future to change the past, present...
and change your destiny a little,
that's all.
- I haven't seen Terminator.
- Right.
We're here to stop you
from marrying Elena.
- Marry her? I just met her.
- Please.
You changed your clothes six times.
The leather jacket, then the denim one.
You spent three hours thinking
about where to take her to dinner.
Bad night, right?
You couldn't sleep
because you kept thinking about her.
Carlos.
Elena isn't good for you.
Will you stay with Cristina?
- Give it to me!
- No!
Carlos!
Freeze, everyone! Freeze!
No videos for social media!
I'll shoot the first person I see
uploading a video to TikTok!
Hey!
Put your phones away.
If you kill him, you kill me. Calm down.
Give me the ticket.
Have you ever looked into someone's eyes
and immediately saw their soul?
Give me the ticket, please.
That was how I felt yesterday.
Looking into her eyes was worth more
than 1,000 conversations.
I'm serious.
It's not just a concert.
It's seeing her again.
What for?
To start a thousand conversations.
- She's not good for you.
- Didn't you hear me?
She's the love of my life,
so now I have to convince her
that I'm the love of her life.
I want to win her over.
I'm going to do it
and I'm going to make her happy.
That's why I have to go to that concert.
Please, don't take this ticket away.
Please.
What?
- Who told you that?
- I had your baby.
That's why I know.
And if what happened yesterday
were real...
But you aren't going to make me happy,
and I won't make you happy either.
It's best you don't see me again.
Carlos, the keys to the Shadow.
They're in the other pocket.
Let's go.
Charlie.
This might not be the right moment
to tell you this, but...
I got Maradona.
- The seatbelt doesn't work.
- It never did, remember?
I don't remember.
I never wore it back then.
Would you have shot me?
What do you think?
You seemed very sure.
- It's clear you're dying for a new life.
- Aren't you?
Enough to kill someone? I don't know.
Are you sure I was going to shoot?
What a criminal record we have now.
Armed robbery, stealing his car,
stealing his wallet.
Technically, we didn't steal anything
from anyone,
because we're driving my car,
it's my wallet, and the ticket's in it.
Sure, tell that to the judge, Mr. Lawyer.
What did you tell him
so he'd give you the ticket?
Something that only the two of us know.
Wow. That was something
between you and me, wasn't it?
Well, technically it's still between
you and me, isn't it?
- What?
- No, nothing.
That smile.
It's been a while since
I've seen you smile, and you look nice.
- Carlos.
- What?
- Look, my ring's gone.
- Did you drop it?
No, it's disappeared, I haven't even
got the mark on my finger...
Carlos!
- We did it.
- We did.
I won't go to the concert,
and we'll never see each other again.
- And... we'll both have different fates.
- Yes.
Different.
Should we celebrate?
Do you remember how this car sounded?
I think... I was never in this car.
Of course you were, this was where...
No, not anymore. I was never in this car.
ELENA AND THE SKATES
GET GOLDEN RECORD!
- Your hair!
- What?
What did I do to my hair?
Carlos, are you wearing hair oil?
Damn. Gel.
So much gel.
I'm the wannabe Prince Charles.
I'm practically a mural.
Fuck, where's my chest hair?
Carlos.
I'm not wearing a seatbelt
and... I don't care.
I need a cigarette.
- You smoke?
- Yes, lots of things.
I need a drink.
- You drink?
- Constantly.
We did it.
We're going to... forget each other.
I think this...
is over.
Elena, hey.
When I said "different"...
I meant passionate, brave, joyful,
that's what I saw in you.
I saw fire in your eyes
and I fell in love.
Now that was a proper compliment.
A little late, but thank you anyway.
I saw you on that stage singing,
and there was that fire in your eyes.
And you know what?
It's too much for me.
I don't know how to handle it.
Carlitos, our son, knew how
to bring out that look.
He was the soundtrack to our story.
Without music, there's not much
of a story to tell.
It's all right, we're going to be okay.
Right?
Elena.
Elena? Elena!
Elena!
57702... 54...
61... All right.
I remembered my parents' number.
Mini-me, pick up, please, pick up.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Mom?
It can't be.
Who is this?
Carlitos? Honey, is it you?
No, sorry. I'm a... policeman.
We found your son's car. I wanted
to know if he could tell us anything.
Officer. Carlitos isn't here,
but it was a scary situation.
You can imagine.
Maybe your son could help us
with the investigation.
Sure, if you want to give me your details,
I'll ask him to call you when he's back.
Would that be okay?
No, I don't know. Do you want to talk...
Thank you, Officer, but no. I mean,
I'm terrified, he's my son. Are you a dad?
Let's see...
Of course. I made it.
Before the concert.
I was a dad too, I had a son.
And, well, there was a car accident.
Oh, my God.
And I lost him.
No! No, no, no!
Where are you? Where are you?
What... What have we done?
And, well, now he's gone.
- He'll never exist.
- I'm so sorry, Officer.
He'll live forever in your heart.
No, he won't. He won't exist. We decided.
He had... light hair.
He had brown hair. Brown hair.
Deep eyes.
He was 1.30 meters high...
Children are like
the soundtrack to our story.
When the soundtrack to our story ends,
kaputt, finito, okay?
Have you ever looked into someone's eyes
and immediately saw their soul?
It's not just a concert,
it's seeing her again.
The last song.
One last song... one last song.
Hi, it's Carlos.
Thanks.
No, thank you.
Hats! Maná hats!
Hats! Get a Maná hat!
- Thanks.
- Maná hats!
Get a Maná hat!
How much?
Hi, Cristi.
Well, come in,
my grandma wants to meet you.
This guy?
What's up?
- No, don't torture me, please!
- Javier!
Hey.
How do you know my name?
- No one knows my name.
- But I do.
I know this is very weird.
But I'm Carlos. Your best friend.
What did you do to your hair?
Gel, and a lot of it but, hey,
I can tell you all about
Miguel Mejía Barón's lineup.
A ton of information
about the future of football.
Like what?
I can tell you who wins the World Cup.
Okay, and what do I have to do?
Get your wingman to the concert
before it ends. That's all.
- But we'll never get there in that.
- We will on your Ninja.
I don't know how to drive my bike.
But I do.
- Miguel Herrera doesn't go?
- No, and it gets worse.
Hugo Sánchez doesn't play
in the decisive match.
- And you know who misses a penalty?
- Who?
Roberto Baggio.
With all the mess the Zapatistas
have made, we need someone like Colosio.
Yes, of course.
And you? Who will you vote for?
Me? I don't know yet.
Sweetie, there's not really
a decision to make.
- Right. We're here.
- Okay.
- Now what?
- You get him out of there.
You give him this ticket
and tell him to go to the concert.
- Me?
- Who else?
The psycho who stole his car and ticket
and fucked up his life out of fear?
Chickless.
You're his best friend. His wingman.
Okay, I'll do it.
- You will?
- Yeah.
- Right...
- Chickless!
Okay.
You're our only hope, okay?
Okay!
Go for it!
Go on!
Carlos.
Sorry, I thought you were someone else.
I got confused, sorry.
The best choice, honey. Delicious!
Oh, baby.
- Chickless?
- What?
- How disgusting, Cristina! Not here.
- What's wrong with you two?
Daddy, relax. I'm...
Chickless? What's he doing here?
- Is it the gardener?
- What's wrong with your friend?
- Your friend?
- Charlie!
I got your ticket back!
Come on, there's still a chance.
What's happening?
- He's running towards the glass window.
- The dumbass will...
My window!
What's that?
- It's my ticket.
- I'm going to call the police.
Your ticket, Charlie.
I'm hope. I got it back.
What are you doing in my house
and who the hell are you?
He's Chickless.
He's my wingman.
- And he's here for me.
- Charlie, what's going on?
If you take that ticket, we're through.
My love...
Carlos, come back here!
How are you?
Charlie, who knows you better than me?
Who?
Even you don't know yourself better
than I do.
I've never seen you like that over a girl.
Don't fuck it up.
Chickless, we won't make it.
Yes, we will.
You again?
Hell no, I'm not going with that madman.
I thought I was the only one
who knew how to ride that bike.
Exactly. Only you know how.
I know this sounds crazy,
but I promise if you don't
get on this bike,
this is the future in store for you.
Wearing an ascot, slicked back hair,
living in daddy's bubble.
Come on!
Go ahead.
Ticket?
Sun coming up
Coming up for you
This regret hurts
It burns without your love
You haven't called me
I'm desperate
The last song.
I've cried for you for many moons
Come on!
Sun coming up
- We did it.
- Yes.
Hey.
Don't fuck it up.
This is like a second chance.
Yes.
Any advice?
- Yes. Don't chew ice.
- But she said it was cool.
No, forget it. She hates it.
Don't chew ice. Okay?
- Okay.
- Say goodbye to that habit forever.
Okay.
One thing.
When you see Mom,
give her a big kiss from both of us?
Okay.
And every time you get in the car,
use the seatbelt.
Get in the car, seatbelt, always.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Carlos.
Good luck.
- Ticket?
- Yeah.
- It has to be here.
- What happened?
- In that tiny pocket.
- No, no, no!
I can't find the ticket.
Oh, shit!
You dropped it.
Now go and kiss me
before the last song's over.
- You?
- No, silly! Not me, the other me! Go!
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
Good luck!
Hi.
That... damn smile again.
That... damn look again.
Sun coming up
Desperation
It's easier to reach the sun
Than your heart
I'm dying for you
Living without you
I can't cope
It hurts so much to be like this
Sun coming up
Sun coming up, the sun
The sun
I want you
I miss you
I want to change.
I love you
I love you more
I feel like I was only thinking about me,
and I'd forgotten about you.
I love you
I want you to be happy.
I miss you
I thought you weren't coming.
And miss out on my future with you? Never.
I want you to do concerts, make music,
fill stadiums, that people...
You talk too much.
That's beautiful.
- When...
- Miss me?
- Damn, you could've warned us!
- Charlie, love is always unexpected.
- Yes, but it's not this scary.
- It can be.
What now?
Listen...
So fucking beautiful.
Let's go.
- What happened?
- I don't know what happened.
- We were...
Asleep.
My clothes.
What happened?
My hair.
My tattoos are gone.
Was it a dream?
- What's going on?
- Look.
THE SKATES
Elena.
I didn't finish signing.
I don't want you to.
Me neither.
Mom! Dad! Come!
Look what I found!
With You in the Future
Careful.
What do we have here?
First, I jumped a two-meter high fence.
Then... a dog, a rabid dog chased me.
And then, I smashed through a window,
there was smoke, glass...
Why on earth would you do that?
Well...
My friend's future depended on it.
So you're not crazy, you're a hero.
Love is the soundtrack to our story.
As long as you want to listen to it,
it doesn't just play on, it evolves.