♪ The earth
♪ Is in a blaze
♪ The world
♪ Is in amaze
♪ The way
♪ Of life today
♪ Is strange and odd
♪ Would happen
♪ Across the sea
♪ May come
♪ To you and me
♪ Whoa, come
♪ Let us go back
♪ To God
♪ Go back
Oh, come on
♪ Let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
let's go back to God
♪ Come on
♪ Let us go back
let's go back to God
♪ I know the way
♪ Without my Lord
let's go back to God
♪ It's mighty hard
♪ Whoa, yeah
let's go back to God
♪ That I know the path
♪ Wander path, yeah
let's go back to God
♪ Left his mark
♪ Of hallowed troughs
♪ Let's go back to God
♪ Come on, yes
let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
♪ Go back to God
come let us go back
♪ To God ♪
(snoring)
(beeping)
(snoring continues)
(door opens)
Uh!
Oh...
Afternoon, Mrs. Munson.
Afternoon, Sheriff.
You know the Funthes boy?
Um...
Mackatee Funthes?
Oh, no, not him.
Weemack.
Mackatee's eldest.
Oh, yeah...
I don't believe I do.
Well, he's a good boy and all,
but he done gone down
to the Costco in Pascagoula
and got hisself a blaster.
What?
And he been playing
that music.
Well, if you want,
you know, I could&
Loud!
Well, I could go talk
to him if you...
"Left My Wallet
in El Segundo."
He left his wallet?
Hippityhop music!
You know, they calls it
hippityhop music,
but it don't make me
want to go hippityhop.
Hm.
And Othar don't like
that music neither.
It's been disturbin'
Othar then, has it?
Well, how could it help but do?
"Left My Wallet
in El Segundo"!
He left his wall--
And, Sheriff, do you know
what they call colored folks
in them songs?
Have you got any idea?
No, ma'am, I don't think...
Niggers!
I don't even want
to say the word.
Now, I won't say it twice,
I can tell you that.
I say it one time...
Yes, ma'am.
...in the course of swearin'
down my complaint.
Yes'm.
Niggers!
Mm-mm-mm!
2000 years after Jesus!
30 years after
Martin Luther King!
The age of Montel!
Mm-mm-mm!
Sweet lord of mercy,
is that where we at?
Mm-hmm.
Weemack down to Pascagoula
and gettin' hisself
a big ol' thumpety stereo
so he can listen to that trash!
Sheriff, you got
to help that boy.
You want me to help him?
Extend that helpin' hand.
Show an interest.
Well, we're here to help.
Well, God bless you for that.
You don't want to be tried
and found wantin'.
No, ma'am.
No, many, many done
tunkalow parzen, Sheriff.
Many, many done tunkalow parzen.
Many what, ma'am?
You been tried
and found wantin'!
You don't want that writin'
on the wall.
Oh, no, ma'am.
Don't want that on the wall.
Feast of Balthazar.
Yeah, that sounds good.
The apostle John said,
"Behold, there's a stranger
in our midst.
Come to destroy us."
(both) Yes, ma'am.
♪ Come
♪ Let us go back...
♪ ...to God,
go back to God
♪ Oh, come on,
let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
♪ Come on
let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
♪ Come on, yes!
let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
♪ Go back to God
Aw. Do you need somethin'
to eat, angel?
(strikes match)
Othar, I went and complained
about Weemack today.
Don't know if it'll do any good.
That boy hangin' by a thread.
Over the pit.
Fiery pit!
"Left My Wallet in El Segundo."
Ooh!
67 years of life.
46 years of marriage.
You mean to tell me you never
once suffered from piles?
Well, it's the human condition.
Most humans, anyhow.
Like that ballplayer said,
"The world's got
two kind of folks.
Them that's got the piles
and them that's goin' get 'em.
But you always
was healthy as a ox.
Passed on 'fore you could
get the piles. Mm-hmm.
Ooh, thank the Lord
you never was sick.
I just want to pass away
nice and peaceful.
Go to sleep one night, wake up
in the glory land! Whoo!
(meows)
(knocking on door)
Pickles!
Go fetch Pickles!
Pickles?
Oh, he's up that tree again!
You better shimmy on up.
Well, I do apologize,
madam, but...
won't the feline eventually
tire of his lonely perch
and, pining for
his master's affection,
return on his own initiative?
Eh, the point being, must we
actually ascend the tree?
Look, I don't want
no doubletalk.
Now, if you not gon' fetch him,
I guess I gotta call the police.
Police?
And they not
goin' be happy.
Every time they
have to fetch him,
they swear they'll
never do it no more.
No need to call
the authorities, madam.
I did this often as a child.
I was a positive lemur.
Here, kitty!
Oh, don't upset him now!
I wouldn't think
of it, madam.
Harmless little Felix
domesticus. (grunts)
Here, Kitty. Come to G.H.
Come, come. Here kitty.
Here, kitty.
(cat growls)
Come, come, come.
No, no, no.
That's not how
Sheriff Wyner do it.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come, come, come.
(hisses)
Come to the professor.
Yes. Y-- Ah!
(rattling)
Uh... thank you, madam,
for your act of kindness.
Well, you let him out.
I certainly did,
and for that
I apologize no end.
Allow me to present myself,
um, formally.
Goldthwait Higginson Dorr, Ph.D.
Like Elmer?
I beg your pardon, ma'am?
Fudd.
No, no, Ph.D. is a mark
of academic attainment
bestowed, in my case,
in recognition of
my mastery
of the antique languages
of Latin and Greek.
I also hold a number
of other advanced degrees,
including the baccalaureate
from a school in Paris, France,
called the Sorbonne.
Sore bone.
Well, that fits.
You ever study
at Bob Jones University?
I have not had that privilege.
Oh, that's a Bible school.
Only the finest in the country.
I send 'em $5 every month.
That is very generous...
I'm on the mailin' list!
Indeed.
I'm a Angel.
Are you? Yes.
Oh, they list my name in
the newsletter every issue.
Do they?
Oh, I got the literature
right over here,
if you'd like
to examine it...
Perhaps when my head has
recovered from its,
uh... uh, buffeting.
Mrs. Munson, are you
at all curious as to
why I darkened your door,
as the expression would have it,
on this lovely, lovely
camellia-scented morn?
Well, I was wonderin'
till you let Pickles out.
I quite understand.
Then in all the excitement,
I just--
The fact is, I saw
the sign in your window
advertising
a room to let?
And there are no other
such signs among the houses
on this charming,
charming street.
Yeah, I got a room.
$15 a week.
I'm lookin'
for a quiet tenant.
Madam, you are addressing
a man who is quiet
and yet not quiet.
If I may offer a riddle.
I am currently on sabbatical
from the institution
where I teach,
the University of Mississippi
at Hattiesburg.
I am takin' a year off
to indulge my passion,
and I do not believe that
is too strong a word,
for the music of
the Renaissance.
Mm-hmm.
I perform in, and have
the honor of directing,
a period instrument ensemble
that performs at Renaissance
Fairs and other cultural fora
throughout central
and southern Mississippi.
We perform on the instruments
for which the music was
originally composed.
Now, wait a minute.
You got some kind of band?
Oh, no. Eh, the word "band"
would be, in this context,
something of a misnomer.
Though we do play together
- hence the word "ensemble" -
the nature of the music
is such that,
well, one would hesitate
to apply the epithet "band,"
with connotations
of janglin' rhythms.
So y'all ain't playi''
no hippityhop?
"I Left My Wallet
in El Segundo."
Songs with the titles
spelled all funny?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We play music
that has been composed
to the greater glory of God.
Devotional music.
Church music.
Gospel music?
Well, inspired by
the gospel, certainly.
The vintage, of course, is no
more recent than the Rococo.
Rococo, huh?
Well, I guess that'd be OK.
But I don't propose to inflict
our rehearsals on you.
May I inquire,
do you have a root cellar?
Ah... Yes.
Yes, yes.
This looks promising.
A little dank, ain't it?
Indeed. That only
improves the acoustics.
(bellows)
Marvelous.
Yes. Ah!
Oh, these earthen walls
are ideal for baffling
the higher registers of
the, uh... lute or sackbut.
(imitates instrument)
That is why so much music
of the cinquecento
was played in crypts
and catacombs.
This is ideal.
This is perfect.
This is more than perfect.
I can scarcely contain my glee.
Oh, you containin' it OK.
(♪ "Trouble In, Trouble Out"
by Nappy Roots)
See, you gotta peel
this shit out, man.
Sometimes it stick
to the bottom.
Hey, this shit smells
like piles.
You wouldn't even
believe this, man.
Even out here
on the casino floor
you gonna find goddamn
mercy pads, Tucks...
I don't know what the fuck
people be doin' here
while they gamblin'.
Man, I ain't peelin' no funky
shit with my human hands.
That ain't nothin' but
a prescription for diseases
and viruses and shit
attackin' your fuckin' insides.
Oh, well, shit,
you gotta do it,
'cause Mr. Gudge
checks everything.
Now, this tunnel
leads back onto the land
for all the people
that work for Mannex.
Mannex Corporation.
They own the Bandit Queen,
three other boats.
Now, this is where they think
on their corporate shit,
Gudge and them.
I mean, the light's
as ugly as all hell,
but, shit, ain't as many Tucks.
Let me in, motherfucker!
What's the password?
Kiss my ass!
(laughing)
Now, this is where
they count the dough.
Now, if you try
to take any of it,
Elron over there'll
shoot yo' ass.
Goddamn!
Dawg, this is a motherfuckin'
pigsty, man!
You are a squeakyass,
motherfuckin' pig!
Man, look at your ass.
You got Cocoa Krispies
on your uniform.
Got breakfast there,
and you still eatin'
goddamn lunch, man.
I swear to God,
if that ass was nickels,
you'd be a motherfuckin'
millionaire.
Spread out, boy. Look at you.
You a disgraceful fucka!
You is a fat motherfucker,
man! I swear...
Hey, Mr. Gudge, uh....
Hey there.
How you doin' this mornin'?
I'm doin' fine.
All right.
So, how's the new man?
Oh, shit, he a cleanin'
motherfucker, man.
Is that a fact?
What's up, my nigga?
Cut! Cut, cut, cut!
Goddamn it, his canteen
fell off. Props!
The goddamn thing's canteen
fell off.
OK. We're prepared for that.
Mountain, put Otto
into the apparatus.
What the hell is this?
World War One
vintage gas mask.
It's authentic.
Strapped on, of course,
so it can't fall off.
Now, the animal is free
to be as active as he wants.
It doesn't inhibit his movement
in any way, and...
I think it really sells
the whole doughboy thing.
It looks like a fucking joke.
Uh, you're absolutely right.
The gas mask
is a whimsical concept.
How the hell does it eat
when it gets to
the Nibbles Ready-to-Eat?
Well, you're absolutely right.
Don't let the clients
see this.
Or that Humane fucker.
No, of course not.
They'll just shut the fucki''
spot down, Pancake.
They'll shut... shut
the fuckin' spot down, OK?
Put the goddamn canteen
back on the dog.
That says he's a soldier!
Dented tin canteen.
All right? Strap it
to his fucking collar!
Easiest thing in the world.
I-I just thought...
What?
...but you're right.
A canteen's much better.
Good concept.
Let's go with that.
What's he doing?
Well, he's, uh...
Just breathe normally, Otto.
The fucking dog
can't breathe.
Oh, no, he can breathe.
Eh, eh, that thing is...
Just breathe normally, Otto.
The fuckin' dog
can't breathe.
cannot breathe!
OK? Get the fu--
Get that fuckin' thing
off of him.
Of course.
Easiest thing in the world.
I don't have my Leatherman.
Mountain, give me your
Leatherman. Chop, chop!
Chitra! Make sure that
Humane fucker doesn't
come over here, OK?
Distract him.
He'll shit if he sees this.
There we go. Mountain, have
electric run me a stinger.
Don't give up on me, Otto!
Mountain, I need two live leads!
Uh, eh, but, Garth the gennie's
a hundred yards away.
Goddamn it. Otto's gonna have
irreversible brain damage
in about 30 seconds.
Here we go. OK, kiss of life.
Otto is fuckin' dead!
What the fuck are you doing?
(quarterback)
Set! 320! 320! Hut!
(grunts)
(heavy breathing)
Ugh!
(crowd cheering)
I-left. 90-tiger, x-slant.
On one. Ready? Break!
Hut!
Ugh! Ooh!
Split left. 68, Z-go.
You the man.
Hey, butthead!
Huh?
You the man!
Me the man?
On one. Ready? Break!
(quarterback) 390! 390! Hut!
(grunts)
(silent)
(crowd cheering)
Ugh!
(cheering louder)
(whistle)
Oh, no!
Hudson! Get your ass
off the field!
Get your ass off the field!
Goddamn it!
Hudson, get your ass out of my
game! You couldn't catch a cold!
(♪ "Another Day, Another Job"
by Nappy Roots)
A'ight, Dragon Lady,
we want that fuckin' money.
We want that doughnut money.
(speaks Asian language)
Oh! OK, papa-san...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
we want that doughnut money.
We ain't fuckin' around,
Mr. Hi-Ho.
Look, this fuckin' thing,
it ain't that complicated.
You give us all the fuckin'
money, you won't get shot
in the head.
A'ight?
You got three seconds.
You... You got three fucking
seconds, a'ight?
One, two, three.
You understand?
We want that doughnut money!
I'm a count uno,
and two and...
His fingers are way
the fuck up my nose!
Get your fingers
out my man's nose!
(shouts in Asian language)
Café?
Ah!
Aah!
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Let it shine on me
♪ Let it shine on
♪ All night, let it
♪ Shine on
♪ Come on, now, let your
♪ Light from the lighthouse
♪ Let it
♪ Shine on me
♪ Oh, let it
♪ Shine on
♪ Come on, let it
♪ I need you to let your
♪ Light from the lighthouse
♪ Let it
♪ Shine on me
♪ Let it shine on me
♪ Shine on
♪ You got to let it
shine on me
♪ Shine on
♪ When you're walki''
in darkness
♪ Shine on
♪ You gotta let it shine
♪ If you want to see the light
You gotta let it shine
♪ You've got to let it shine
Whoo!
♪ Come on, shine, yes!
Come on, shine
♪ Come on, shine
♪ You've got to come on
and let it shine
♪ Yeah, help me let it shine
♪ Let it shine
♪ Shine!
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Hey, let it shine
♪ Shine on
♪ Let it shine
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine...
♪ On...
♪ Me!
♪ Let it shine on me
Yeah! ♪
(applause)
I know you all remember
that when Moses came
down the mountain
carrying the Word of God,
come down that Sinai peak,
he caught them Israelites .
red-handed
(all) Yes!
What he catch 'em doin'?
He caught 'em worshippin'
a golden calf.
(all) Yes!
He caught 'em worshippin'
a false god.
He caught them Israelites
in decline.
In decline!
What did Moses do
when he saw those...
declinin', backslidin',
never-mindin' sinners?
What did he do?
Mosses smote those sinners
in his wrath! Yes, he did!
Y'all know what "smote" is?
I smite, you smite,
he smites, we done smote!
To smite is to go
upside the head!
Because sometimes, brothers and
sisters, that's the only way!
The only way.
To smite is to remind
we got to stop that decline
and scramble back up
to the face
of the Almighty God!
Amen!
Instead of worshippi''
that golden calf,
that earthly trash
on that garbage island.
That garbage island in
the shadowland, wa-a-ay...
Way outside the Kingdom of God!
That garbage island,
where scavenger birds feast
on the bones
of the backslidin' damned!
And so... let us pray.
(crowd quiets)
(♪ Mrs. Munson hums)
(knocking)
My dear lady, I do so hope
this is not an inopportune time
for our first practice.
Somebody die?
I beg your pardon? Oh!
(laughs) No, no, no.
No, I'm not bereaved.
Though it is so kind of you
to inquire.
The hearse is simply
a vehicle commodious enough
to accommodate all the members
of our ensemble.
And, of course, our instruments
contrived in an age
ignorant of miniaturization.
Allow me to introduce
my friends, my colleagues,
these devoted
and passionate musicians.
Ain't no smoki''
in this house.
Oh. Sorry.
(strumming lute)
What do you think, General?
Present any problems?
Good then.
Gentlemen, why don't we crowd
around and go over the plan?
Gentlemen,
this is the Bandit Queen.
Gambling den. Cash cow.
Sodom of the Mississippi Delta
and the focus
of our little exercise.
Here is Orchard Street.
Here is the residence
of Marva Munson,
the charming lady
whom you all met moments ago.
Gentlemen, I'm sure
you're all aware
that the Solons of the state
of Mississippi, to wit,
its legislature,
have decreed that no gaming
establishment shall be erected
within its borders
upon dry land.
They may, however,
legally float.
While the gambling activity is
restricted to these riverboats,
no such restrictions apply
to the functions ancillary
to this cash-besotted business.
The casino's offices,
locker rooms,
facilities to cook and clean,
and, most importantly,
its counting houses,
the reinforced, secret,
super-secure repositories
of the lucre,
may all be situated...
wherever.
Gawain, where is "wherever"?
Say what?
Where's the money?
Oh.
OK, look.
At the end of every shift,
the pit boss brings the cash
down to the hold of the ship
in a locked cashbox,
and once a day all the cash is
moved down to the countin' room.
And where is the counting room?
Uh... it be right there in that
square where you pointin'.
And what, to flog a horse
that if not dead
is at this point in mortal
danger of expiring,
does this little square
represent?
Offices. Underground.
Ha! Underground! Mmm!
Underground.
During the casino's
hours of operation,
the door to this counting room
is fiercely guarded.
The door itself is of
redoubtable Pittsburgh steel.
When the casino closes,
this entire underground complex
is locked up,
and the armed guard retreats
to the casino's main entrance.
There, then far from the guard,
reposes the money
behind a five-inch-thick
steel portal, yes.
But the walls...
the walls are but humble masonry
behind which is only
the soft, loamy soil
deposited over centuries
by the Old Man,
the meanderin' Mississippi,
as it fanned its way
back and forth across the great
alluvial plain, leaving earth.
This earth.
The General here,
whose curriculum vitae
comprehends massive
tunnelin' experience
through the soil of his native
French Indochina,
shall be directin' our little
old tunnelin' operation.
Garth Pancake,
though a master of none,
is a jack of all those trades
corollary to our aim.
He will be doin' such
fabricatin' and demolition work
as our little caper
shall require.
Happy to be on board.
Gawain is our proverbial
"inside man."
He has managed to secure
himself a berth
on the custodial staff
of the Bandit Queen.
Damn skippy!
And this brings us to Lump.
To look at Lump,
you might wonder
what specialized expertise
could he possibly offer
our merry little
old band of miscreants.
Well, gentlemen,
in a project of such risks,
it is imperative to enlist
the services of a hooligan,
a goon, an ape,
a physical brute.
Someone who will
be our security,
our battering ram,
our blunt instrument.
And, on our behalf, I wish him
a warm Mississippi welcome.
Fuckin' A.
Whassup, my nigga?
Well, gentlemen, here you are.
Men of different backgrounds
and differing talents.
Men with, in fact,
but two things in common:
One, you all saw fit
to answer my advertisement
in the Memphis Scimitar;
and two, you're all going
to be, in consequence,
very, very, incredibly... rich.
Let us revel in our adventure,
gentlemen.
Let us make beautiful...
(laughs) ...music together,
and, by all means,
let us keep this to ourselves.
What we say in this root cellar,
let it stay in this root cellar.
There's no "I" in "team."
(♪ "Trouble of This Word")
(♪ "Trouble In, Trouble Out"
by Nappy Roots)
♪ Trouble in and trouble out
♪ Trouble's what
this world's about
♪ Troubles of this world
the Devil's in this world
♪ Trouble in, trouble out
♪ Trouble's what
this world's about
♪ Troubles of this world
the Devil's in this world
♪ You up the river
without a paddle
♪ In a lot of trouble
♪ Without a doubt you going
under running out of bubbles
♪ Pass me the body bag
♪ Watch me dump 'em
♪ It ain't nothing for you
to get squashed like a pumpkin
♪ I try so hard
and play my cards
♪ Afraid to fall,
I ain't involved
♪ I gotta call
I'm much appalled
♪ I came to OZ
and broke the laws
♪ Bring on the casket
ain't too glad
♪ 'Cause dirty hazard
wrapped in plastic
(♪ continues rapping)
(♪ "Trouble of this World")
(knocking)
(whistles)
It's OK. Don't stop
on account of me.
No. No, no, no, no.
Not at all, madam.
Not at all. We were about
to take a break anyway.
The glissandi
on this particular piece
are technically very,
very demanding,
and I'm sure we would all
welcome a moment of R and R.
Well, I just thought maybe
you'd like to see...
What have you gotten into,
honey? Why you sweatin'
like that?
Uh... Uh...
Uh, eh, 'cause, 'cause...
That boy right there?
He plays one bitch barrel
full of a sackbut!
Ain't that right, Lump?
Uh-huh.
I'm tellin' you, he can
tear it up. Right, Lump?
Ain't nobody play the sackbut
like Lump right there. He...
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Don't be shy, Lump.
Don't be shy.
Lump, that boy,
he go at it like
it was some pussy!
Oh, shit!
Mind your mouth!
This is a Christian house, boy.
No hippity-hop language in here.
Sometime it's the only way.
Now listen,
you ain't gonna hit me...
I'm tryin' to help you, boy,
better yourself!
And so you should, madam.
So you should.
Gawain is so far transported
by his love of the music
of the early Renaissance...
Don't make me no never-mind,
he transported!
I understand.
You been smokin'?
Oh, certainly not, ma'am.
I understand your indignation,
ma'am.
And I was offering explanation,
not an excuse.
I myself am...
(Gawain) Hey, hey, hey...
...don't be
explainin' me, dawg!
You can't read
my motherfuckin' mind, man!
You might got yo' Ph.D.,
but I got my G.E.D.!
Yes.
Nigga!
A fiery lad...
but then youth is fiery.
A fact often remarked upon by
the poets of the Romantic era.
My youth, I was in church.
I wasn't walkin' around fiery.
Youth ain't no excuse
for nothin'.
Anyhow, I just came
to show you the fife.
Othar's fife. Burned his own.
I thought maybe, you bein' a man
of music, you'd be interested.
Oh, indeed I am.
Cut it hisself
and burned his holes.
The Israelites called it
a khalil.
Yeah, you can read
all about it in the Bible.
Ain't nothin' new under the sun.
Indeed not.
Gone these 20 years.
He was some kind of man.
(sighs) Blowed the khalil.
I don't suppose Othar
ever turned his hand
or... or turned his lip
to blowing the shofar?
The ceremonial ram's horn
sounded by the priests
of the Hebrews.
No, I don't know nothin'
about that.
Othar never blowed no shofar!
Of course not.
Not to the extent
of my knowledge.
The khalil was good enough
for my Othar.
He was some kind of man.
Some kind of man.
Mm, goddamn! Come on, girl,
let me get one little peek.
Don't be cruel.
Come on, just one butt cheek.
Pull that ass out
and make it clap.
Ah, just 'cause I'm dressed
like a janitor,
that don't mean you
gotta do me dirty.
This muthafucka's hit the
jackpot. Come on, girl.
Come over here and
blow on these dice.
You know, I'm a seven
on the roll now,
but I'm a 10 the hard way,
and I ain't just talkin' crap.
Mr. Gudge, she had a ass
that could pull a bus.
I mean, Gudge, it was more
than an ass, it was literature.
Yeah, I don't care how big her
ass was, MacSam. You're fired.
You say what?
There is no fraternizing
with customers
on the Bandit Queen.
Clean out your locker.
But, Mr. Gudge,
I wasn't fraterniz--
I said get outta here.
You're fired.
You can't fire me!
I'll sue your ass!
Sue me? For what?
For fuckin'
punitive damages, man!
Punitive damages.
Yeah.
You goddamn skippy!
(laughs) Punitive damages.
I see why you firin' me,
Mr. Gudge.
It's simple and plain.
You firin' me 'cause I'm black.
MacSam, everybody on the
custodial staff is black.
Your replacement
is gonna be black.
His replacement, no doubt,
will be black!
Well, the fuckin' judge is
goin' be black, muthafucka.
Oh.
And you?
You gon' stand tall
before the man.
Oh.
And your replacement's
gonna be black,
muthafucka!
Thank you.
Oh, my.
Oh, my, my, my,
my, my, my, my.
This is a severe setback.
I am distraught.
I'm more than distraught.
I am devastated.
I-I'm beside myself.
I'm at a positive loss
for words.
You still talkin' OK,
though.
Have you all decided?
Madam, we must have waffles.
We must all have
waffles forthwith.
We must all think.
We must all have waffles
and think,
each and every one of us,
to the very best of his ability.
Perhaps if you apologized
to the man and gave him flowers.
Or perhaps a fruit basket
with a card
depicting a misty seascape
and inscribed with a sentiment.
I ain't apologizin'
to that muthafucka.
He fired me 'cause I'm black!
He can't do that.
You could sue him.
Open and shut case.
Fuckin' A.
Surely a chocolate
assortment has been known
to melt the heart of even
the hardest misanthrope.
That man ain't rollin' over
for no fucking candy bar.
Uh, we've had
a bit of a setback
on the tunneling front, too.
We've run into
a pretty large rock.
Rock!
Very bad. Very bad.
Oh, my.
Seems that the poet was right.
Troubles never singly come.
Oh, no, we can get through
the rock. No worries there.
Easiest thing in the world.
Why, we just blow right
through it.
I got a pyro license.
Just, uh, bore a hole
in the rock
and pack in a little plastique
and Igneous blows pretty good.
And then we could--
Hello, Garth.
Am I ordering
the primer cord?
Yes, Mountain.
We were just talking about that,
and some plastique.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, this is Mountain Girl.
Mountain is my right hand.
She helps me out with ordnance.
Helps me with...
damn near everything.
Hey.
You brought yo' bitch
to the Waffle Hut?
(Dorr clears throat)
I-I must confess myself
to be puzzled as well.
I thought it was understood
that when it came
to our little enterprise,
"mum" was the word.
Of course, I understand that,
but this is Mountain Girl.
I don't keep secrets
from Mountain.
That's not how you maintain
a loving, caring relationship.
You brought yo' bitch
to the Waffle Hut!
The man brought his bitch...
All right, look, you,
I will thank you to stop
referring to Mountain that way.
She is the other half
of my life.
You know, everybody lookin' at
me like I'm some kind of fuck-up
for losin' a sorry-ass job,
and this muthafucka
brings his bitch
to the muthafuckin'
Waffle Hut!
Son of a bitch punk!
Shut your goddamn mouth!
You better raise
the fuck up, fucka!
Gentlemen, please.
Back the fuck up!
You gon' back that shit
the fuck up!
Gentlemen, please.
What? What?
Please, gentlemen,
this behavior does you
no credit in the eyes
of your colleagues,
nor in those of
the other patrons
(lowers voice)
of this Waffle Hut.
Little punk.
Oh, look at this.
I got blueberry syrup
on my safari jacket!
Gentlemen, I propose that
we consider the matter
of this woman,
Mountain Water...
Mountain Girl.
I'm so very sorry.
I propose that we consider
this matter closed.
And we shall choose to trust her
since we have no choice,
and since she shall share
only in Mr. Pancake's portion
of the booty.
Of course.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
Yeah, you damn right
you won't.
Up yours, punk.
Oh, fuck you
and the Swiss Miss.
The matter of disposing
of our igneous impediment
is also...
C-Coach... Coach...
C-C-Coach, I...
...closed. Settled.
That leaves us only
with the question of
Gawain retrieving his job.
Coach, I...
Yes, Lump?
Couldn't we just
bribe the guy?
(♪ "Any Day Now"
by The Soul Stirrers)
(chuckles)
You are a readin' fool,
aren't you, Mr. Dorr?
Yes, I must confess.
I often find myself more at home
in these ancient volumes
than I do in the hustle-bustle
of the modern world.
To me, paradoxically,
the literature of
the so-called "dead tongues"
holds more currency
than this morning's newspaper.
In these books,
in these volumes,
there is the accumulated
wisdom of mankind,
which succors me
when the day is hard
and the night lonely and long.
Mm. The wisdom of mankind, huh?
What about the wisdom
of the Lord?
Oh, yes, yes.
The Good Book, mm.
I have found reward
in its pages,
but to me, there are other
good books as well.
Heavy volumes of antiquity
freighted with the insights
of man's glorious age.
And then, of course,
I just love, love, love
the works of
Mr. Edgar Allan Poe.
Oh, I know who he was.
Kinda spooky.
No, madam, no, no.
Not of this world, it's true.
He... he lived in a dream.
An ancient dream.
"Helen...
"Thy beauty is to me
"Like those Nicean barks
of yore,
"That gently,
o'er a perfumed sea,
"The weary,
wayworn wanderer bore
To his own native shore."
Who was Helen?
Some kinda whore of Babylon?
One doesn't know
who Helen was...
but I picture her
as being very, very...
extremely...
...pale.
Mrs. Munson, I have been trying
to figure out some way of
expressin' my gratitude to you
for takin' in this weary,
wayworn wanderer.
It's just a little old present.
Why, it's hardly
anything at all.
Oh, why, Mr. Dorr!
You are a gallant man.
Oh, madam, I blush, I melt.
No...
I just happened to hear of this
gospel concert tomorrow night,
"The Mighty, Mighty Clouds
of Joy",
and I thought you and a friend
from church perhaps would...?
Yes, I have
a widow ladyfriend.
The concert is up in Memphis,
so I have arranged a car service
to transport you thither.
(knocking)
Ah?
Why, Sheriff Wyner!
How you doin'?
Good evenin', Mrs. Munson.
I just stopped by here
to let you know I did have
a talk with Weemack,
and he told me he's gonna
comply with your request
in keepin' that music down
and neighborly.
So you just go and have yourself
a pleasant evenin'.
Wait a minute. I got somebody
that I want you to meet.
Uh, ma'am, you know what? I'm...
I'm a little pressed for time.
You got a gang of bank robbers
youse chasin'?
Come on in here and say hello.
Yeah, we was in here,
havin' tea and...
Huh!
Bussed his own dishes.
You can always tell a gentleman.
Somebody was in here, ma'am?
Yeah, with me and Othar.
Well, you know what?
Maybe I'll catch him
the next time.
Oh, come on up to his room
with me and say hello.
I got a family.
My wife got dinner
on the table.
I really have to be goin'.
Oh, my. He is neat!
Yes, ma'am, he very neat.
He probably went down
to the cellar to play
with his friends.
Ma'am, I really got
to be goin' now.
What...?
Ma'am, I really need
to be gettin' back.
Mrs. Munson, don't...
You don't have to...
Mrs. Munson?
(laughing) Why, Professor!
What in the world are you
doin' havin' tea down there?
Uh... Mrs. Munson?
(Munson laughing)
Oh, Lord Jesus.
continues laughing)
Mrs. Munson?
Land of Goshen, child!
Come on out from under there!
Mrs. Munson,
my pager just went off.
I got to go. Mm-hmm.
I'll meet you
and your friend later.
(footsteps descending)
That was refreshing.
(Sheriff) Y'all have
a good evenin' now!
As you know, we academics
are inordinately fond of
wedgin' ourselves
into confined spaces.
Mm!
At Yale, the students will
see how many of their number
they can enclose
in a telephone booth.
At Harvard, a broom closet.
Oh! Hope I didn't spill my tea.
Well, what the hell is this?
I guess it's just
my way of sayin', um...
Oh, well, goddamn it,
Mr. Gudge. Look here, I...
I don't know what it's like
walkin' in your shoes...
you know, with you bein'
a tight-ass and all.
And... I-I-I'm pretty sure
you don't know
what it's like
walkin' in my shoes.
See, Mr. Gudge, there's
the custodian, right?
And then there's the man
inside the custodian.
And that's the motherfucker
we got a problem with.
See, 'cause that man,
he got needs, Mr. Gudge,
and normally those needs gotta
do with women with big asses.
I guess my point bein' is, uh...
I realize I'm a bunkie junkie.
Mm-hmm.
If you woulda seen
the kettle drums
on this girl, Mr. Gudge, whew!
Well... we all human.
This apology buys you
a one-week probationary period.
Thank you, Mr. Gudge.
Stay away from
the customers, MacSam.
Uh. This drill bit's
getting awfully hot.
Gawain, maybe you could
fill a Hudson sprayer
and spritz it down
while I drill.
Fuck you. I ain't your
motherfuckin' house nigger.
I'm the inside man.
All right, look, are you
gonna have a bug up your ass
for the rest of the time
we work together?
I'll get the sprayer.
Oh, no, no. No.
Me and this gentleman here
have to get square.
Let me tell you somethin',
MacSam.
I'm gonna tell you about how
I came down to Mississippi.
I wasn't born here, you know.
I'm from Scranton, Pennsylvania.
(stomach growls)
What the fuck?
Scranton. Pennsylvania.
Came down here in 1964.
Greyhound bus.
With the Freedom Riders.
Do you know who the Freedom
Riders were, MacSam?
No, and I don't give a fuck.
Just tell me when the fuck
they gonna leave. Damn!
The Freedom Riders,
my fine young man,
were a group of concerned
liberals from up north,
all working together,
just like we are here.
Involved citizens
who came down here
so that local black folk
could have their civil
liberties.
So that people like you
could have the vote.
You know what, man?
What, brother?
I don't vote. So fuck you.
You little fuckin' ingrate.
And the bus you rode in
on, jackass!
Let's step outside, MacSam!
Fuck the outside!
Come on! What?
(knocking)
My friend Mrs. Funthes is here,
so I'm about to go out.
Just thought I'd leave y'all
with some cinnamon cookies.
Why, that is lovely.
Ooh, y'all sound good!
(chuckles) Maybe you could come
by the church one Sunday...
...give us a recital.
Why, how kind of you.
Our music, however, is, uh...
well, how shall I put this?
Uh, a bit Roman
in its out-look.
Uh, many of our pieces were
commissioned by the Holy See.
Oh, I see, all right,
but we don't make no big
whoop-dee-do about denomination.
Everybody welcome at our church.
Yeah, we had a Methodist
come in.
Episcopalian. Back in the 60s,
we had a Jew come in!
(Dorr chuckles)
Yeah, he had a guitar.
(chucking)
A Jew with a guitar.
If you will excuse me,
eh, one moment, madam,
I shall, uh,
I shall see you out.
If you gentlemen can
labor harmoniously
in the course of my absence,
perhaps upon my return
we shall be prepared to explode
that vexin' old piece
of igneous.
Oh, Professor!
This is Mrs. Funthes.
Enchanté, Mrs. Funthes.
Allow me.
Rosalie, this is Professor
G.H. Dorr, Ph.D.
Oh, my. That's an awful
lot of letters.
Oh, well, no.
Of course, in my youth,
I was known simply
as Goldthwait.
Uh-huh.
All right, safety meeting.
Let's listen up. General, can
you hand me the primer cord?
Before we set the charge, we
will run through our procedure.
I have earplugs
for whoever wants them.
Just wedge those
right in your ears.
Now, here we have...
Not yet, Lump.
Oh.
Now, primer cord.
Gelatinite. C-4.
Time comes, we pack the hole
in the rock with the C-four
and insert two leads:
A and B.
I remember my father
sayin' to me...
And it's one of the few memories
I retain of the man
from one of his visits home,
and how I do cherish it.
He said to me, "Goldthwait,
you are not formed
as other boys."
He a man of learnin'?
This is the same procedure
we will be using
when we collapse the tunnel
after entering the casino vault
and returning
to the root cellar.
Uh, he was a self-educated man.
Didn't have a career as such,
but the government did recognize
the breadth of his readin'
by makin' him librarian of
the state nervous hospital
in Meridian, where he was
a distinguished inmate.
Once these materials
are combined
only the professionals
may handle them.
That means me
or the General.
Mm.
Separately they are harmless.
Completely inert.
Why, you could light this stuff
on fire, hit it with a ham...
(explosion)
(car alarms/dogs bark)
What in the name of
heavens was that?
Well, um... I'm quite certain
there's absolutely
no reason to be alarmed.
Why, I-I'm not even
absolutely certain
I-I-I-I heard anything at all.
Didn't hear nothin'?
Well, something perhaps.
Nothing that need discompose us
was the sense
I was tryin' to convey.
Now, Mrs. Munson,
I will not have you missin'
your musical recital.
Off you go!
I shall call the gas company,
or the water company.
Whatever subterranean utility
is implicated in this,
uh, contretemps.
I shall see to the matter,
as only a highly educated
classicist could.
You stupid fuckin' jackass!
Blood! Blood!
Blood, Professor!
Give a signal
for somethin' like this!
(Pancake) It's nothin'
to make a fuss about.
It's perfectly all right.
Jackass! You better get
yo' ass back down there
and find that shit,
dipshit!
Really, I'm perfectly
all right.
Perfectly all right?
Jackass. you just blew
your goddamn finger off!
The muthafucka down there
flappin' the fuck around!
You better get yo' ass
back down there and find it!
I'm a tell you right now,
nubbie, I ain't pickin' up
your goddamn finger!
I gather there was
a premature detonation.
Would you tell this muthafucka
he can sew this shit back on?
It's like that dude
whose wife cut his dick off,
threw it on the freeway?
She just called Triple A,
they towed the dick and sewed
the muthafucka back on!
Listen up! Jackass,
I saw the muthafucka
in a porno!
The thang still worked!
It looked like a chewed-up
frank,
but that little muthafucka
be workin' that muthafucka!
It's mangly, but he be fucki''
the bitch all kind of ways
with a twisted dick!
Oh! Your fuckin' finger
just moved! The muthafucka
movin' slow now!
I'm not gettin' that shit.
Fuck that!
Fuck all y'all.
You're on your own there!
They usin' the house
to practice music...
of the Rococo.
Mm-hmm.
(Gawain) You ain't
gon' catch his ass.
I propose we get
our fallen comrade
to the hospital.
The General will follow
when he manages to recover
the severed digit.
No, no, really,
I'm perfectly all right.
I don't know what
all the fuss is about.
Good news! Good news!
Pickles! Go get him!
The house is
in apple-pie order,
though we do have to get medical
attention for Mr. Panacke,
who, durin' the disturbance,
pinched his finger
in the valve of his sackbut.
You let the cat out!
Wha--?
The General is even now
exercisin' every effort
in retrievin'...
your mischievous little Pickles.
Please, go on.
Go on and enjoy the concert!
Driver! Au revoir, Mesdames.
(Dorr) Despite our setback,
we find ourselves on schedule
to penetrate the vault here
this afternoon
while Mrs. Munson is at church
havin' blasted that
little old rock to pieces
durin' Mrs. Munson's
choir practice.
Garth, can you run us
through the game plan
for what remains
of our tunnel?
Of course.
Why, it's child's play now.
The easiest thing in the world.
Only a couple of feet
separate us from the vault.
Just the usual spade work
until we get to the masonry
of the vault,
and then we just drill through.
And will you be able
to wield the drill
with your maimed extremity?
Oh, well, yeah,
I should think so.
Yeah, it's, uh...
it's only one finger.
Inhibits me in doing
finer work, of course.
I'll always have
to live with that.
(clears throat)
Maybe, uh... I'm just
thinkin' out loud here.
Maybe, since as you say,
there will be problems later,
maybe, uh... I actually
mentioned this
to Mountain Girl,
she agrees with me, so it's
not just one person's opinion.
Maybe, uh...
I should get a little extra
compensation for the accident.
Somewhat larger share.
Why, if this was any other
line of work, I'd be
getting workman's comp.
Wouldn't I? Might even have
a pretty good lawsuit.
Wait, so you gonna sue yourself
for blowing your own
goddamn finger off?
Well, now that
is simply asinine.
Yes, but you see, Garth,
this is not
what you just called
"some other line of work."
Yeah, no, no, no,
but if it were...
This is a criminal enterprise,
not to put too fine
a point on it,
entailing any manner of risk
not involved in honest labor.
Governmental regulations
and civic safeguards
cannot be assumed
to apply to antisocial pursuits.
Yeah, but he lost his finger.
We don't give a fuck!
That fool could blow
his goddamn dick off,
it don't make no nevermind
to us!
We not payin' this jackass
for goin' around,
blowin' off goddamn body parts!
Get yo' fuckin' head
out yo' ass, man!
Look you,
there is no call for...
No extra share!
OK. Majority rules.
Like I say, it was
just a trial balloon.
Hand's not so bad, really.
I even get some phantom feeling.
Yeah, you pull on your prick,
you get some phantom feelin'.
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Fuck you, nubbie!
Well, now that
that matter is settled,
why don't we synchronize
our watches before Gawain
reports to work.
In 20 seconds,
it will be exactly 12:16.
Fifteen...
What, it'll be 12:15?
No, 15 seconds.
Well, 11 seconds now.
It'll be 12:16.
Eight, seven...
Professor? Prof...?
...six...
Professor?
...five... Yes, Lump!
I don't have a watch.
♪ There'll be no more
weepin' and wailin'
♪ No more weepin' and wailin'
♪ No more weapin' and wailin'
♪ Home to live with God
Oh...
♪ Soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ Trouble of this world
Trouble of this world
♪ Oh, soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ I'm goin' home
to live with God
♪ Soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ Trouble of this world
Trouble of this world
♪ Soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ I'm goin' home
to live with God
♪ Well, soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ Trouble of this world
Trouble of this, great God!
♪ Soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ I'm goin' home
to live with God
♪ Well, I'm goin' up
to see King Jesus
♪ I'm gonna shake Him
by His hand
♪ I'm gonna tell Him
all about my trouble
♪ As I'm travelin'
through this land
♪ Oh, soon I will be done
♪ Trouble of this world
♪ Yeah, soon I will be done
♪ I'm goin' home
to live with God
♪ Yeah, soon I will be done
with the trouble of this world
♪ Trouble of this world
♪ Yeah, soon I will be done
with the trouble, yeah
♪ I'm goin' home
to live with God ♪
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Ain't that somethin'!
(moans)
I.B.S.
You be what?
Irritable Bowel Syndrome!
Is there a men's room down here?
Oh, come on. You shouldn't
be usin' the men's room now!
Or a lady's room. (sniffs)
Quickly. (sniffs) I.B.S.
Man, if you knew you had
the runs, why didn't you
shit back at the house?
Quickly!
We don't want Elron
finding your stinkin' ass
on the crapper!
No choice.
It's a medical condition.
Quickly!
You one disgustin' individual,
you know that?
Come on. Follow me.
toilet flushes)
(sighs)
I feel 30 pounds lighter.
Come the fuck on
with your stinkass.
Thank you for being
so understanding.
Not everyone is, of course,
which is why the biggest
challenge of I.B.S.
is educating the public.
Afflicts over two million
people,
yet most of us have
never heard of it.
And it strikes without regard
to age, gender or race.
Oh, fuck, man, I don't want
to hear about this shit.
Well, that's exactly the kind
of attitude we're fighting.
I guess I never told you that's
how Mountain Girl and I met.
They had an I.B.S. weekend
at Grossinger's
up in the Catskills.
Of course, the tourist business
there has suffered
with the demise
of the Borscht Belt,
so they have various
promotions, mixers, so on.
This was a weekend
for Irritable Bowel singles
to meet and support
each other and
share stories.
Man, look it here.
I don't wanna hear a single
one of them stories, OK?
Now, some of them
are very moving.
Not one fucking story!
Look, I didn't choose
to have I.B.S.
Man, shut the fuck up!
There's no cure, you know.
Only control.
Lifelong condition.
Yeah, you know what?
Bein' an asshole's
a lifelong condition, too.
Just drop the fuckin' tools.
I'm not complaining.
I did meet Mountain Girl.
Man, get back
in the fuckin' hole!
Oh! (laughs)
Marvelous. Marv--
This way!
This way, gentlemen! Oh!
Excellent! Excellent.
Flawless, flawless. Thumbs up.
Can't stop shittin'.
Can't stop talkin'
about shittin'.
Gentlemen, to we few...
We who have shared
each other's company,
each other's cares,
each other's joys,
and who shall now reap the
fruits of our communal efforts,
shoulder to shoulder, from each
according to his abilities,
so forth and whatnot.
We have had our little
differences along the way,
but, uh, I'd like to think
that they've only made us
value one another all the more.
Each of us coming
to understand and appreciate
the other's unique qualities
and potencies
and, yes... foibles.
I suggest that we shall look
back upon this little caper
one day,
one distant day...
eh, grandchildren
dandled upon our knee...
and perhaps a tear will form
and we shall say,
"Well, with wit and grit
and no small amount of courage,
we accomplished something
on that day,
a feat of derringdo,
an enterprise not ignoble."
We merry band, unbound by
the constraints of society
and the prejudices
of the common ruck.
We happy few.
Gentlemen, to us!
(all) To us!
(laughter)
Charge shoulda
gone off already.
I do beg your pardon?
The charge to collapse
the tunnel. I set it
for eight minutes.
Well, that much time and more
has certainly elapsed.
I need not remind you, it is
of the essence of this plan
that the money should appear
to have simply vanished
without a trace,
spirited away, as it were,
by ghosts.
Of course.
The conundrum of the undisturbed
yet empty vault.
The unsolvable riddle
of the sealed,
yet violated sanctum
is of the utmost importance,
not only to make our caper more
intellectually satisfying,
it is exigent as a matter
of practical fact.
I remind you that
if any tunnel is ever found
leading to this house,
the owner knows all your names.
(stomach rumbling)
(grunts)
(♪ "Trouble of this World")
(beeping)
(♪ "Trouble of This World")
(rumbling)
You just fart?
(laughing)
Nope, nope, I'm fine.
Perfectly all right!
Not a problem!
There's no hole left.
Professor!
I'm surprised!
Well... uh...
properly speaking, madam,
we are surprised.
You are taken aback.
Though I do acknowledge
that the sense that you intend
is gaining increasing currency
through its use, yes.
You have returned from
your devotions betimes.
I had to make tea.
I want to talk to you,
Professor, so don't
you be leavin'!
And you!
I told you I don't want
any smokin' in this house!
(doorbell rings)
(sighs)
Oh, come on in!
How you doin'?
(chattering)
Tea, ladies.
Now, I don't know what
you boys been up to
but I know mischief
when I see it.
Now, I want an explanation,
but first, I want you
to get your fannies up here with
all y'all's period instruments.
Now, I been tellin'
the ladies about your music
and they want to hear you play.
Professor?
Yes, Lump?
I can't really play
the buttsack.
(chattering stops)
Madam, or rather, mesdames,
you must accept our apologies
for not bein' able to perform,
for, as you see,
we are shorthanded.
Gawain is still at work,
and we could no more play
with one part tacit
than a horse could canter
shy one leg.
Perhaps I could offer
as a poor but ready substitute,
a brief poetic recital.
Though I do not pretend to
any great oratorical skills,
I would be happy to present,
with your ladies' permission,
verse from the unquiet mind
of Mr. Edgar Allan Poe.
"Ladies, thy beauty is to me
"Like those Nicean barks
of yore,
"That gently,
o'er a perfumed sea,
"The weary,
wayworn wanderer bore
"To his own native shore."
(ladies sigh)
My, my, my.
"On desperate seas
long wont to roam,
"Thy hyacinth hair,
thy classic face,
"Thy Naiad airs
have brought me home
"To the glory that was Greece,
And the grandeur that was Rome."
(tea lady #1)
Glory hallelujah.
(all) Amen!
Hm?
(Dorr) Bye-bye, ladies.
It was... it was my pleasure.
(tea lady #1) We have
to do this again.
(tea lady #2)
Yes, we do got to.
Such a pleasure.
Safe home. Safe home.
(Mrs. Munson chuckles)
Now I want to know
what's goin' on.
Oh, indeed, indeed.
The thirst for knowledge
is a very commendable thing.
Though I do believe
when you hear the explanation
you shall laugh riotously,
slappin' your knee
and perhaps even wipin'
away a giddy tear,
relieved of your former concern.
Lump here is an avid collector
of Indian arrowheads,
and having found one simply
lying on your cellar floor
- a particularly rare artifact
of the Natchez tribe? -
Nats... what?
He enlisted the entire ensemble
in an all-out effort
to sift through the subsoil
in search of others.
And apparently, in doing so,
we hit a mother lode
of natural gas.
I myself became acutely aware
of the smell of "rotten eggs."
And it was just at
this inopportune moment
that the General here violated
the cardinal rule of this house
and lit himself a cigarette.
So sorry.
Well, what about
all that money?
Ah.
The money.
Well, the money
is Mr. Pancake's.
(clears throat) That's right.
Who only just remortgaged
his home
in order to raise the money
for a surgical procedure
that will correct the wandering
eye of his common-law wife,
Mountain Water, who suffers
from astigmia and strabismus
and a general curdling
of the... vitreous jelly.
Mr. Pancake is an ardent foe
of the Federal Reserve,
and is, in fact, one of those
eccentrics one often reads about
hoardin' his entire life savings
in Mr. Pancake's case,
in a Hefty bag that is
his constant companion.
The Steel Sak.
Don't trust the banks.
Never have.
Mm-mn.
It don't smell right to me.
I'm callin' Sheriff Wyner.
No! Madam!
Please, please. Madam!
No, no, I beg of...
Yes! Yes!
It is a lie!
It is a fantastic tale!
You have us dead to rights,
but, madam, please, please,
please
allow me to tell you
the truth... in private.
Madam...
Madam, we are not musicians
of the late Renaissance.
Nor of the early,
nor mid period.
Mm-hmm.
We are, in fact... criminals.
Desperate men, Mrs. Munson.
We have... tunneled
into the nearby offices
of the Bandit Queen
gambling emporium
and relieved it
of its treasure.
Lord have mercy.
It is true.
the Bandit Queen
is a den of iniquity,
a painted harlot
luring people into sin
by exciting the vice of greed
with her promise
of easy winnings.
Oh, yes.
Her gains are ill-gotten,
but, I offer no excuses...
save one.
We men have each pledged one
half of our share of the booty
to a charitable institution.
In compensation
for the use of your home,
we had planned
to donate a full share
to Bob Jones University.
Without burdening you
with guilty knowledge
by informing you of same.
But now you have wrested
the information from me.
There you have it.
It is on your table,
Mrs. Munson.
The "awful truth."
Stolen money.
But find the victim,
Mrs. Munson.
I challenge you.
Even the casino itself,
that riparian Gomorrah,
shall suffer no harm.
It has an insurance company.
A financial behemoth that
will cheerfully replenish
its depleted vaults.
That is its function.
And that insurance company
has tens and tens
of thousands
of policy holders.
So that... We have done
the calculations, Mrs. Munson.
So that at the end of the day,
at the final reckoning,
each and every one of
those policy holders
shall have contributed
one penny.
One, single solitary cent...
to the satisfaction
of this claim.
One penny?
One penny.
Think of it, Mrs. Munson.
One penny from those thousands
upon thousands of people
so that Bob Jones University
can continue on its mission.
Why, I have no doubt that,
were those policy holders
made aware of the existence
of that august institution,
each and every one of them
would have volunteered
some token amount for the
furtherance of its aims.
Well, that's prob'ly true.
Sadly, the criminal stain
is upon my soul,
but the benefit shall accrue
to any number of worthy causes
as long, that is,
as the secret stays with us.
Well...
I can't hardly see
the harm in it.
One penny?
(mouthing) One penny.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me?
No, I'm sorry, it's wrong,
and don't you be leadin' me
into temptation.
No, no, madam,
I must strenuously--
I'm sorry,
it's just plain wrong.
Stealin'!
No, madam...
I know your intentions
was good.
No, they weren't!
And I won't call the police
if you give back the money
and y'all go to church
with me next Sunday.
And engage in divine worship?
I've made up my mind.
Now, you can doubletalk
all you want.
It's church or the county jail.
Think it over.
I gotta feed the cat.
(plucks strings)
Motherfuck!
Yes.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Munson
has rather complicated
the situation.
Yeah, well, I know how
to de-complicate it.
You bust a cap
in that old bitch's head,
everything be simple.
Not easy to do.
Many reasons.
Practical ones:
Quiet neighborhood, sleepy town.
Reasons of moral repugnance:
A harmless woman,
a deed conceived
and executed in cold blood.
Oh, no, Gawain, would that
it were simple.
Well, fuck, man!
What we gonna do?
Give the money back
and go to church?
I shudder. I quake.
You, sir, are a Buddhist.
Is there not a "middle" way?
Mm.
Must float like a leaf
on the river of life...
and kill old lady.
Yes, yes, I suppose
you are right.
It is the active nature of the
crime, though, that so abhors.
The squeezing of the trigger,
the plunging of the knife.
But... let us think a moment.
What other tools
do we have at hand?
We have the cellar.
We have the cavity.
We have masonry and trowel.
Perhaps we could simply...
immure her.
Sure. Easiest thing
in the world.
I can whip up a little mortar
in a snow saucer.
Lay the bricks.
Anchor in some chains.
Mountain Girl could
outsource the manacles.
Ah, gentlemen, gentlemen,
we delude ourselves.
No, eh, shortest and painless
is best.
Gawain's gun, retort muffled
by a pillow, into the brain.
(claps)
The affair of an instant.
The only question is:
who wields the weapon?
I believe it is traditional
in such circumstances
to draw straws.
Fair enough.
Here you go, Lump.
I'm thinkin', though, that,
uh, since I lost a finger
- and I mean literally lost it,
'cause of that fuckin' cat -
maybe I should be excused
from this thing.
Hard for me to squeeze
a trigger anyway.
You one whiny muthafucka.
I'll come over there
and squeeze
your fuckin' nutsack,
you keep that bullshit up.
Shut up, punk!
I'll kick your goddamn ass,
sweet-legs!
Gentlemen, gentlemen!
No special pleading.
No exceptions.
It is of the nature
of the situation we would
all prefer to be excused.
Well, OK, it was
just a trial balloon.
Long straw. You all see it.
All that fuss for nothin', punk.
Fuck you.
Motherfuck!
♪ Lord, I'm troubled
Oh, Lord, by my soul
♪ My Lord, but when I
get up in Kingdom, Lord
♪ I won't be troubled no more
♪ Oh, Lord, I'm troubled
♪ Lord, I'm troubled
♪ Lord, I'm troubled...
(over TV) Make yourself
comfortable while I bring
out the coffee.
Oh, would you like
a hot cross bun?
No, just an explanation.
Coming up!
Ouisie, I'll take some cocoa.
Hi, George.
What's goin' on?
George!
How did they get in here?
(raucous laughter)
What you got there, Gawain?
Why, nothin', Mama.
Nothin', my ass!
You got a dog there!
No, Mama.
A filthy, noisy
little pest
of a puppy dog goin' shit
all over the house!
He won't shit in the house,
Mama. I'm gonna train him.
I promise.
I'll train him real good!
I'm gonna train you real good!
You wait till your daddy
get home.
He gonna lay into you proper!
(sobbing) No, Mama!
Please, Mama! I love you!
Your daddy goin' kick yo' ass!
Mama's whuppin' Gawain's ass!
Ain't you gonna
use the strap, Mama?
I love you, Mama.
I'm sorry, Mama, I love you.
Yeah, I'll wipe the dog's ass
and everything, Mama.
I'll train him to shit
in the toilet, Mama.
I'll wipe his ass
and everything, Mama.
What you doin'?
What you doin' with my pillow?
Nothin', ma'am.
I just came down to get a--
Ugh!
I'm displeased with you!
Yeah, but...
Fine colored boy like you,
fallin' in with that trash
downstairs!
Ugh!
Now, I know your mama
taught you better than that!
I can't do it.
She remind me of my mama.
Look, man...
Why, this is most irregular.
...y'all muthafuckas just
gonna have to draw straws again.
Wait a minute. You've got to
accept your responsibilities,
young man,
and shoot that old lady.
Hey, man, fuck you
and your irritated bowel!
Must shoot.
Now, look here,
it's the easiest thing
in the world.
Just pretend her head's
a casaba melon
and the gun is a melon baller.
What the fuck are you talkin'
about? A melon baller?
Look, man, you do it.
Oh, this is most irregular.
Now, look, with equal rights
comes equal responsibility.
I'm afraid Mr. Pancake
is correct. We cannot
draw straws again.
The exercise would lose all
credibility if you show
the loser can simply beg off.
Must shoot.
Hey, look, man, she's just
an old colored lady to you.
Come on, man, you do it.
Why, you sniveling
little coward.
What did you say to me?
Sniveling little coward.
You whiny muthafucka.
I will come up yo' stankin',
irritated asshole with this gun
and give you a lead colonic,
muthafucka!
You think you scare me,
you mewling punk?
You don't scare me.
Bull Connor and all his dogs
didn't scare me!
Now, be a man.
You fuck!
You ain't no fuckin' man!
Oh, my, this is most
distressin'.
Be a man!
You ain't no fuckin' man!
Fuckin' a 60-year-old
with pigtails!
Why, you bastard punk!
Mountain Girl is 53!
She could ride your ass
to jelly!
Oh, yeah?
(both grunting)
Gentlemen, please!
I seen Virginia hams
I'd rather stick my dick in
than that big ol' white chick!
(gunshot)
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
(pants tensely)
Oh, my.
I think he's hit.
(Lump) Oh, no....
I'll just check
the carotid artery.
That's a negative.
Is he dead, Professor?
Oh, sure he's dead, Lump.
I just checked
his carotid artery.
(Dorr) Well, this is
most irregular.
We shall need a Hefty bag.
She is in the kitchen.
You steal out with the carcass
while I dazzle her
with conversation.
My dear Mrs. Munson,
I have outlined your position
with my colleagues,
and I now return to you to
render our collective verdict.
Uh-huh.
There was much
spirited discussion...
...and an atmosphere
of frank give-and-take.
Some of our number were
initially appalled
at your proposal
that we simply return the money.
Some were more receptive.
I don't care if they was
receptive or not!
And that attitude, madam, was
a factor in our discussions.
To a man, I must say they were
devastated at the prospect
of not being able to contribute
to their respective charities.
Well, that is a shame.
Indeed, but at the end of the
day, your position prevailed.
So we have decided
to return the money,
every last cent of it,
and attend Sunday services,
rather than spend the remainder
of our days wastin' away
at the Mississippi Men's
Correctional Facility.
(thud)
Though that was the original
preference of some.
(grunts)
You are not assistin'
with the cadaver.
Oh, no need.
Just chuck it off the bridge.
Easiest thing in the world.
I'm just cleanin' up here.
(door shuts)
Oh! That's them.
Back already.
I'll just go dump these
in the hearse. (sniffs)
Yeah, easiest thing
in the world.
General!
No extra share, huh?
(grunts)
(stomach rumbling)
Mountain?
Garth?
(gasps)
I.B.S., dear?
(choking)
♪ Oh, come
♪ Let us go back
♪ To God
♪ Go back to God
♪ Oh, come on
♪ Let's go back to God
♪ Let us go back
Come on
♪ Let's go back to God
Get Garth.
♪ Let us go back
♪ To God
♪ Go back to God
Excellent.
I believe, at last, we have
the right man for the job.
(snoring)
(♪ gospel)
(continues snoring)
♪ They crucified the Savior
♪ And nailed Him to the cross
(♪ song continues)
(clock cuckoos)
(gulps)
(gasps)
♪ And ascended in a cloud
And ascended in a cloud
(cat screeches)
♪ And ascended in a cloud
♪ Oh, and ascended in a cloud ♪
(thunderclap)
The old woman is a more
formidable antagonist
than one had imagined.
(foghorn)
(grunts)
Now, Lump...
it falls to you
to finish the job.
The comedy must end.
You know, I've been doi''
some thinkin', Professor.
Oh, dear.
Maybe we should be
goin' to church.
Maybe she is right.
Ooh, dear, Lump.
I, eh, feared those
would be your words.
Not that I don't appreciate
you giving the matter
the benefit of your thought,
but recall, my dear boy,
our respective functions
in this enterprise.
I am a professor.
The professor,
as you yourself so often say.
The thinker.
Trained, in fact,
in the arts of cogitation.
You, Lump, are the goon,
the hooligan, the dumb brute,
whose actions must be directed
by a higher intelligence.
Yeah, I-I know, but&
Ah, ah, ah!
No buts, dear boy.
Do not repeat
the error of thinkin'.
Now is the moment of praxis.
Now, Lump, you must act.
Well, I can't do it, Professor.
A nice old lady like that.
Think of the riches, Lump,
that you and I alone
shall divide.
Yeah, I-I-I know, but...
And reflect also that
if you decline to act,
thus forcin' me to do so,
you shall no longer have
any entitlement to the money.
Your offices shall
have been nugatory.
You mean y-you're
gonna kill her?
Of course, yes.
My hand shall be forced.
I can't allow you
to do that, Professor.
(laughs) You... allow?
Mm-hmm.
(laughs) Not allow?
What presumption!
You stupid boy!
You very...
very, extremely stupid boy.
Oh, yeah?
Who looks stupid now?
No bullets?
Perhaps it had to be thus.
"Lo, in yon brilliant
window-niche
"How statue-like
I see thee stand
"A raven
(caws)
(foghorn)
"The agate lamp within thy hand
"Ah, Psyche!
"From the regions which
Are holy land!"
Ugh!
(coat tears)
Huh?
Uh-huh.
Professor? (gasps)
Mm, mm, mm!
Couldn't face the music.
I appreciate that,
but we don't know what to do.
Tried that, too. Eh, eh...
Oh...
Uh, Mrs. Munson...
Gotta make a statement,
Sheriff.
Ma'am, could it possibly wait?
We're kinda busy down here
today.
Oh, well, I suppose
it could wait,
but it's about
that casino money.
Let me call you back.
You know somethin' about it?
Somethin'? Everything!
I got it at home.
You got what at home?
The money!
$1.6 million dollars.
It's down in my root cellar.
How did it get there, Marva?
Well, a bunch of
desperate men stole it
and put it there, that's how!
See, they was musicians
of the Renaissance period.
(chuckles) Turned out they
really couldn't play,
but they could recite poems
that'd break your heart.
The ringleader spoke
in dead tongues.
Does he now?
Oh, I tried to get you
to see him.
That night.
Yes, ma'am.
I had to holler at 'em about
stealin' all that money.
Mm-hmm.
And I guess I made 'em
feel real bad,
'cause they just picked up
and left without
takin' the money!
And they let Pickles out!
So you want us to come over
and fetch him.
Oh, no, no, he's back.
What you want me to do
with the money?
Well...
you keep it!
Why don't you keep it?
Keep it?
Go on and keep it, Miss Marva.
Well...
It is just a penny off
of everybody's policy.
Could...?
You don't suppose I could...?
Yes, ma'am?
Could I just give it all
to Bob Jones University?
Yeah. That'd be nice.
Give it all to 'em!
That's a good idea!
As long as everybody knows.
(♪ "Let Your Light Shine on Me"
by Blind Willie Johnson)
How you doin'?
(laughs)
Oh! Pickles!
Oh, Lord, Pickles!
♪ Shine on
♪ Oh, let it shine on
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Shine on
♪ Oh, let it shine on
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on
♪ I know I've got religion
♪ And I ain't ashamed
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Angels in heaven
♪ Done wrote name
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on
♪ Oh, let it shine on
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Shine on
♪ Oh, let it shine on
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ I know I got religion
and I ain't ashamed
♪ Let our light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Angels up heaven
♪ Done wrote my name
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Come on, let it
Shine on
♪ Come on now, let it
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Oh, let it shine on
come on now, let it
♪ Shine on
Come and let it
♪ Let your light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine on me
♪ Let it shine
shine on
♪ You've got to let it shine
♪ If you wandered in darkness
shine on
♪ You want to see the light
♪ You gotta take his hand
shine on
♪ And shine all night
♪ You've got to let it shine
♪ You've got to let it
♪ Let it
♪ All night long
♪ Come on
♪ Yeah, let it shine
♪ Let it shine
Ooh
♪ You got to feel it
shine on
♪ In your heart
♪ You gotta feel it
shine on
♪ In your soul
♪ You gotta take his hand
shine on
♪ Oh, you gotta shine on me
♪ I said shine on me
shine on
♪ Let the light
from the lighthouse
♪ Shine...
♪ On...
♪ Me!
♪ Let it shine on me, yeah
♪ Hallelujah
♪ Ohh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah
(♪ gospel beat)
♪ Shine on!
♪ Shine
shine on!
♪ On
shine on
♪ Me
♪ Shine
shine on
♪ Let the light
♪ From the lighthouse
shine on
♪ Shine on me
♪ In the morning
shine on
♪ Shine on me
♪ In the new day
Shine on
♪ Shine on me
shine on
♪ In the midnight
shine on me
♪ Shine on me
shine on
♪ I need your peace
Shine on
♪ Shine on me
♪ I need your love
shine on me
♪ Shine on
♪ I need your spirit
shine on me
♪ Shine on me
♪ Let the light
from the lighthouse shine
♪ Shine
♪ On
♪ Me
♪ Yeah-ah-ah
(cheers/applause continue)
♪ Yes
(applause)
♪ Oh, yes
♪ Yes
♪ Thank you, thank you,
thank you
♪ Yes
(applause)
♪ Hallelujah!
♪ Thank you, Lord!
♪ Thank you, Lord
♪ Yeah
♪ You see, you been mighty good
♪ Oh, yes, you have
ohh
♪ You see,
you been mighty good
♪ Been mighty good
♪ Been mighty good, yeah
♪ Yes, yes, yes, Lord ♪