Man:
13 METERS. YOU SHOULD SEE IT.
OKAY, TAKE HER UP
AND OVER THE BOW RAIL.
Okay, Mir 2, we're going
over the bow.
Stay with us.
OKAY, QUIET. WE'RE ROLLING.
SEEING HER COMING OUT OF
THE DARKNESS LIKE A GHOST SHIP
STILL GETS ME EVERY TIME--
TO SEE THE SAD RUIN
OF THE GREAT SHIP SITTING HERE
WHERE SHE LANDED AT 2:30
IN THE MORNING OF APRIL 15, 1912
AFTER HER LONG FALL
FROM THE WORLD ABOVE.
YOU ARE SO FULL OF SHIT, BOSS.
Man:
DIVE SIX-- HERE WE ARE AGAIN
ON THE DECK OF TITANIC
2½ MILES DOWN, 3,821 METERS.
THE PRESSURE OUTSIDE IS
3½ TONS PER SQUARE INCH.
THESE WINDOWS ARE NINE INCHES
THICK AND IF THEY GO
IT'S SAYONARA
IN TWO MICROSECONDS.
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH
OF THAT BULLSHIT.
JUST PUT HER DOWN ON THE ROOF
OF THE OFFICER'S QUARTERS
LIKE YESTERDAY.
Man:
SURE.
Okay, Mir 2.
We have landed right
on the grand staircase.
You guys set to launch?
YEAH, BROCK--
LAUNCHING DUNKIN NOW.
GO, CHARLIE.
ALL RIGHT,
TETHER OUT.
Man:
Okay, Brock
we're dropping down
along the hull.
Brock:
ROGER THAT.
OKAY, DROP DOWN
AND GO
INTO THE FIRST CLASS
GANGWAY DOOR.
I WANT YOU GUYS WORKING
THE D DECK RECEPTION AREA
AND THE DINING SALOON.
Man:
Copy that.
TETHER OUT.
Man:
NOW LEFT, LEFT.
I'M COMING LEFT.
Brock:
Snoop Dog is on the move.
We're headed down the stairwell.
OKAY, LEWIS, DROP DOWN
TO B DECK.
A DECK.
Lewis:
GIVE ME SOME
ROPE, CAPTAIN.
B DECK-- GET IN
THERE, GET IN THERE.
Brock:
WATCH THE DOORFRAME.
WATCH THE DOORFRAME--
WATCH IT, WATCH IT.
I SEE IT.
I GOT IT.
WE'RE GOOD--
JUST CHILL, BOSS.
Brock:
MAKE YOUR TURN.
COME AROUND.
Lewis:
CABLE OUT, CAPTAIN.
MAKE YOUR TURN,
WATCH THE WALL.
YEAH, BROCK, WE'RE
AT THE PIANO, YOU COPY?
Brock:
Okay, copy that.
OKAY, RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE-- THAT'S IT!
THAT'S THE BEDROOM DOOR.
I SEE IT... I SEE IT.
WE'RE IN!
WE'RE IN, BABY,
WE'RE THERE!
Brock:
THAT'S HOCKLEY'S BED.
THAT'S WHERE
THE SON OF A BITCH SLEPT.
Lewis:
OOPS, SOMEBODY LEFT
THE WATER RUNNING.
HEY, HOLD IT JUST A SECOND.
GO BACK TO THE RIGHT.
THAT WARDROBE DOOR--
GET CLOSER.
YOU SMELLING SOMETHING, BOSS?
I WANT TO SEE WHAT'S UNDER IT.
GIVE ME
MY HANDS, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT EASY,
IT MIGHT COME APART.
OKAY.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
FLIP IT OVER,
FLIP IT OVER, GO.
KEEP GOING,
GO, GO, GO.
OKAY, DROP IT.
OH, BABY, BABY,
ARE YOU SEEING THIS, BOSS?
IT'S PAYDAY, BOYS.
KA-CHING!
WE DID IT, BOBBY.
Lewis:
OH, YEAH, WHO'S THE MAN?
WHO'S THE
BEST, BABY?
SAY IT, SAY IT.
YOU ARE, LEWIS.
BOBBY, MY CIGAR.
Bobby:
RIGHT HERE.
Brock:
OKAY, CRACK HER OPEN.
SHIT.
NO DIAMOND.
YOU KNOW, BOSS, THIS SAME THING
HAPPENED TO GERALDO
AND HIS CAREER NEVER RECOVERED.
TURN THE CAMERA OFF.
Bobby:
BROCK, THE PARTNERS
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
HOW IT'S GOING.
HEY, DAVE, BARRY, HI.
LOOK, IT WASN'T IN THE SAFE
BUT HEY, HEY,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE'S STILL PLENTY
OF PLACES IT COULD BE.
HELL YES!-- THE FLOOR DEBRIS
IN THE SUITE, THE MOTHER'S ROOM
PURSER'S SAFE ON C DECK.
JIMMY HOFFA'S BRIEFCASE.
Brock:
A DOZEN OTHER PLACES.
GUYS, LOOK, YOU'VE JUST GOT
TO TRUST MY INSTINCTS.
I KNOW WE'RE CLOSE.
WE JUST GOT TO GO THROUGH
A LITTLE PROCESS OF ELIMINATION.
HANG ON A SECOND.
LET ME SEE THAT.
Bobby:
WE MIGHT HAVE
SOMETHING HERE, GUYS.
WHERE'S THE PHOTOGRAPH
OF THE NECKLACE?
WE'LL CALL YOU RIGHT BACK.
I'LL BE GODDAMNED.
Reporter:
Treasure hunter Brock Lovett
is best known
for finding Spanish gold...
IT'S OKAY.
I'LL FEED YOU IN A MINUTE.
Now he has chartered
Russian subs to reach
the most famous shipwreck
of all: the Titanic.
He is with us live
via satellite
from the research ship Keldysh
in the North Atlantic.
Hello, Brock.
Brock:
Hello, Tracy.
Everyone knows the familiar
stories of Titanic--
the nobility, the band playing
till the very end and all that.
But what I'm interested in
are the untold stories
the secrets locked deep
inside the hull of Titanic.
We're out here using
robot technology
to go further
into the wreck
than anybody's
ever done before.
Your expedition is at the center
of a storm of controversy
over salvage rights
and even ethics.
Many are calling you
a grave robber.
Nobody called
the recovery
of the artifacts
of King Tut's tomb
"grave robbing."
Woman:
WHAT IS IT?
TURN THAT UP, DEAR.
I have museum-trained experts
out here making sure
that these relics are preserved
and catalogued properly.
Take a look at this drawing
that we found just today:
a piece of paper that's been
underwater for 84 years
and my team were able
to preserve it intact.
Should this have remained unseen
at the bottom of the ocean
for eternity?
I'LL BE GODDAMNED.
Man:
Vnimanye, Vnimanye...
Bobby:
BROCK!
THERE'S A SATELLITE
CALL FOR YOU.
BOBBY, WE'RE LAUNCHING.
YOU SEE THESE SUBMERSIBLES
GOING IN THE WATER?
TRUST ME, BUDDY.
YOU WANT TO TAKE THIS CALL.
THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
YOU GOT TO SPEAK UP.
SHE'S KIND OF OLD.
GREAT.
THIS IS BROCK LOVETT.
HOW CAN I
HELP YOU, MRS...
CALVERT, ROSE CALVERT.
MRS. CALVERT?
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU HAD FOUND THE HEART
OF THE OCEAN YET, MR. LOVETT.
TOLD YOU YOU WANTED
TO TAKE THE CALL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE
MY ATTENTION, ROSE.
CAN YOU TELL
US WHO THE WOMAN
IN THE PICTURE IS?
OH, YES.
THE WOMAN IN THE PICTURE IS ME.
SHE'S A GODDAMNED LIAR--
SOME NUT CASE SEEKING
MONEY OR PUBLICITY.
GOD ONLY KNOWS WHY, LIKE THAT
RUSSIAN BABE, ANESTHESIA.
THEY'RE INBOUND!
ROSE DEWITT BUKATER DIED
ON THE TITANIC
WHEN SHE WAS 17, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IF SHE HAD LIVED,
SHE'D BE OVER 100 BY NOW.
101 NEXT MONTH.
OKAY, SO SHE'S A VERY OLD
GODDAMNED LIAR.
LOOK, I'VE ALREADY DONE
THE BACKGROUND ON THIS WOMAN
ALL THE WAY
BACK TO THE '20s
WHEN SHE WAS WORKING
AS AN ACTRESS.
AN ACTRESS!
THERE'S YOUR FIRST CLUE,
SHERLOCK!
HER NAME WAS
ROSE DAWSON BACK THEN.
THEN SHE MARRIES
THIS GUY NAMED CALVERT.
THEY MOVE TO CEDAR RAPIDS
AND SHE PUNCHES OUT
A COUPLE OF KIDS.
NOW, CALVERT'S DEAD
AND FROM WHAT I HEAR,
CEDAR RAPIDS IS DEAD.
AND EVERYBODY WHO
KNOWS ABOUT THE DIAMOND
IS SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD
OR ON THIS BOAT, BUT SHE KNOWS.
DOESN'T EXACTLY
TRAVEL LIGHT, DOES SHE?
MRS. CALVERT,
I'M BROCK LOVETT.
WELCOME TO THE KELDYSH.
OKAY, LET'S GET HER
INSIDE THERE.
HI, MS. CALVERT.
HI.
WELCOME TO THE KELDYSH.
Man:
HEY.
HEY!
Rose:
YES?
ARE YOUR STATEROOMS
ALL RIGHT?
Rose:
OH, YES,
VERY NICE.
HAVE YOU MET MY
GRANDDAUGHTER LIZZIE?
SHE TAKES CARE OF ME.
WE MET JUST
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
REMEMBER, NANA, UP ON DECK?
THERE, THAT'S NICE.
HAVE TO HAVE
MY PICTURES
WHEN I TRAVEL.
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE?
YES.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE MY DRAWING.
Brock:
LOUIS XVI WORE A FABULOUS STONE
THAT WAS CALLED
THE BLUE DIAMOND OF THE CROWN
WHICH DISAPPEARED IN 1792
ABOUT THE SAME TIME
OLD LOUIS LOST EVERYTHING
FROM THE NECK UP.
THE THEORY GOES
THAT THE CROWN DIAMOND
WAS CHOPPED, TOO
RECUT INTO A HEARTLIKE SHAPE
THAT BECAME KNOWN AS
"THE HEART OF THE OCEAN."
TODAY IT WOULD BE WORTH MORE
THAN THE HOPE DIAMOND.
IT WAS A DREADFUL,
HEAVY THING.
I ONLY WORE IT
THIS ONCE.
Lizzie:
YOU ACTUALLY
THINK
THIS IS YOU, NANA?
IT IS ME, DEAR.
WASN'T I A DISH?
I TRACKED IT DOWN
THROUGH INSURANCE RECORDS--
AN OLD CLAIM THAT WAS SETTLED
UNDER TERMS OF ABSOLUTE SECRECY.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHO THE CLAIMANT
WAS, ROSE?
I SHOULD IMAGINE
SOMEONE NAMED HOCKLEY.
Brock:
NATHAN HOCKLEY,
THAT'S RIGHT.
PITTSBURGH STEEL TYCOON.
CLAIM WAS FOR
A DIAMOND NECKLACE
HIS SON CALEDON BOUGHT
HIS FIANCEE-- YOU
A WEEK BEFORE
HE SAILED ON TITANIC.
IT WAS FILED RIGHT
AFTER THE SINKING
SO THE DIAMOND HAD TO HAVE
GONE DOWN WITH THE SHIP.
YOU SEE THE DATE?
"APRIL 14, 1912."
WHICH MEANS IF YOUR GRANDMOTHER
IS WHO SHE SAYS SHE IS
SHE WAS WEARING THE DIAMOND
THE DAY THE TITANIC SANK.
AND THAT MAKES YOU
MY NEW BEST FRIEND.
THESE ARE SOME
OF THE THINGS
WE RECOVERED
FROM YOUR STATEROOM.
THIS WAS MINE.
HOW EXTRAORDINARY!
AND IT LOOKS
THE SAME AS IT DID
THE LAST TIME I SAW IT.
THE REFLECTION
HAS CHANGED A BIT.
ARE YOU READY TO GO
BACK TO TITANIC?
Lewis:
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
SHE HITS THE BERG ON
THE STARBOARD SIDE, RIGHT?
SHE KIND OF BUMPS ALONG
PUNCHING HOLES LIKE
MORSE CODE-- DIT-DIT-DIT--
ALONG THE SIDE,
BELOW THE WATERLINE.
THEN THE FORWARD COMPARTMENTS
START TO FLOOD.
NOW, AS THE WATER
LEVEL RISES
IT SPILLS OVER THE
WATERTIGHT BULKHEADS
WHICH UNFORTUNATELY DON'T GO
ANY HIGHER THAN E DECK.
SO NOW AS THE BOW GOES DOWN,
THE STERN RISES UP
SLOW AT FIRST, THEN FASTER
AND FASTER UNTIL FINALLY
SHE'S GOT HER WHOLE ASS
IS STICKING UP IN THE AIR
AND THAT'S A BIG ASS.
WE'RE TALKING
20,000, 30,000 TONS, OKAY?
AND THE HULL'S NOT DESIGNED
TO DEAL WITH THAT PRESSURE
SO WHAT HAPPENS?
SHE SPLITS,
RIGHT DOWN TO THE KEEL
AND THE STERN
FALLS BACK LEVEL.
THEN AS THE BOW SINKS,
IT PULLS THE STERN VERTICAL
AND THEN FINALLY DETACHES.
NOW, THE STERN SECTION JUST
KIND OF BOBS THERE LIKE A CORK
FOR A COUPLE OF MINUTES, FLOODS
AND FINALLY GOES UNDER
ABOUT 2:20 A.M.
TWO HOURS AND 40 MINUTES
AFTER THE COLLISION.
THE BOW SECTION PLANES AWAY
LANDING ABOUT
A HALF A MILE AWAY
GOING 20, 30 KNOTS WHEN
IT HITS THE OCEAN FLOOR.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
THANK YOU FOR THAT FINE
FORENSIC ANALYSIS, MR. BODINE.
OF COURSE, THE EXPERIENCE OF IT
WAS... SOMEWHAT DIFFERENT.
WILL YOU SHARE IT WITH US?
I'M TAKING HER TO REST.
NO.
COME ON, NANA.
NO!
TAPE RECORDER.
TELL US, ROSE.
IT'S BEEN 84 YEARS.
IT'S OKAY.
JUST TRY TO REMEMBER
ANYTHING--
ANYTHING AT ALL.
DO YOU WANT TO HEAR THIS
OR NOT, MR. LOVETT?
IT'S BEEN 84 YEARS...
AND I CAN STILL SMELL
THE FRESH PAINT.
THE CHINA HAD NEVER BEEN USED.
THE SHEETS HAD NEVER
BEEN SLEPT IN.
TITANIC WAS CALLED
"THE SHIP OF DREAMS"
AND IT WAS, IT REALLY WAS.
Man:
ALL THIRD-CLASS PASSENGERS
WITH A FORWARD BERTH
THIS WAY, PLEASE,
THIS QUEUE.
RIGHT HERE.
BIG BOAT, HUH?
DADDY, IT'S A SHIP.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T SEE WHAT
ALL THE FUSS IS ABOUT.
IT DOESN'T
LOOK ANY BIGGER
THAN THE MAURITANIA.
YOU CAN BE BLASE
ABOUT SOME THINGS, ROSE
BUT NOT
ABOUT TITANIC.
IT'S OVER
100 FEET LONGER
THAN MAURITANIA
AND FAR MORE LUXURIOUS.
YOUR DAUGHTER IS
FAR TOO DIFFICULT
TO IMPRESS, RUTH.
SO THIS IS
THE SHIP
THEY SAY IS
UNSINKABLE.
IT IS UNSINKABLE.
GOD HIMSELF COULD
NOT SINK THIS SHIP.
SIR, YOU
HAVE TO CHECK
YOUR BAGGAGE
THROUGH THE
MAIN TERMINAL.
IT'S ROUND
THAT WAY, SIR.
I PUT MY FAITH
IN YOU, GOOD SIR.
NOW, KINDLY SEE MY MAN.
YES, SIR,
MY PLEASURE, SIR.
IF I CAN DO
ANYTHING AT ALL.
OH, YES, RIGHT.
ALL THE TRUNKS
FROM THAT CAR THERE
12 FROM HERE, AND THE SAFE...
TO THE PARLOR SUITE,
ROOMS B-52, 54, 56.
LADIES...
BETTER HURRY.
MY COAT?
Woman:
I HAVE IT.
Man:
ALL THIRD-CLASS
PASSENGERS
DUE HERE FOR HEALTH INSPECTION.
ALL THIRD-CLASS PASSENGERS
HEAD UP.
WELCOME ABOARD, MA'AM.
WELCOME TO TITANIC.
Rose:
IT WAS THE SHIP OF DREAMS
TO EVERYONE ELSE.
TO ME IT WAS A SLAVE SHIP
TAKING ME BACK TO AMERICA
IN CHAINS.
OUTWARDLY, I WAS EVERYTHING A
WELL-BROUGHT-UP GIRL SHOULD BE.
INSIDE, I WAS SCREAMING.
JACK, YOU ARE PAZZO.
YOU BET EVERYTHING
WE HAVE.
WHEN YOU GOT NOTHING
YOU GOT NOTHING
TO LOSE.
SVEN?
ALL RIGHT... MOMENT OF TRUTH.
SOMEBODY'S LIFE'S
ABOUT TO CHANGE.
FABRIZIO?
NIENTE.
OLAF?
NOTHING.
SVEN?
UH-OH...
TWO PAIR.
I'M SORRY, FABRIZIO.
CHE "SORRY?" MA VAFFANCULO!
YOU BET ALL
THE MONEY.
I'M SORRY,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SEE
YOUR MOM AGAIN
FOR A LONG TIME
BECAUSE WE'RE
GOING TO AMERICA.
FULL HOUSE, BOYS.
WHOA!
YEAH!
DIO MIO, GRAZIE!
COME ON.
FIGLIO DI PUTTANA!
I'M GOING HOME!
I'M GOING HOME.
I GO TO AMERICA.
Man:
NO, MATE.
TITANIC GO TO AMERICA
IN FIVE MINUTES.
COME ON.
COME ON, HERE.
Fabrizio:
ANDIAMO.
WE'RE RIDING IN
HIGH STYLE NOW.
WE'RE A COUPLE
OF REGULAR SWELLS.
WE'RE PRACTICALLY GODDAMN
ROYALTY, RAGAZZO MIO.
Fabrizio:
YOU SEE, IT'S MY DESTINO!
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
I GO TO AMERICA
TO BE MILLIONARIO.
Driver:
WHOA, WHOA!
BASTARDO!
YOU'RE PAZZO!
MAYBE, BUT I'VE
GOT THE TICKETS.
COME ON, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE FAST.
ASPETTA!
WAIT, WAIT!
HEY, WAIT.
WE'RE PASSENGERS.
PASSENGERS.
HAVE YOU BEEN THROUGH
THE INSPECTION QUEUE?
OF COURSE!
ANYWAY, WE DON'T
HAVE ANY LICE.
WE'RE AMERICANS,
BOTH OF US.
RIGHT, COME ABOARD.
WE'RE THE LUCKIEST
SONS OF BITCHES
IN THE WORLD, YOU KNOW THAT?
GOOD-BYE!
YOU KNOW SOMEBODY?
OF COURSE NOT--
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
GOOD-BYE! I'LL MISS YOU!
GOOD-BYE!
I'M GOING TO NEVER
FORGET YOU.
ALL THE WAY, DARLING.
360, 360...
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
OH, RIGHT HERE.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
JACK.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M JACK DAWSON.
HOW YOU DOING?
WHO SAYS YOU GET
TOP BUNK, HUH?
THIS IS YOUR PRIVATE
PROMENADE DECK, SIR.
WOULD YOU BE
REQUIRING ANYTHING?
HMM...
EXCUSE ME.
Woman:
THIS ONE?
Rose:
NO... IT HAD A LOT
OF FACES ON IT.
THIS IS THE ONE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
ALL OF THEM OUT, MISS?
YES... WE NEED A LITTLE
COLOR IN THIS ROOM.
PUT IT IN THERE,
IN THE WARDROBE.
GOD, NOT THOSE
FINGER PAINTINGS AGAIN.
THEY CERTAINLY WERE
A WASTE OF MONEY.
THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN CAL'S
TASTE IN ART
AND MINE IS THAT I HAVE SOME.
THEY'RE FASCINATING...
LIKE BEING INSIDE
A DREAM OR SOMETHING.
THERE'S TRUTH, BUT NO LOGIC.
WHAT'S
THE ARTIST'S NAME?
SOMETHING
PICASSO.
"SOMETHING
PICASSO."
HE WON'T AMOUNT
TO A THING.
HE WON'T, TRUST ME.
PUT THE DEGAS
IN THE BEDROOM.
AT LEAST THEY
WERE CHEAP.
AH, PUT IT
IN THE WARDROBE.
AT CHERBOURG, A WOMAN CAME
ABOARD NAMED MARGARET BROWN.
WE ALL CALLED HER MOLLY.
HISTORY WOULD CALL HER
"THE UNSINKABLE MOLLY BROWN."
WELL, I WASN'T
ABOUT TO WAIT
ALL DAY FOR YOU, SONNY.
HERE, YOU THINK YOU CAN MANAGE?
HER HUSBAND HAD STRUCK GOLD
SOMEPLACE OUT WEST
AND SHE WAS WHAT MOTHER CALLED
"NEW MONEY."
BY THE NEXT AFTERNOON,
WE WERE STEAMING WEST
FROM THE COAST OF IRELAND
WITH NOTHING OUT AHEAD OF US
BUT OCEAN.
TAKE HER TO SEA,
MR. MURDOCH.
LET'S STRETCH HER LEGS.
YES, SIR.
ALL AHEAD FULL,
MR. MOODY.
VERY GOOD, SIR.
ALL AHEAD FULL.
Man:
COME ON, LADS.
GET MOVING.
WHAT'S THE READING?
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S STOKE THEM RIGHT UP!
WE'RE GOING FULL AHEAD!
21 KNOTS, SIR.
HEY, LOOK,
LOOK, LOOK!
SEE IT?
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
SEE HIM?
LOOK AT THAT ONE.
LOOK AT HIM JUMP!
WHOO-HOO!
WHOO!
I CAN SEE THE STATUE
OF LIBERTY ALREADY!
VERY SMALL,
OF COURSE.
I'M THE KING OF THE WORLD.
Man:
SHE'S THE LARGEST MOVING OBJECT
EVER MADE BY THE HAND OF MAN
IN ALL HISTORY.
AND OUR MASTER SHIPBUILDER,
MR. ANDREWS HERE
DESIGNED HER
FROM THE KEEL PLATES UP.
WELL, I MAY HAVE
KNOCKED HER TOGETHER
BUT THE IDEA
WAS MR. ISMAY'S.
HE ENVISIONED A STEAMER SO GRAND
IN SCALE AND SO LUXURIOUS
IN ITS APPOINTMENTS
THAT ITS SUPREMACY
WOULD NEVER BE
CHALLENGED.
AND HERE SHE IS
WILLED INTO
SOLID REALITY.
Man:
HEAR, HEAR.
YOU KNOW I DON'T
LIKE THAT, ROSE.
SHE KNOWS.
WE'LL BOTH
HAVE THE LAMB...
RARE, WITH VERY
LITTLE MINT SAUCE.
HMM... YOU LIKE LAMB,
RIGHT, SWEET PEA?
ARE YOU GOING TO CUT HER MEAT
FOR HER, TOO, THERE, CAL?
HEY, UH, WHO THOUGHT
OF THE NAME "TITANIC"?
WAS IT YOU, BRUCE?
WELL, YES, ACTUALLY.
I WANTED TO CONVEY
SHEER SIZE
AND THE SIZE
MEANS STABILITY
LUXURY, AND ABOVE
ALL, STRENGTH.
DO YOU KNOW OF DR. FREUD,
MR. ISMAY?
HIS IDEAS ABOUT THE MALE
PREOCCUPATION WITH SIZE
MIGHT BE OF PARTICULAR
INTEREST TO YOU.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
EXCUSE ME.
I DO APOLOGIZE.
SHE'S A PISTOL, CAL.
HOPE YOU CAN HANDLE HER.
WELL, I MAY HAVE
TO START MINDING
WHAT SHE READS FROM NOW ON,
WON'T I, MRS. BROWN?
FREUD-- WHO IS HE?
IS HE A PASSENGER?
...MAKES THESE WAVES,
MAKES THEM SPIN.
Fabrizio:
THE SHIP IS
NICE, HUH?
YEAH, IT'S AN IRISH SHIP.
IS ENGLISH, NO?
NO, IT WAS BUILT IN IRELAND.
15,000 IRISHMEN BUILT THIS SHIP.
SOLID AS A ROCK.
BIG IRISH HANDS.
THAT'S TYPICAL.
FIRST-CLASS DOGS COME
DOWN HERE TO TAKE A SHIT.
UH... IT
LETS US KNOW
WHERE WE RANK
IN THE SCHEME OF THINGS.
LIKE WE COULD FORGET?
I'M TOMMY RYAN.
JACK DAWSON.
HELLO.
FABRIZIO.
HI. DO YOU MAKE ANY MONEY
WITH YOUR DRAWINGS?
OH, FORGET IT, BOYO.
YOU'D AS LIKE HAVE ANGELS
FLY OUT OF YOUR ARSE
AS GET NEXT
TO THE LIKES OF HER.
DO YOU MIND?
I HOPE YOU'RE
PROUD OF THIS.
I SAW MY WHOLE LIFE
AS IF I'D ALREADY LIVED IT--
AN ENDLESS PARADE
OF PARTIES AND COTILLIONS
YACHTS AND POLO MATCHES
ALWAYS THE SAME NARROW PEOPLE,
THE SAME MINDLESS CHATTER.
I FELT LIKE I WAS STANDING
AT A GREAT PRECIPICE
WITH NO ONE TO PULL ME BACK
NO ONE WHO CARED
OR EVEN NOTICED.
DON'T DO IT.
STAY BACK.
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
COME ON.
JUST GIVE ME
YOUR HAND.
I'LL PULL YOU
BACK OVER.
NO! STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
I MEAN IT.
I'LL LET GO.
NO, YOU WON'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
NO, I WON'T?
DON'T PRESUME TO TELL ME
WHAT I WILL AND WILL NOT DO.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
WELL, YOU WOULD HAVE
DONE IT ALREADY.
YOU'RE DISTRACTING ME.
GO AWAY.
I CAN'T.
I'M INVOLVED NOW.
YOU LET GO
AND I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO JUMP IN THERE AFTER YOU.
DON'T BE ABSURD.
YOU'LL BE KILLED.
I'M A GOOD SWIMMER.
THE FALL ALONE
WOULD KILL YOU.
IT WOULD HURT.
I'M NOT SAYING
IT WOULDN'T.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH
I'M A LOT
MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT WATER BEING SO COLD.
HOW COLD?
FREEZING.
MAYBE A COUPLE DEGREES OVER.
YOU EVER, UH...
EVER BEEN TO WISCONSIN?
WHAT?
WELL, THEY HAVE SOME
OF THE COLDEST WINTERS AROUND.
I GREW UP THERE
NEAR CHIPPEWA FALLS.
I REMEMBER WHEN I WAS A KID
ME AND MY FATHER,
WE WENT ICE FISHING
OUT ON
LAKE WISSOTA.
ICE FISHING IS, YOU KNOW,
WHERE YOU...
I KNOW WHAT ICE FISHING IS!
SORRY.
YOU JUST SEEM LIKE, YOU KNOW,
KIND OF AN INDOOR GIRL.
ANYWAY, I, UH...
I FELL THROUGH
SOME THIN ICE
AND I'M TELLING YOU...
WATER THAT COLD,
LIKE RIGHT DOWN THERE
IT HITS YOU
LIKE A THOUSAND KNIVES
STABBING YOU ALL OVER YOUR BODY.
YOU CAN'T
BREATHE
YOU CAN'T THINK--
AT LEAST NOT ABOUT ANYTHING
BUT THE PAIN.
WHICH IS WHY I'M NOT
LOOKING FORWARD
TO JUMPING IN THERE
AFTER YOU.
LIKE I SAID...
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
I GUESS I'M KIND OF HOPING
YOU'LL COME BACK OVER THE RAIL
AND GET ME OFF THE HOOK HERE.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
THAT'S WHAT
EVERYBODY SAYS, BUT...
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, MISS
I'M NOT THE ONE HANGING OFF
THE BACK OF A SHIP HERE.
COME ON.
COME ON, GIVE ME
YOUR HAND.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS.
WHEW!
I'M JACK DAWSON.
ROSE DEWITT BUKATER.
I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO GET YOU
TO WRITE
THAT ONE DOWN.
COME ON.
I GOT YOU!
COME ON!
HELP! PLEASE!
PLEASE GET ME!
LISTEN...
LISTEN TO ME.
I'VE GOT YOU...
I WON'T LET GO.
NOW PULL
YOURSELF UP.
COME ON!
COME ON.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN DO IT.
I GOT YOU.
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
YOU STAND BACK!
AND DON'T MOVE AN INCH!
FETCH THE MASTER-AT-ARMS!
CARE FOR A BRANDY?
Cal:
THIS IS COMPLETELY
UNACCEPTABLE!
WHAT MADE YOU THINK
THAT YOU COULD
PUT YOUR HANDS
ON MY FIANCEE?
LOOK AT ME, YOU FILTH!
CAL...
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU WERE DOING?
CAL, STOP.
IT WAS
AN ACCIDENT.
AN ACCIDENT?
IT WAS.
STUPID REALLY.
I WAS LEANING OVER,
AND I SLIPPED.
I WAS LEANING FAR OVER
TO SEE THE, UH...
UH... UH...
THE, UH... UH...
PROPELLERS?
PROPELLERS,
AND I SLIPPED.
AND I WOULD HAVE
GONE OVERBOARD
BUT MR. DAWSON HERE
SAVED ME
AND ALMOST
WENT OVER HIMSELF.
Cal:
YOU WANTED
TO SEE...
SHE WANTED TO SEE
THE PROPELLERS.
LIKE I SAID
WOMEN AND MACHINERY
DO NOT MIX.
WAS THAT
THE WAY OF IT?
YEAH... YEAH, THAT WAS
PRETTY MUCH IT.
WELL, THE BOY'S A HERO THEN.
GOOD FOR YOU, SON.
WELL DONE.
SO IT'S
ALL'S WELL
AND BACK
TO OUR BRANDY, EH?
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU MUST BE FREEZING.
LET'S GET YOU INSIDE.
PERHAPS A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR THE BOY.
OF COURSE.
MR. LOVEJOY, I THINK
A 20 SHOULD DO IT.
IS THAT THE GOING RATE
FOR SAVING THE WOMAN
YOU LOVE?
ROSE IS DISPLEASED.
WHAT TO DO?
I KNOW.
PERHAPS YOU COULD JOIN US
FOR DINNER TOMORROW EVENING
TO REGALE OUR GROUP
WITH...
YOUR HEROIC TALE.
SURE, COUNT ME IN.
GOOD.
SETTLED THEN.
THIS SHOULD BE
INTERESTING.
MMM.
CAN I, UH...
BUM A SMOKE?
YOU'LL WANT
TO TIE THOSE.
IT'S INTERESTING.
THE YOUNG LADY SLIPS
SO SUDDENLY
AND YOU STILL HAD TIME
TO REMOVE YOUR JACKET
AND YOUR SHOES.
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
MELANCHOLY.
I DON'T PRETEND
TO KNOW WHY.
I INTENDED TO SAVE THIS
UNTIL THE
ENGAGEMENT GALA
NEXT WEEK.
BUT I THOUGHT TONIGHT.
GOOD GRACIOUS.
PERHAPS AS
A REMINDER
OF MY FEELINGS
FOR YOU.
IS IT A...?
DIAMOND? YES.
56 CARATS TO BE EXACT.
IT WAS WORN BY LOUIS XVI
AND THEY CALLED IT
"LE COEUR DE LA MER."
Both:
THE HEART OF THE OCEAN.
YES.
IT'S OVERWHELMING.
WELL, IT'S FOR ROYALTY.
WE ARE ROYALTY, ROSE.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NOTHING
I COULDN'T GIVE YOU.
THERE'S NOTHING
I'D DENY YOU
IF YOU WOULD NOT DENY ME.
NOW OPEN YOUR HEART
TO ME, ROSE.
Jack:
WELL, I'VE BEEN ON
MY OWN SINCE I WAS 15
SINCE MY FOLKS DIED.
AND I HAD NO
BROTHERS OR SISTERS
OR CLOSE KIN IN THAT
PART OF THE COUNTRY.
SO I LIT
ON OUT OF THERE
AND I HAVEN'T
BEEN BACK SINCE.
YOU COULD JUST CALL ME
A TUMBLEWEED
BLOWING IN THE WIND.
WELL, ROSE...
WE'VE WALKED
ABOUT A MILE
AROUND THIS BOAT DECK
AND CHEWED OVER HOW
GREAT THE WEATHER'S BEEN
AND HOW I GREW UP
BUT I RECKON THAT'S
NOT WHY YOU CAME TO
TALK TO ME, IS IT?
MR. DAWSON, I...
JACK.
JACK...
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR WHAT YOU DID.
NOT JUST FOR...
FOR PULLING ME BACK
BUT FOR
YOUR DISCRETION.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT
YOU MUST BE THINKING.
POOR LITTLE RICH GIRL.
WHAT DOES SHE KNOW
ABOUT MISERY?
NO.
NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
WHAT I WAS THINKING WAS
WHAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED
TO THIS GIRL
TO MAKE HER THINK
SHE HAD NO WAY OUT?
WELL, I...
IT WAS EVERYTHING.
IT WAS MY WHOLE WORLD
AND ALL
THE PEOPLE IN IT
AND THE INERTIA
OF MY LIFE
PLUNGING AHEAD
AND ME, POWERLESS
TO STOP IT.
GOD! LOOK AT THAT THING.
YOU WOULD HAVE GONE
STRAIGHT TO THE BOTTOM.
500 INVITATIONS
HAVE GONE OUT.
ALL OF PHILADELPHIA
SOCIETY WILL BE THERE
AND ALL THE WHILE
I FEEL I'M...
STANDING IN THE MIDDLE
OF A CROWDED ROOM
SCREAMING AT THE TOP
OF MY LUNGS
AND NO ONE
EVEN LOOKS UP.
DO YOU LOVE HIM?
PARDON ME?
YOU'RE BEING VERY RUDE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
ASKING ME THIS.
WELL, IT'S
A SIMPLE QUESTION.
DO YOU LOVE
THE GUY OR NOT?
THIS IS NOT
A SUITABLE CONVERSATION.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST
ANSWER THE QUESTION?
THIS IS ABSURD.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME,
AND I DON'T KNOW YOU
AND WE ARE NOT HAVING
THIS CONVERSATION AT ALL.
YOU ARE RUDE AND UNCOUTH
AND PRESUMPTUOUS
AND I AM LEAVING NOW.
JACK... MR. DAWSON,
IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE.
I SOUGHT YOU OUT
TO THANK YOU
AND NOW I HAVE
THANKED YOU...
AND YOU'VE INSULTED ME.
WELL, YOU DESERVED IT.
RIGHT.
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE LEAVING.
I AM.
YOU ARE SO ANNOYING.
WAIT.
I DON'T HAVE TO LEAVE.
THIS IS MY PART
OF THE SHIP.
YOU LEAVE.
OH-HO-HO,
WELL, WELL, WELL.
NOW WHO'S BEING RUDE?
WHAT IS THIS STUPID THING
YOU'RE CARRYING AROUND?
SO WHAT ARE YOU,
AN ARTIST OR SOMETHING?
WELL, THESE ARE RATHER GOOD.
THEY'RE, UH...
THEY'RE VERY GOOD
ACTUALLY.
JACK, THIS IS
EXQUISITE WORK.
THEY DIDN'T THINK TOO MUCH
OF THEM IN OLD PAREE.
PARIS!
YOU DO GET AROUND
FOR A POOR...
WELL, UH, UH, A PERSON
OF LIMITED MEANS.
GO ON, A POOR GUY,
YOU CAN SAY IT.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
AND THESE WERE DRAWN
FROM LIFE?
WELL, THAT'S ONE OF THE
GOOD THINGS ABOUT PARIS--
LOTS OF GIRLS WILLING
TO TAKE THEIR CLOTHES OFF.
YOU LIKED THIS WOMAN.
YOU USED HER
SEVERAL TIMES.
WELL, SHE HAD BEAUTIFUL
HANDS, YOU SEE?
I THINK YOU MUST HAVE HAD
A LOVE AFFAIR WITH HER.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO.
JUST WITH HER HANDS.
SHE WAS A
ONE-LEGGED PROSTITUTE.
SEE?
OH!
AH, SHE HAD A GOOD SENSE
OF HUMOR, THOUGH.
OH, AND THIS LADY...
SHE USED TO SIT AT
THIS BAR EVERY NIGHT
WEARING EVERY PIECE
OF JEWELRY SHE OWNED
JUST WAITING
FOR HER LONG-LOST LOVE.
CALLED HER
MADAME BIJOU.
SEE HOW HER CLOTHES
ARE ALL MOTH-EATEN?
WELL, YOU HAVE A GIFT, JACK.
YOU DO.
YOU SEE PEOPLE.
I SEE YOU.
AND?
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE JUMPED.
BUT THE PURPOSE
OF UNIVERSITY
IS TO FIND
A SUITABLE HUSBAND.
ROSE HAS ALREADY
DONE THAT.
LOOK, HERE COMES
THAT VULGAR
BROWN WOMAN.
QUICKLY, GET UP
BEFORE SHE SITS WITH US.
HELLO, GIRLS.
I WAS HOPING
I'D CATCH YOU AT TEA.
WE'RE AWFULLY SORRY
YOU MISSED IT.
THE COUNTESS AND I
WERE JUST OFF
TO TAKE THE AIR
ON THE BOAT DECK.
WHAT A LOVELY IDEA.
I NEED TO CATCH UP
ON MY GOSSIP.
Molly:
COUNTESS.
SO YOU'VE NOT YET
LIT THE LAST FOUR BOILERS?
NO, I DON'T SEE
THE NEED.
WE ARE MAKING
EXCELLENT TIME.
THE PRESS KNOWS
THE SIZE OF TITANIC.
NOW I WANT THEM TO MARVEL
AT HER SPEED.
WE MUST GIVE THEM
SOMETHING NEW TO PRINT.
THIS MAIDEN VOYAGE OF TITANIC
MUST MAKE HEADLINES.
MR. ISMAY...
I WOULD PREFER NOT
TO PUSH THE ENGINES
UNTIL THEY'VE BEEN
PROPERLY RUN IN.
OF COURSE
I'M JUST A PASSENGER.
I LEAVE IT
TO YOUR GOOD OFFICES
TO DECIDE WHAT'S BEST.
BUT WHAT A GLORIOUS END
TO YOUR FINAL CROSSING
IF WE WERE TO GET INTO NEW YORK
ON TUESDAY NIGHT
AND SURPRISE THEM ALL.
MAKE THE MORNING PAPERS.
RETIRE WITH A BANG,
EH, E.J.?
GOOD MAN.
WELL, AFTER THAT
I WORKED ON
A SQUID BOAT IN MONTEREY.
THEN I WENT
DOWN TO LOS ANGELES
TO THE PIER
IN SANTA MONICA
AND STARTED DOING
PORTRAITS THERE
FOR TEN CENTS APIECE.
WHY CAN'T I
BE LIKE YOU, JACK--
JUST HEAD OUT
FOR THE HORIZON
WHENEVER I FEEL LIKE IT?
SAY WE'LL GO THERE
SOMETIME TO THAT PIER
EVEN IF WE ONLY
EVER JUST TALK ABOUT IT.
NO, WE'LL DO IT.
WE'LL DRINK CHEAP BEER.
WE'LL RIDE ON THE ROLLER COASTER
TILL WE THROW UP.
THEN WE'LL RIDE
HORSES ON THE BEACH
RIGHT IN THE SURF.
NOW, BUT YOU'LL
HAVE TO DO IT
LIKE A REAL COWBOY.
NONE OF THAT
SIDESADDLE STUFF.
YOU MEAN,
ONE LEG ON EACH SIDE?
YEAH.
CAN YOU SHOW ME?
SURE... IF YOU LIKE.
TEACH ME TO RIDE
LIKE A MAN.
AND CHEW TOBACCO
AND SPIT LIKE A MAN.
THEY DIDN'T TEACH YOU THAT
IN FINISHING SCHOOL?
NO.
WELL, COME ON,
I'LL SHOW YOU.
LET'S DO IT.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW--
COME ON.
JACK, NO!
WAIT, JACK.
NO, JACK.
I COULDN'T
POSSIBLY, JACK.
WATCH CLOSELY.
THAT'S DISGUSTING!
ALL RIGHT, YOUR TURN.
THAT WAS PITIFUL!
COME ON, YOU REALLY GOT
TO HAWK IT BACK, YOU KNOW?
GET SOME LEVERAGE TO IT.
USE YOUR ARMS,
ARC YOUR NECK.
SEE THE RANGE
ON THAT THING?
MM-HMM.
Jack:
OKAY, GO.
THAT WAS BETTER--
YOU GOT TO WORK ON IT.
REALLY?
REALLY TRY
AND HAWK IT UP
AND GET SOME BODY
TO IT, YOU KNOW?
YOU GOT TO...
MOTHER.
MAY I INTRODUCE JACK DAWSON?
CHARMED, I'M SURE.
THE OTHERS WERE GRACIOUS
AND CURIOUS
ABOUT THE MAN
WHO HAD SAVED MY LIFE
BUT MY MOTHER LOOKED AT HIM
LIKE AN INSECT--
A DANGEROUS INSECT
WHICH MUST BE SQUASHED QUICKLY.
WELL, JACK, SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE A GOOD MAN TO HAVE AROUND
IN A STICKY SPOT.
WHY DO THEY ALWAYS INSIST
ON ANNOUNCING DINNER
LIKE A DAMN CAVALRY CHARGE?
SHALL WE GO DRESS, MOTHER?
SEE YOU
AT DINNER, JACK.
UH, SON?
SON!
DO YOU HAVE THE SLIGHTEST
COMPREHENSION WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
NOT REALLY.
WELL, YOU'RE ABOUT TO GO
INTO THE SNAKEPIT.
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING TO WEAR?
I FIGURED.
COME ON.
I WAS RIGHT.
YOU AND MY SON
ARE JUST ABOUT
THE SAME SIZE.
PRETTY CLOSE.
YOU SHINE UP LIKE A NEW PENNY.
GOOD EVENING, SIR.
GOOD EVENING.
Man:
HELLO.
Cal:
DO YOU KNOW
THAT THERE ARE
SEVERAL THOUSAND TONS
OF HOCKLEY STEEL
IN THIS VERY SHIP?
Ruth:
HMM... WHICH PART?
Cal:
ALL THE RIGHT ONES,
OF COURSE.
THEN WE'LL KNOW WHO
TO HOLD ACCOUNTABLE
IF THERE'S A PROBLEM.
WHERE'S MY DAUGHTER?
OH, SHE'LL BE ALONG.
THERE IS THE COUNTESS.
HELLO, MY DEAR.
GOOD EVENING, CAL.
Cal:
SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I SAW THAT
IN A NICKELODEON ONCE
AND I ALWAYS
WANTED TO DO IT.
Ruth:
I'LL SEE
YOU AT DINNER.
DARLING?
SURELY YOU
REMEMBER MR. DAWSON.
DAWSON?
WELL, IT'S AMAZING.
YOU COULD ALMOST PASS
FOR A GENTLEMAN.
ALMOST.
EXTRAORDINARY.
Ruth:
MY DEAR, IT'S
DELIGHTFUL TO SEE YOU.
WHAT A REMARKABLE
VOYAGE THIS IS.
IT'S MAD, ISN'T IT?
Ruth:
I LOVE YOUR PERFUME.
THERE'S THE
COUNTESS OF ROTHES.
AND, UM... THAT'S
JOHN JACOB ASTOR--
THE RICHEST MAN ON THE SHIP.
HIS LITTLE WIFEY THERE,
MADELEINE, IS MY AGE
AND IN A DELICATE CONDITION.
SEE HOW SHE'S
TRYING TO HIDE IT?
QUITE THE SCANDAL.
HMM.
AND THAT'S BENJAMIN
GUGGENHEIM
AND HIS MISTRESS
MADAME AUBERT.
MRS. GUGGENHEIM
IS AT HOME
WITH THE CHILDREN,
OF COURSE.
AND OVER HERE
WE HAVE
SIR COSMO AND
LUCILLE LADY DUFF-GORDON.
SHE DESIGNS NAUGHTY LINGERIE,
AMONG HER MANY TALENTS.
VERY POPULAR WITH THE ROYALS.
CONGRATULATIONS, HOCKLEY.
SHE'S SPLENDID.
WHY, THANK YOU.
CARE TO ESCORT
A LADY TO DINNER?
CERTAINLY.
SWEET PEA?
Cal:
SWEET PEA.
AIN'T NOTHIN' TO IT,
IS THERE, JACK?
REMEMBER, THEY
LOVE MONEY
SO JUST PRETEND LIKE
YOU OWN A GOLD MINE
AND YOU'RE
IN THE CLUB.
HEY, ASTOR!
WELL, HELLO, MOLLY.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
J.J., MADELEINE
I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET JACK DAWSON.
HOW DO YOU DO?
PLEASURE.
HELLO, JACK.
ARE YOU OF THE BOSTON DAWSONS?
NO-- THE CHIPPEWA FALLS
DAWSONS, ACTUALLY.
OH, YES... YES.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN NERVOUS,
BUT HE NEVER FALTERED.
THEY ASSUMED
HE WAS ONE OF THEM--
HEIR TO A RAILROAD FORTUNE,
PERHAPS.
NEW MONEY, OBVIOUSLY,
BUT STILL A MEMBER OF THE CLUB.
MOTHER, OF COURSE,
COULD ALWAYS BE COUNTED UPON.
TELL US OF THE ACCOMMODATIONS
IN STEERAGE, MR. DAWSON.
I HEAR THEY'RE QUITE GOOD
ON THIS SHIP.
THE BEST I'VE SEEN, MA'AM.
HARDLY ANY RATS.
MR. DAWSON
IS JOINING US
FROM THE THIRD CLASS.
HE WAS OF
SOME ASSISTANCE
TO MY FIANCEE
LAST NIGHT.
IT TURNS OUT
THAT MR. DAWSON
IS QUITE A FINE ARTIST.
HE WAS KIND
ENOUGH TO SHOW ME
SOME OF HIS WORK TODAY.
ROSE AND I
DIFFER SOMEWHAT
IN OUR DEFINITION
OF FINE ART.
NOT TO IMPUGN
YOUR WORK, SIR.
Ismay:
SHE MAY BE MINE ON PAPER
BUT IN THE EYES OF GOD,
SHE BELONGS TO THOMAS ANDREWS.
ARE THESE ALL FOR ME?
JUST START
FROM THE OUTSIDE
AND WORK YOUR WAY IN.
HE KNOWS EVERY RIVET
IN HER, DON'T YOU, THOMAS?
Andrews:
INDEED.
YOUR SHIP IS A WONDER,
MR. ANDREWS, TRULY.
THANK YOU, ROSE.
AND HOW DO YOU TAKE
YOUR CAVIAR, SIR?
NO CAVIAR FOR ME, THANKS.
NEVER DID LIKE IT MUCH.
AND WHERE, EXACTLY,
DO YOU LIVE, MR. DAWSON?
WELL, RIGHT NOW, MY ADDRESS
IS THE R.M.S. TITANIC.
AFTER THAT,
I'M ON GOD'S GOOD HUMOR.
AND HOW IS IT YOU HAVE
MEANS TO TRAVEL?
I WORK MY WAY
FROM PLACE TO PLACE--
YOU KNOW,
TRAMP STEAMERS AND SUCH.
BUT I WON MY TICKET
ON TITANIC HERE
AT A LUCKY HAND
AT POKER.
A VERY LUCKY HAND.
ALL LIFE IS A GAME OF LUCK.
MMM.
A REAL MAN MAKES
HIS OWN LUCK, ARCHIE.
RIGHT, DAWSON?
MMM.
AND YOU FIND THAT SORT
OF ROOTLESS EXISTENCE
APPEALING, DO YOU?
WELL, YES, MA'AM, I DO.
I MEAN...
GOT EVERYTHING I NEED
RIGHT HERE WITH ME.
GOT AIR IN MY LUNGS
AND A FEW BLANK SHEETS OF PAPER.
I MEAN, I LOVE WAKING
UP IN THE MORNING
NOT KNOWING
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
OR WHO I'M GOING TO MEET,
WHERE I'M GOING TO WIND UP.
JUST THE OTHER NIGHT,
I WAS SLEEPING UNDER A BRIDGE
AND NOW HERE I AM ON
THE GRANDEST SHIP IN THE WORLD
HAVING CHAMPAGNE
WITH YOU FINE PEOPLE.
I'LL TAKE SOME MORE OF THAT.
I FIGURE LIFE'S A GIFT
AND I DON'T INTEND
ON WASTING IT.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT HAND
YOU'RE GOING TO GET DEALT NEXT.
YOU LEARN TO TAKE LIFE
AS IT COMES AT YOU--
HERE YOU GO, CAL.
TO MAKE EACH DAY COUNT.
WELL SAID, JACK.
HEAR, HEAR!
TO MAKING IT COUNT.
All:
Archie:
BRAVO.
MR. BROWN HAD NO IDEA I'D HIDDEN
THE MONEY IN THE STOVE.
SO HE COMES HOME
DRUNK AS A PIG, CELEBRATING
AND HE LIGHTS A FIRE.
NEXT IT'LL BE BRANDIES
IN THE SMOKING ROOM.
Archie:
WELL...
JOIN ME IN A BRANDY, GENTLEMEN?
NOW THEY RETREAT
INTO A CLOUD OF SMOKE
AND CONGRATULATE EACH OTHER ON
BEING MASTERS OF THE UNIVERSE.
LADIES, THANK YOU FOR THE
PLEASURE OF YOUR COMPANY.
ROSE, MAY I ESCORT YOU
BACK TO THE CABIN?
NO, I'LL STAY HERE.
HERE YOU GO, MOLLY.
Archie:
JOINING US, DAWSON?
YOU DON'T WANT
TO STAY OUT HERE
WITH THE WOMEN, DO YOU?
NO, THANKS.
I'VE GOT TO BE
HEADING BACK.
AH.
PROBABLY BEST.
IT'LL BE ALL BUSINESS
AND POLITICS
THAT SORT OF THING--
WOULDN'T INTEREST YOU.
BUT DAWSON...
GOOD OF YOU TO COME.
JACK, MUST YOU GO?
TIME FOR ME TO GO ROW
WITH THE OTHER SLAVES.
GOOD NIGHT, ROSE.
SO YOU WANT TO GO
TO A REAL PARTY?
IS OKAY I PUT
MY HAND HERE.
OKAY.
TALLA FRIKKEN SVENSKA?
WHAT?
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
HEY...!
BRAVO, BRAVO!
THANK YOU.
COME ON, GUYS,
LET'S GO!
HO!
I'M GOING TO DANCE
WITH HER NOW, ALL RIGHT?
COME ON.
WHAT?
COME WITH ME.
WHAT? JACK...
JACK, WAIT!
I CAN'T DO THIS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
GET A LITTLE BIT CLOSER.
LIKE THIS.
YOU'RE STILL MY
BEST GIRL, CORA.
I DON'T
KNOW THE STEPS.
NEITHER DO I.
JUST GO WITH IT.
DON'T THINK.
HEY.
WAIT, JACK, JACK!
WAIT! STOP, JACK!
BA-BA-BA.
Rose:
WAIT!
HEY... HEY!
Jack:
YEAH!
JACK... NO!
WHAAA...
...JURISDICTION
OF THE SHERMAN ACT
SO MY LAWYERS
WILL ARGUE.
THAT'S WHAT
ROCKEFELLER SAID
BUT THE SUPREME COURT
IS NOT SWALLOWING IT.
WHAT?
YOU THINK
A FIRST-CLASS GIRL
CAN'T DRINK?
GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
TWO OUT OF THREE,
TWO OUT OF THREE.
SO...
YOU THINK YOU'RE
BIG, TOUGH MEN?
LET'S SEE YOU DO THIS.
HOLD THIS FOR ME, JACK.
HOLD IT UP.
OW!
JESUS, MARY
AND JOSEPH!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I HAVEN'T DONE
THAT IN YEARS.
GO SEE MAGGIE, LADS.
GIVE HER THE HOLLEY!
LET'S GO!
Musicians:
HO!
COFFEE, SIR?
I HAD HOPED YOU WOULD
COME TO ME LAST NIGHT.
I WAS TIRED.
YOUR EXERTIONS BELOW DECKS
WERE NO DOUBT EXHAUSTING.
I SEE YOU HAD THAT UNDERTAKER
OF A MANSERVANT FOLLOW ME.
HOW TYPICAL.
YOU WILL NEVER BEHAVE
LIKE THAT AGAIN, ROSE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I'M NOT A FOREMAN
IN ONE OF YOUR MILLS
THAT YOU CAN COMMAND.
I'M YOUR FIANCEE.
MY FIANCEE?
MY FIANCEE?!!
YES, YOU ARE,
AND MY WIFE!
MY WIFE IN PRACTICE
IF NOT YET BY LAW
SO YOU WILL HONOR ME.
YOU WILL HONOR ME THE
WAY A WIFE IS REQUIRED
TO HONOR A HUSBAND
BECAUSE I WILL NOT BE
MADE OUT A FOOL, ROSE.
IS THIS IN
ANY WAY UNCLEAR?
NO.
GOOD.
EXCUSE ME.
MISS ROSE!
WE HAD
A LITTLE... ACCIDENT.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
MISS ROSE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, TRUDY.
LET ME HELP YOU.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, MISS.
TEA, TRUDY.
YES, MA'AM.
YOU'RE NOT TO SEE
THAT BOY AGAIN
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
ROSE, I FORBID IT.
OH, STOP IT, MOTHER.
YOU'LL GIVE YOURSELF
A NOSEBLEED.
THIS IS NOT A GAME.
OUR SITUATION
IS PRECARIOUS.
YOU KNOW
THE MONEY'S GONE.
OF COURSE
I KNOW IT'S GONE.
YOU REMIND ME EVERY DAY.
YOUR FATHER LEFT US
NOTHING BUT A LEGACY
OF BAD DEBTS
HIDDEN BY A GOOD NAME.
THAT NAME IS THE ONLY
CARD WE HAVE TO PLAY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
IT IS A FINE MATCH
WITH HOCKLEY.
IT WILL ENSURE
OUR SURVIVAL.
HOW CAN YOU PUT
THIS ON MY SHOULDERS?
WHY ARE YOU
BEING SO SELFISH?
I'M BEING SELFISH?
DO YOU WANT TO SEE ME
WORKING AS A SEAMSTRESS?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
TO SEE OUR FINE THINGS
SOLD AT AUCTION?
OUR MEMORIES
SCATTERED TO THE WINDS?
IT'S SO UNFAIR.
OF COURSE IT'S UNFAIR.
WE'RE WOMEN.
OUR CHOICES
ARE NEVER EASY.
HMM?
Congregation:
♪ PROTECT THEM BY
THY GUARDIAN HAND ♪
♪ FROM EVERY PERIL
ON THE LAND. ♪
♪ O SPIRIT,
WHOM THE FATHER SENT ♪
♪ TO SPREAD ACROSS
THE FIRMAMENT ♪
♪ O WIND OF HEAVEN,
BY THY MIGHT ♪
♪ SAVE ALL WHO DARE
THE EAGLE'S FLIGHT ♪
♪ AND KEEP THEM
BY THY WATCHFUL... ♪
HELLO, MR. ANDREWS.
HELLO, JACK.
SIR...
I JUST NEED TO
TALK TO SOMEBODY
FOR A SECOND.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE IN HERE.
♪ ...FIRE AND FOE ♪
♪ PROTECT THEM... ♪
I WAS JUST
HERE LAST NIGHT.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ME?
NO, I'M
AFRAID I DON'T.
NOW, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TURN AROUND.
HE'LL TELL YOU.
I JUST...
I JUST NEED...
MR. HOCKLEY
AND MRS. DEWITT BUKATER
CONTINUE TO BE APPRECIATIVE
OF YOUR ASSISTANCE.
THEY ASKED ME TO, UH...
GIVE YOU THIS IN GRATITUDE.
I DON'T WANT YOUR MONEY.
PLEASE, I JUST...
AND ALSO TO REMIND YOU
THAT YOU HOLD
A THIRD-CLASS TICKET
AND THAT YOUR
PRESENCE HERE
IS NO LONGER
APPROPRIATE.
PLEASE, I JUST WANT
TO SPEAK TO ROSE FOR...
GENTLEMEN,
WILL YOU PLEASE SEE
THAT MR. DAWSON GETS
BACK TO WHERE HE BELONGS
AND THAT HE STAYS THERE?
YES, SIR.
COME ALONG,
YOU.
♪ OH, HEAR US
WHEN WE CRY TO THEE ♪
♪ FOR THOSE IN PERIL
ON THE SEA. ♪
Ruth:
AND WHY DO YOU HAVE
TWO STEERING WHEELS?
WE REALLY ONLY USE
THIS NEAR SHORE.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
ANOTHER ICE WARNING.
THIS ONE'S FROM
THE NOORDAM.
THANK YOU, SPARKS.
OH, NOT TO WORRY.
QUITE NORMAL
FOR THIS TIME OF YEAR.
IN FACT,
WE'RE SPEEDING UP.
I'VE JUST ORDERED
THE LAST BOILERS LIT.
Man:
OKAY, SON,
WIND IT UP TIGHT
LIKE I SHOWED YOU.
OKAY, NOW, LET IT GO.
WAS GOOD,
WASN'T IT?
QUITE NICE.
THAT'S
EXCELLENT, SON.
Rose:
MR. ANDREWS,
FORGIVE ME...
I DID THE SUM
IN MY HEAD
AND WITH THE NUMBER
OF LIFEBOATS
TIMES THE CAPACITY
YOU MENTIONED
FORGIVE ME, BUT IT SEEMS
THAT THERE ARE NOT ENOUGH
FOR EVERYONE ABOARD.
ABOUT HALF, ACTUALLY.
ROSE, YOU MISS
NOTHING, DO YOU?
IN FACT, I PUT IN
THESE NEW TYPE DAVITS
WHICH CAN TAKE AN
EXTRA ROW OF BOATS
INSIDE THIS ONE
BUT IT WAS
THOUGHT BY SOME
THAT THE DECK WOULD
LOOK TOO CLUTTERED
SO I WAS
OVERRULED.
WASTE OF DECK SPACE
AS IT IS
ON AN UNSINKABLE SHIP.
SLEEP SOUNDLY,
YOUNG ROSE.
I HAVE BUILT YOU
A GOOD SHIP
STRONG AND TRUE.
SHE'S ALL THE LIFEBOAT
YOU NEED.
JUST KEEP
HEADING AFT.
THE NEXT STOP WILL BE
THE ENGINE ROOM.
COME ON.
JACK, THIS IS
IMPOSSIBLE.
I CAN'T SEE YOU.
I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
NO, JACK, NO.
JACK, I'M ENGAGED.
I'M MARRYING CAL.
I LOVE CAL.
ROSE, YOU'RE NO PICNIC.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE A SPOILED
LITTLE BRAT, EVEN
BUT UNDER THAT
YOU'RE THE MOST
AMAZINGLY ASTOUNDING
WONDERFUL GIRL-- WOMAN--
THAT I'VE EVER
KNOWN AND...
JACK, I...
NO, LET ME TRY
AND GET THIS OUT.
YOU'RE, YOU'RE AMA...
I'M NOT AN IDIOT.
I KNOW HOW
THE WORLD WORKS.
I'VE GOT TEN BUCKS
IN MY POCKET.
I HAVE NOTHING TO OFFER
YOU AND I KNOW THAT.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT I'M TOO
INVOLVED NOW.
YOU JUMP, I JUMP,
REMEMBER?
I CAN'T TURN AWAY
WITHOUT KNOWING
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL THAT I WANT.
WELL, I'M FINE.
I'LL BE FINE, REALLY.
REALLY?
I DON'T THINK SO.
THEY'VE GOT
YOU TRAPPED, ROSE
AND YOU'RE GOING TO DIE
IF YOU DON'T BREAK FREE--
MAYBE NOT RIGHT AWAY
BECAUSE YOU'RE
STRONG, BUT...
SOONER OR LATER
THAT FIRE THAT I LOVE
ABOUT YOU, ROSE...
THAT FIRE IS GOING
TO BURN OUT.
IT'S NOT UP TO YOU
TO SAVE ME, JACK.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
ONLY YOU CAN DO THAT.
I'M GOING BACK.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
Countess:
TELL LUCILLE ABOUT
THE DISASTER YOU HAD
WITH THE STATIONER'S.
WELL, OF COURSE,
THE INVITATIONS HAD
TO BE SENT BACK TWICE.
OH, MY DEAR!
AND THE DREADFUL
BRIDESMAIDS' GOWNS--
LET ME TELL YOU
WHAT AN ODYSSEY
THAT HAS BEEN.
ROSE DECIDED
SHE WANTED LAVENDER.
SHE KNOWS
I DETEST THE COLOR
SO SHE DID IT
ONLY TO SPITE ME.
Lucille:
IF ONLY YOU'D
COME TO ME SOONER.
RUTH SAW
SOME OF MY DESIGNS
IN "LA MODE ILLUSTREE."
THEY WERE FOR
THE TROUSSEAU
OF THE DUCHESS
OF MALBOROUGH'S
YOUNGEST DAUGHTER.
THEY WERE
QUITE CHARMING
BUT I THINK
YOU'LL AGREE, MY DEAR
THAT TOGETHER
WE'VE CREATED
SOMETHING OF A PHOENIX
FROM THE ASHES.
HELLO, JACK.
I CHANGED MY MIND.
THEY SAID YOU MIGHT BE...
SHH...
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
NOW CLOSE YOUR EYES.
GO ON.
STEP UP.
NOW HOLD ON
TO THE RAILING.
KEEP YOUR EYES CLOSED,
DON'T PEEK.
I'M NOT.
STEP UP ONTO THE RAIL.
HOLD ON...
HOLD ON.
KEEP YOUR EYES
CLOSED.
DO YOU TRUST ME?
I TRUST YOU.
ALL RIGHT...
OPEN YOUR EYES.
I'M FLYING!
JACK!
♪ COME, JOSEPHINE,
MY FLYING MACHINE ♪
♪ GOING UP, SHE GOES,
UP, SHE GOES... ♪
THAT WAS THE LAST TIME TITANIC
EVER SAW DAYLIGHT.
SO WE'RE UP TO DUSK
THE NIGHT OF THE SINKING.
SIX HOURS TO GO.
INCREDIBLE.
THERE'S SMITH
AND HE'S STANDING THERE
AND HE'S GOT
THE ICEBERG WARNING
IN HIS FUCKING HAND--
EXCUSE ME-- HIS HAND
AND HE'S ORDERING
MORE SPEED.
26 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE
WORKING AGAINST HIM.
HE FIGURES ANYTHING BIG
ENOUGH TO SINK THE SHIP
THEY'RE GOING TO SEE
IN TIME TO TURN
BUT THE SHIP'S TOO BIG
WITH TOO SMALL A RUDDER.
DOESN'T CORNER
WORTH A DAMN.
EVERYTHING HE KNOWS
IS WRONG.
IT'S QUITE PROPER,
I ASSURE YOU.
THIS IS
THE SITTING ROOM.
WILL THIS LIGHT DO?
WHAT?
DON'T ARTISTS NEED GOOD LIGHT?
THAT IS TRUE, BUT I'M NOT
USED TO WORKING
IN SUCH HORRIBLE
CONDITIONS.
MONET!
DO YOU KNOW
HIS WORK?
OF COURSE.
LOOK AT HIS USE OF COLOR HERE.
ISN'T HE GREAT?
I KNOW,
IT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
CAL INSISTS ON CARTING
THIS HIDEOUS THING
EVERYWHERE.
SHOULD WE BE EXPECTING HIM
ANYTIME SOON?
NOT AS LONG AS
THE CIGARS AND
BRANDY HOLD OUT.
THAT'S NICE.
WHAT IS IT,
A SAPPHIRE?
A DIAMOND,
A VERY RARE DIAMOND.
JACK, I WANT YOU
TO DRAW ME
LIKE ONE OF YOUR
FRENCH GIRLS...
WEARING THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
WEARING ONLY THIS.
THE LAST THING I NEED
IS ANOTHER PICTURE OF ME
LOOKING LIKE A PORCELAIN DOLL.
AS A PAYING CUSTOMER...
I EXPECT TO GET WHAT I WANT.
OVER ON THE BED...
THE COUCH.
GO... LIE DOWN.
TELL ME WHEN
IT LOOKS RIGHT.
PUT YOUR ARM BACK
THE WAY IT WAS.
RIGHT.
PUT THAT OTHER ARM UP, THAT HAND
RIGHT BY YOUR FACE THERE.
RIGHT.
NOW, HEAD DOWN...
EYES TO ME,
KEEP THEM ON ME.
AND TRY TO STAY STILL.
SO SERIOUS.
I BELIEVE
YOU ARE BLUSHING,
MR. BIG ARTISTE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
MONSIEUR MONET BLUSHING.
HE DOES LANDSCAPES.
JUST RELAX
YOUR FACE.
SORRY.
NO LAUGHING.
MY HEART WAS POUNDING
THE WHOLE TIME.
IT WAS THE MOST EROTIC MOMENT
OF MY LIFE.
UP UNTIL THEN, AT LEAST.
SO WHAT
HAPPENED NEXT?
YOU MEAN, DID WE DO IT?
SORRY, TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
MR. BODINE.
JACK WAS VERY PROFESSIONAL.
THANK YOU.
WHAT YOU
DOING?
WILL YOU PUT THIS BACK
IN THE SAFE FOR ME?
MM-HMM.
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME?
NONE OF THE STEWARDS
HAVE SEEN HER.
THIS IS ABSURD.
IT'S A SHIP, THERE'S ONLY
SO MANY PLACES SHE COULD BE.
LOVEJOY, FIND HER.
CLEAR.
YES.
I DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER SEEN
SUCH A FLAT CALM.
LIKE A MILL POND.
NOT A BREATH OF WIND.
IT WILL MAKE THE BERGS
HARDER TO SEE
WITH NO BREAKING WATER
AT THE BASE.
HMM.
WELL, I'M OFF.
MAINTAIN SPEED
AND HEADING
MR. LIGHTOLLER.
YES, SIR.
IT'S GETTING COLD.
YOU LOOK NICE.
Lovejoy:
MISS ROSE?
MY DRAWINGS!
COME ON!
NO, WAIT, WAIT!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
GO, GO!
DOWN, DOWN!
Rose:
QUICKLY, QUICKLY!
BYE!
SORRY!
IT'S ALL RIGHT!
PRETTY TOUGH FOR
A VALET, THIS FELLOW.
SEEMS MORE LIKE A COP.
I THINK HE WAS.
Jack:
OH, SHIT.
NO, OVER HERE!
QUICK!
NOW WHAT?!
WHAT?!
HOLD UP!
WHAT'RE YOU TWO
DOING DOWN HERE?
YOU SHOULDN'T
BE DOWN HERE!
IT COULD BE DANGEROUS!
Jack:
CARRY ON!
DON'T MIND US, YOU'RE
DOING A GREAT JOB!
KEEP UP
THE GOOD WORK!
AH, LOOK WHAT
WE HAVE HERE, HUH?
THANK YOU.
WHERE TO, MISS?
TO THE STARS.
YOU NERVOUS?
NO.
PUT YOUR HANDS ON ME, JACK.
Crewman:
GOD, IT'S
BLOODY COLD.
YOU KNOW, I CAN SMELL
ICE, YOU KNOW...
WHEN IT'S NEAR.
BOLLOCKS.
BUT I CAN,
ALL RIGHT!
Murdoch:
DID YOU EVER FIND
THOSE BINOCULARS
FOR THE LOOKOUTS?
HAVEN'T SEEN THEM
SINCE SOUTHAMPTON.
WELL, I'LL BE
ON MY ROUNDS.
CHEERIO.
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THEY RAN
DOWN THERE.
RIGHT.
Lovejoy:
ANYTHING MISSING?
I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
GOTCHA!
DID YOU SEE
THOSE GUYS' FACES?
DID YOU SEE THE...?
WHEN THE SHIP DOCKS...
I'M GETTING OFF
WITH YOU.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I KNOW.
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
THAT'S WHY I TRUST IT.
OH, YES...
HERE, LOOK AT THIS.
OH, LOOK AT THAT
WOULD YOU?
THEY'RE A BIT WARMER
THAN WE ARE.
WELL, IF THAT'S
WHAT IT TAKES
FOR US TO GET WARMER
I'D RATHER NOT
IF IT'S ALL
THE SAME TO YOU.
BUGGER ME!
PICK UP, YOU BASTARDS.
Is there anyone there?
YES, WHAT DO YOU SEE?
ICEBERG! RIGHT AHEAD!
THANK YOU.
HARD TO STARBOARD!
Crewman:
TURN, TURN! STEADY!
FULL ASTERN!
HARD OVER.
HELM'S HARD OVER, SIR.
GO, LADS! GO!
SHUT ALL THE DAMPERS!
SHUT THEM!
HOLD IT.
HOLD IT!
NOW, ENGAGE THE
REVERSING ENGINE!
WHY AREN'T THEY TURNING?!
IS IT HARD OVER?!
Crewman:
IT IS, YES,
SIR, HARD OVER!
COME ON... COME ON... COME ON...
TURN.
YES...
IT'S GOING TO HIT!
JESUS CHRIST.
JESUS...
HARD TO PORT!
Crewman:
HARD TO THE PORT!
GET BACK!
COME ON, LET'S GO!
GET OUT THE DOOR!
THEY'RE CLOSING THE DOORS!
GET OUT!
GET OUT! GET OUT!
GET OUT
THE DOOR!
GO ON!
COME ON, LADS!
GO, LADS, GO!
GET OUT!
:
OH, MY GOD...
THAT WAS A CLOSE SHAVE,
WEREN'T IT?
SMELL ICE, CAN YOU?
BLEEDING CHRIST.
NOTE THE TIME
AND ENTER IT IN THE LOG.
WHAT WAS THAT, MR. MURDOCH?
AN ICEBERG, SIR.
I PUT HER HARD
TO STARBOARD
AND RAN THE ENGINES
FULL ASTERN
BUT IT WAS TOO CLOSE.
I TRIED TO PORT ROUND IT
BUT SHE HIT AND THE...
CLOSE THE
WATERTIGHT DOORS.
Murdoch:
THE DOORS
ARE CLOSED, SIR.
ALL STOP.
Crewman:
AYE, SIR!
FIND THE CARPENTER.
GET HIM TO SOUND THE SHIP.
YES, SIR!
Fabrizio:
PORCA PUTTANA!
CHE CAZZO E?
COME ON, LET'S GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE!
COME ON, HURRY UP.
EXCUSE ME.
WHY HAVE THE
ENGINES STOPPED?
I FELT A SHUDDER.
I SHOULDN'T
WORRY, MADAM.
WE'VE LIKELY THROWN
A PROPELLER BLADE.
THAT'S THE SHUDDER YOU FELT.
MAY I BRING YOU ANYTHING?
NO, THANK YOU.
Man:
DID YOU SEE ANYTHING?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING
NOW, DO YOU?
IF THIS IS THE DIRECTION
THE RATS ARE GOING
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH
FOR ME.
Crewman:
PLEASE, SIR, PLEASE.
EVERYTHING'S
UNDER CONTROL.
YOU THERE.
SIR, THERE IS
NO EMERGENCY.
YES, THERE IS,
I HAVE BEEN ROBBED.
GET THE
MASTER-AT-ARMS.
NOW, YOU MORON!
YES, SIR.
HEY, YOU'RE GOING
TO MISS THE FUN.
DID YOU SEE WHAT HAPPEN?
NO, I MISSED IT.
APPARENTLY,
IT HIT OVER THERE.
Crewman:
BOILER ROOM SIX IS FLOODED
EIGHT FEET ABOVE THE PLATE
AND THE MAIL HOLD IS WORSE.
SHE'S ALL BUCKLED IN
IN THE FORWARD HOLD.
CAN YOU SHORE UP?
NOT UNLESS THE
PUMPS GET AHEAD.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE DAMAGE
IN THE MAIL HOLD?
NO, SHE'S
ALREADY UNDERWATER.
THIS IS BAD.
WE SHOULD TELL
MOTHER AND CAL.
I THINK THEY'RE
VERY GOOD, SIR.
DON'T TOUCH
ANYTHING.
I WANT THE ENTIRE ROOM
PHOTOGRAPHED.
Rose:
JUST KEEP
HOLDING MY HAND.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU, MISS.
Rose:
WELL, HERE WE GO.
SOMETHING SERIOUS
HAS HAPPENED.
YES, IT HAS...
INDEED. TWO THINGS DEAR TO ME
HAVE DISAPPEARED THIS EVENING.
NOW THAT ONE IS BACK
I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
WHERE TO FIND THE OTHER.
SEARCH HIM.
TAKE YOUR
COAT OFF, SIR.
NOW WHAT?
COME ON.
CAL, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF AN EMERGENCY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS THIS IT?
THAT'S IT.
THIS IS HORSESHIT!
DON'T YOU BELIEVE IT, ROSE.
DON'T!
HE COULDN'T HAVE.
OF COURSE HE COULD.
IT'S EASY ENOUGH
FOR A PROFESSIONAL.
BUT I WAS WITH HIM
THE WHOLE TIME.
THIS IS ABSURD.
PERHAPS HE DID IT
WHILE YOU
WERE PUTTING
YOUR CLOTHES
BACK ON, DEAR.
REAL SLICK CAL.
ROSE, THEY PUT IT IN MY POCKET.
SHUT UP.
IT ISN'T EVEN YOUR POCKET,
IS IT, SON?
PROPERTY OF A. L. RYERSON.
THAT WAS REPORTED
STOLEN TODAY.
I JUST BORROWED IT.
I WAS GOING
TO RETURN IT.
WE HAVE AN HONEST
THIEF HERE, DO WE?
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T
DO THIS, ROSE.
YOU KNOW IT--
DON'T YOU BELIEVE
THEM, ROSE.
YOU KNOW IT.
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T DO IT.
COME ON,
LET'S GO.
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T
DO IT, ROSE. ROSE!
COME ON, SON.
THERE'S A GOOD LAD.
COME ON.
YOU KNOW
I DIDN'T DO IT!
YOU KNOW ME!
Ismay:
MOST UNFORTUNATE, CAPTAIN.
WATER... 14 FEET ABOVE
THE KEEL IN TEN MINUTES--
IN THE FOREPEAK
IN ALL THREE HOLDS
AND IN BOILEROOM SIX.
THAT'S RIGHT, SIR.
WHEN CAN WE GET
UNDER WAY, DAMN IT?
THAT'S FIVE COMPARTMENTS.
SHE CAN STAY AFLOAT
WITH THE FIRST FOUR
COMPARTMENTS BREACHED
BUT NOT FIVE.
NOT FIVE.
AS SHE GOES DOWN
BY THE HEAD
THE WATER WILL SPILL
OVER THE TOPS
OF THE BULKHEADS
AT E DECK FROM
ONE TO THE NEXT.
BACK AND BACK.
THERE'S NO STOPPING IT.
THE PUMPS...
IF WE OPENED
THE DOORS...
THE PUMPS BUY YOU TIME,
BUT MINUTES ONLY.
FROM THIS MOMENT
NO MATTER WHAT WE DO
TITANIC WILL FOUNDER.
BUT THIS SHIP CAN'T SINK.
SHE'S MADE OF IRON, SIR.
I ASSURE YOU, SHE CAN...
AND SHE WILL.
IT IS A MATHEMATICAL CERTAINTY.
HOW MUCH TIME?
AN HOUR.
TWO AT MOST.
AND HOW MANY ABOARD,
MR. MURDOCH?
2,200 SOULS ON BOARD, SIR.
WELL, I BELIEVE YOU MAY GET
YOUR HEADLINES, MR. ISMAY.
OH, IT IS A LITTLE
SLUT, ISN'T IT?
WILL YOU LOOK AT ME
WHEN I'M TALKING TO YOU.
MR. HOCKLEY?
NOT NOW,
WE'RE BUSY.
SIR, I'VE BEEN TOLD
TO ASK YOU
TO PLEASE PUT ON
YOUR LIFEBELTS
AND COME UP TO THE...
I SAID NOT NOW.
I'M SORRY TO INCONVENIENCE YOU,
MR. HOCKLEY
BUT IT'S CAPTAIN'S ORDERS.
NOW, PLEASE, DRESS WARMLY.
IT'S QUITE COLD
OUT TONIGHT.
NOW, MAY I SUGGEST
TOPCOATS AND HATS.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
NOT TO WORRY, MISS.
I AM SURE IT'S
JUST A PRECAUTION.
EVERYBODY UP!
LIFEBELTS ON!
WHAT'S HE YELLING ABOUT?
EVERYBODY UP!
PUT YOUR LIFEBELTS ON!
WHAT'S THE RUCKUS?
JUST PUT
YOU LIFEBELTS ON!
Crewman:
C.Q.D.?
SIR?
THAT'S RIGHT-- C.Q.D.
THE DISTRESS CALL.
THAT'S OUR POSITION.
TELL WHOEVER RESPONDS
THAT WE'RE GOING DOWN
BY THE HEAD.
WE NEED
IMMEDIATE ASSISTANCE.
BLIMEY.
KEEP LOWERING!
MR. WILDE!
MR. WILDE, WHERE ARE
THE PASSENGERS?
WE MOVED THEM
BACK INSIDE.
IT'S TOO DAMN COLD
AND NOISY FOR THEM.
YOU THERE!
GET DOWN HERE AND
HELP WITH THESE LINES.
CARE FOR A DRINK, SIR?
Crewman:
PLEASE PUT YOUR LIFEBELTS ON.
HEY, SONNY, WHAT'S DOING?
YOU GOT US ALL
TRUSSED UP HERE
AND NOW WE'RE
COOLING OUR HEELS.
SORRY, MA'AM.
LET ME GO
AND FIND OUT.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY KNOWS
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON AROUND HERE.
IT'S THE GODDAMNED ENGLISH
DOING EVERYTHING
BY THE... BOOK.
THERE'S NO NEED FOR
LANGUAGE, MR. HOCKLEY.
GO BACK AND TURN
THE HEATERS ON IN OUR ROOMS.
I'D LIKE A CUP OF TEA
WHEN I RETURN.
YES, MA'AM.
MR. ANDREWS...
I SAW THE ICEBERG
AND I SEE IT
IN YOUR EYES.
PLEASE TELL ME THE TRUTH.
THE SHIP WILL SINK.
YOU'RE CERTAIN.
YES, IN AN HOUR
OR SO...
ALL THIS WILL BE
AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE ATLANTIC.
WHAT?
PLEASE, TELL ONLY
WHO YOU MUST.
I DON'T WANT TO
BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR A PANIC
AND GET TO A BOAT
QUICKLY, DON'T WAIT.
YOU REMEMBER
WHAT I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE BOATS?
YES...
I UNDERSTAND.
OVER HERE, SIR.
SIR, THEY NEED YOU
UP IN THE SECOND-CLASS
PURSER'S OFFICE.
THERE'S A BIG MOB
UP THERE.
GO ON, I'LL KEEP
AN EYE ON HIM.
AYE, RIGHT.
SIR!
CARPATHIA SAYS
THEY'RE MAKING
17 KNOTS.
FULL STEAM FOR THEM, SIR.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S RESPONDING?
THE ONLY ONE CLOSE, SIR.
SHE SAYS THEY CAN
BE HERE IN FOUR HOURS.
FOUR HOURS?
THANK YOU, BRIDE.
MY GOD.
SIR!
WE ARE SWUNG OUT
AND READY, SIR.
HADN'T WE BETTER GET
THE WOMEN AND CHILDREN
INTO THE BOAT, SIR?
YES, WE DO.
SIR?
WOMEN AND CHILDREN FIRST.
YES...
YES, SIR.
Crewman:
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE!
STEP THIS WAY, PLEASE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
COME TOWARDS ME.
THANK YOU.
GOOD.
FOR THE TIME BEING
I SHALL REQUIRE
ONLY WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
Man:
RIGHT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
LIKE THE CAPTAIN SAID
NICE AND CHEERY
SO THERE'S NO PANIC.
"WEDDING DANCE."
LIFEBELTS ON!
HERE, PUT YOUR LIFEBELTS ON.
PUT YOUR LIFEBELTS ON.
HERE, PUT YOUR LIFEBELT ON.
HERE, COME ON, HERE.
Crewman:
IT ISN'T TIME TO GO UP
TO THE BOATS YET.
PLEASE STAY CALM.
LOOK, PLEASE,
MAKE SURE EVERYBODY
YOU'VE GOT
YOUR LIFEBELTS ON
AND GENTLEMEN, ALLOW
THE WOMEN AND CHILDREN
THROUGH TO THE FRONT.
WHAT ARE WE DOING, MOMMY?
WE'RE JUST WAITING, DEAR.
WHEN THEY'RE FINISHED PUTTING
THE FIRST-CLASS
PEOPLE IN THE BOATS
THEY'LL START WITH US
AND WE'LL WANT TO BE
ALL READY, WON'T WE?
GO AND GET SOME HELP.
LOWER AWAY!
LEFT AND RIGHT
TOGETHER!
STEADY!
BOTH SIDES TOGETHER!
HOLD THE LEFT SIDE!
RIGHT SIDE ONLY!
RIGHT SIDE DOWN!
LOWER AWAY TOGETHER!
STEADY, LADS!
YOU KNOW, I DO BELIEVE
THIS SHIP MAY SINK.
I'VE BEEN ASKED
TO GIVE YOU
THIS SMALL TOKEN
OF OUR APPRECIATION.
COMPLIMENTS OF
MR. CALEDON HOCKLEY.
COME ON, SISTER, YOU HEARD
THE MAN-- INTO THE BOAT.
ANY ROOM FOR
A GENTLEMAN,
GENTLEMEN?
Crewman:
ONLY WOMEN
AT THIS TIME, SIR.
WILL THE LIFEBOATS
BE SEATED
ACCORDING TO CLASS?
I HOPE THEY'RE
NOT TOO CROWDED.
OH, MOTHER...
SHUT UP!
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THE WATER IS FREEZING
AND THERE AREN'T ENOUGH BOATS.
NOT ENOUGH BY HALF.
HALF THE PEOPLE ON THIS SHIP
ARE GOING TO DIE.
NOT THE BETTER HALF.
COME ON, RUTH, GET IN THE BOAT.
FIRST-CLASS SEATS
ARE RIGHT UP HERE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A PITY
I DIDN'T
KEEP THAT DRAWING.
IT'LL BE WORTH
A LOT MORE BY MORNING.
YOU UNIMAGINABLE BASTARD.
Molly:
COME ON,
ROSE, DARLING.
THERE'S PLENTY
OF ROOM FOR YOU.
COME ON, ROSE.
YOU'RE NEXT, DARLING.
COME INTO
THE BOAT, ROSE.
COME.
ROSE...
GET INTO THE BOAT.
ROSE.
GOOD-BYE, MOTHER.
ROSE!
ROSE,
COME BACK HERE!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO HIM?!
TO BE A WHORE
TO A GUTTER RAT?
I'D RATHER BE HIS
WHORE THAN YOUR WIFE.
NO... NO!
I SAID NO!
Ruth:
ROSE!
PLEASE STOP!
Crewman:
AND LOWER AWAY!
ROSE!!
MAN THE TILLER!
NO, WAIT!
LOWER AWAY!
ROSE!
LOWER TOGETHER!
HELP!
CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME?
HELLO, HELP ME!
HELP ME!
CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME?
SOMEBODY HELP ME, PLEASE!
Rose:
MR. ANDREWS?
STEWARD, CHECK
THE STARBOARD CORRIDOR.
YES, MR. ANDREWS.
MADAM, PLEASE,
PUT ON A LIFEBELT.
GET TO THE BOAT DECK
IMMEDIATELY.
LUCY, FOR GOD'S SAKE,
PUT ON YOUR LIFEBELT.
SET A GOOD EXAMPLE.
YES, SIR.
ANYONE IN HERE?
MR. ANDREWS?
MR. ANDREWS,
THANK GOD.
WHERE WOULD THE MASTER-
AT-ARMS TAKE SOMEONE
UNDER ARREST?
WHAT? YOU HAVE TO GET
TO A BOAT RIGHT AWAY.
NO!
I'M DOING THIS WITH OR
WITHOUT YOUR HELP, SIR
BUT WITHOUT
WILL TAKE LONGER.
TAKE THE ELEVATOR
TO THE VERY BOTTOM.
GO TO THE LEFT
DOWN THE CREWMEN'S PASSAGE.
THEN GO RIGHT AND LEFT
AGAIN AT THE STAIRS.
YOU'LL COME TO
A LONG CORRIDOR.
THIS COULD BE BAD.
OH, SHIT.
OH, SHIT!
EXCUSE ME, THANK YOU.
Crewman:
THE LIFTS ARE CLOSED.
Woman:
I DO NOT CARE...
THE LIFTS ARE...
I'M SORRY, MISS,
BUT THE LIFTS ARE CLOSED.
I'M THROUGH BEING
POLITE, GODDAMN IT!
NOW TAKE ME DOWN!
E DECK.
COME ON.
OH, COME ON.
I'M GOING BACK UP!
NO!
NO, NO!
COME BACK!
I'M GOING BACK UP.
I'M GOING BACK UP!
CREW PASSAGE...
CREW PASSAGE.
JACK?
JACK?!
ROSE!
ROSE, I'M IN HERE!
I'M IN HERE.
JACK?!
ROSE!
JACK! JACK!
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
THAT GUY LOVEJOY
PUT IT IN MY POCKET.
I KNOW, I KNOW,
I KNOW, I KNOW.
LISTEN, ROSE, YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO FIND
A SPARE KEY, ALL RIGHT?
LOOK IN THAT CABINET
RIGHT THERE.
IT'S A LITTLE
SILVER ONE, ROSE.
THESE ARE ALL BRASS ONES!
CHECK RIGHT HERE, ROSE.
ROSE...
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
I DIDN'T DO IT?
I DIDN'T.
I JUST REALIZED I ALREADY KNEW.
KEEP LOOKING.
OH.
NO KEY.
THERE'S NO KEY!
ALL RIGHT,
ROSE, LISTEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GO FIND SOME HELP.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'LL JUST WAIT HERE.
HELLO, IS THERE ANYONE HERE?
HELLO?
IS THERE ANYBODY DOWN HERE?
WE NEED HELP! HELLO!
DAMN IT.
CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME?
PLEASE, HELLO!
HELLO!
OH, THANK GOD.
WAIT, PLEASE,
I NEED YOUR HELP.
THERE'S A MAN
BACK HERE AND...
WAIT!
HELLO?
AH, MISS, YOU SHOULDN'T
BE HERE, NOW.
PLEASE, I NEED
YOUR HELP.
THIS WAY, QUICKLY.
THERE IS A MAN DOWN HERE
AND HE IS TRAPPED.
PLEASE.
THERE'S NO NEED TO PANIC.
NO, I'M NOT PANICKING.
YOU'RE GOING THE WRONG WAY!
LET GO OF ME, LISTEN!
TO HELL WITH YOU.
OH!
OH, MY GOD...
JACK!
ROSE!
WILL THIS WORK?
I GUESS WE'LL FIND OUT.
COME ON.
WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT.
TRY A COUPLE PRACTICE SWINGS
OVER THERE.
GOOD, NOW TRY TO HIT
THE SAME MARK AGAIN, ROSE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
OKAY, THAT'S
ENOUGH PRACTICE.
COME ON, ROSE,
YOU CAN DO IT.
LISTEN, JUST HIT IT
REALLY HARD AND REALLY FAST.
WAIT, OPEN YOUR HANDS UP
A LITTLE MORE.
LIKE THAT?
RIGHT.
LISTEN, ROSE,
I TRUST YOU.
GO!
YOU DID IT!
COME ON, LET'S GO.
OH, SHIT, THIS IS COLD.
OH, SHIT!
SHIT, SHIT.
THIS IS THE WAY OUT.
WE HAVE TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY.
COME ON.
Tiller:
PULL.
PUT YOUR BACKS
INTO IT, PULL!
PULL!
NOW, THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T SEE EVERY DAY.
PULL!
Crewman:
WHAT'S THIS LUGGAGE DOING HERE?
GET RID OF IT, WE NEED THE ROOM.
KEEP CALM.
NO!
LOVEJOY.
SHE'S NOT ON
THE STARBOARD SIDE EITHER.
WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME
AND THIS
STRUTTING MARTINET
ISN'T LETTING
ANY MEN ON AT ALL.
THERE'S ONE ON
THE OTHER SIDE
LETTING MEN ON.
WELL, THEN,
THAT'S OUR PLAY.
WE'LL NEED SOME
INSURANCE FIRST.
COME ON.
THIS WAY.
ALL THE
WAY DOWN HERE.
Steward:
HERE!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY
FOR THAT, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S WHITE STAR LINE PROPERTY.
Both:
SHUT UP!
WILL YOU HOLD THE BOAT A MOMENT?
I JUST HAVE TO RUN
BACK TO MY ROOM...
SIT DOWN!
SHE'S THE LAST.
ALL RIGHT TO LOWER.
MR. LIGHTOLLER,
WHY ARE THE BOATS
BEING LAUNCHED
HALF FULL?
NOT NOW, MR. ANDREWS.
THERE, LOOK,
20 OR SO
IN A BOAT
BUILT FOR 65
AND I SAW ONE BOAT
WITH ONLY 12-- 12!
WELL, WE WEREN'T SURE
OF THE WEIGHT, MR. ANDREWS.
THESE BOATS MAY BUCKLE.
RUBBISH.
THEY WERE
TESTED IN BELFAST
WITH THE WEIGHT
OF 70 MEN!
NOW, FILL THESE BOATS,
MR. LIGHTOLLER
FOR GOD'S SAKE, MAN!
PLEASE, I NEED MORE WOMEN
AND CHILDREN, PLEASE.
Crewman:
GET BACK IN THERE.
THIS IS NOT AN EXIT.
YOU CAN'T KEEP US LOCKED
IN HERE LIKE ANIMALS.
THE SHIP'S BLOODY SINKING!
BRING FORWARD
THE WOMEN!
UNLOCK THE GATES.
WOMEN ONLY!
NO MEN!
GET BACK!
LOCK THE GATES!
GET THEM BACK
FROM THOSE GATES!
DON'T TOUCH THE GATES!
FOR GOD'S SAKE, MAN, THERE ARE
WOMEN AND CHILDREN DOWN HERE!
LET US UP SO WE
CAN HAVE A CHANCE!
GET BACK!
JACK!
TOMMY!
CAN WE GET OUT?
IT'S HOPELESS THAT WAY!
WHATEVER WE DO
WE'VE GOT TO DO IT FAST.
JACK!
FABRIZIO!
THE BOATS ARE ALL GONE.
THIS WHOLE PLACE
IS FLOODING.
THERE IS NIENTE
THIS WAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO
THIS WAY, ALL RIGHT?
COME ON.
I MAKE MY OWN LUCK.
SO DO I.
COME ON!
NO, COME ON,
LET'S GO THIS WAY.
THIS WAY.
Steward:
JUST GO BACK
TO THE MAIN STAIRWELL
AND EVERYTHING
WILL BE SORTED OUT THERE.
Man:
HELL, IT WILL.
IT WILL ALL GET
SORTED OUT BACK THERE.
GO BACK TO THE
MAIN STAIRWELL.
OPEN THE GATE.
GO BACK DOWN
THE MAIN STAIR.
OPEN THE GATE
RIGHT NOW!
GO BACK DOWN
THE MAIN STAIRWELL
LIKE I TOLD YOU.
GODDAMN IT!
SON OF A BITCH!
Man:
OPEN THE DAMN GATE!
OPEN IT!
FABRI, TOMMY,
GIVE ME A HAND HERE!
Rose:
MOVE ASIDE.
COME ON, PULL!
PULL! PULL!
MOVE ASIDE!
Steward:
PUT THAT DOWN.
MOVE ASIDE!
ONE!
TWO!
STOP THAT!
THREE!
AGAIN!
Jack:
LET'S GO!
LET'S GO, ROSE.
YOU CAN'T
GO UP THERE.
DO THIS!
Lightoller:
KEEP ORDER HERE.
BACK, BACK, BACK.
HOLD ON TO HER!
PULL HER IN!
GET BACK I SAY
OR I'LL SHOOT YOU ALL LIKE DOGS.
KEEP ORDER HERE!
KEEP ORDER, I SAY.
MR. LOWE, MAN THIS BOAT.
Lowe:
RIGHT, IS EVERYBODY
ALL RIGHT?
NOBODY PANIC.
Crewman:
STAY BACK!
WE'RE TOO LATE.
THERE ARE MORE BOATS
DOWN THE FRONT.
STAY WITH
THIS ONE-- MURDOCH.
HE SEEMS TO BE
QUITE PRACTICAL.
Lowe:
SIT DOWN!
STAY BACK, YOU LOT.
STAY BACK!
STAY BACK, THE LOT OF YOU!
IT'S STARTING
TO FALL APART.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
MR. MURDOCH?
MR. HOCKLEY...
YOU TWO,
WITH ME, NOW.
I'M A BUSINESSMAN,
AS YOU KNOW
AND I HAVE A BUSINESS
PROPOSITION FOR YOU.
Crewman:
EASY NOW.
ALL TOGETHER.
LOWER AWAY, LOWER AWAY.
Jack:
COME ON, ROSE.
THE BOATS ARE GONE!
COLONEL, ARE THERE
ANY BOATS ON THAT SIDE?
NO, MISS, BUT THERE
ARE A COUPLE OF BOATS
ALL THE WAY FORWARD.
THIS WAY, I'LL LEAD YOU.
WHAT'S THE USE?
NOBODY'S LISTENING
TO US ANYWAY.
WELL, THEY DON'T LISTEN TO US
AT DINNER EITHER.
COME ON, LET'S PLAY.
KEEP US WARM.
"ORPHEUS."
MUSIC TO DROWN BY.
NOW I KNOW
I'M IN FIRST CLASS.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
THEY'RE ALL
STILL AFT, SIR.
WE HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING
THEN, MR. MURDOCH?
WOMEN AND CHILDREN ONLY!
GET BACK!
STEP BACK, SIR.
COME THROUGH, MADAM.
THIS WAY.
STEP BACK, SIR.
YOU'D BETTER CHECK
THE OTHER SIDE.
GO!
Crewman:
ANY MORE WOMEN
AND CHILDREN?
I FOUND HER
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
WAITING
FOR A BOAT...
WITH HIM.
ANY MORE WOMEN
AND CHILDREN?
THEY'RE ALL ABOARD,
MR. MURDOCH.
ANYONE ELSE, THEN?
ANYONE ELSE?
HURRY ALONG.
STAND BY THE FALLS.
OH, GODDAMN IT ALL TO HELL.
SHIT.
FIRE!
SIR!
SIR, YOU CAN'T
GO THROUGH HERE.
GO THROUGH.
YES, YES, SPLENDID.
RIGHT.
Murdoch:
PREPARE TO LOWER!
READY ON THE LEFT.
TAKE THEM DOWN.
KEEP IT STEADY.
BOTH SIDES TOGETHER,
STEADY.
KEEP IT STEADY.
GIVE HER TO ME.
Girl:
DADDY...
Man:
IT'LL BE FINE,
DARLING.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
IT'S GOOD-BYE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
ONLY FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
THERE'LL BE
ANOTHER BOAT
FOR THE DADDIES.
THIS BOAT'S FOR
THE MUMMIES AND
THE CHILDREN.
YOU HOLD MUMMY'S
HAND AND BE A GOOD
LITTLE GIRL.
I'M NOT GOING WITHOUT YOU.
NO, YOU HAVE TO GO... NOW!
NO, JACK.
GET IN THE BOAT, ROSE.
YES, GET ON THE BOAT.
YES, GET ON
THE BOAT, ROSE.
MY GOD, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU LOOK A FRIGHT.
HERE.
PUT THIS ON.
COME.
GO ON, I'LL GET
THE NEXT ONE.
NO, NOT WITHOUT YOU.
Jack:
I'LL BE
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN,
I'LL BE FINE.
I'M A SURVIVOR, ALL RIGHT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
Jack:
NOW GO ON, GET ON.
I HAVE AN ARRANGEMENT
WITH AN OFFICER
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE SHIP.
JACK AND I
CAN GET OFF SAFELY.
BOTH OF US.
SEE.
GOT MY OWN BOAT
TO CATCH.
Cal:
NOW, HURRY.
THEY'RE ALMOST FULL.
STEP ABOARD, MISS.
Cal:
COME ON, HURRY.
STEP ABOARD,
PLEASE.
Man:
BE DADDY'S GOOD GIRL.
STEP LIVELY.
Crewman:
KEEP BACK, KEEP BACK, I SAY.
CLEAR THE ROW, PLEASE.
LOWER AWAY!
Crewman:
SLOWLY...
KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
AND LOWER AWAY EVENLY, LADS.
EASY. LOWER AWAY.
YOU'RE A GOOD LIAR.
ALMOST AS GOOD AS YOU.
Crewman:
EASY NOW... AND LOWER AWAY.
THERE'S NO, UH...
THERE'S NO ARRANGEMENT,
IS THERE?
NO, THERE IS.
NOT THAT YOU'LL
BENEFIT MUCH FROM IT.
I ALWAYS WIN, JACK...
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
Crewman:
EASY... EVEN, LADS.
KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
ROSE!
STOP HER!
Jack:
ROSE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Cal:
STOP HER!
NO!
ROSE.
YOU'RE SO STUPID.
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
YOU'RE SO STUPID, ROSE.
WHY DID YOU
DO THAT? WHY?
YOU JUMP, I JUMP, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
OH, GOD, I COULDN'T GO.
I COULDN'T GO, JACK.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING.
Rose:
AT LEAST I'M WITH YOU.
WE'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING.
COME ON!
COME ON, MOVE!
COME ON.
MOVE!
COME ON,
COME ON, ROSE.
COME ON.
ROSE, COME ON!
MOVE, ROSE!
I HOPE YOU ENJOY
YOUR TIME TOGETHER.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
BE FUNNY?
I PUT THE DIAMOND IN THE COAT.
AND I PUT
THE COAT ON HER!
COME ON.
WE CAN'T LEAVE HIM.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
GO BACK!
IT'S THE WRONG WAY!
COME BACK.
GO!
JACK!
ROSE!
THIS WAY.
COME ON.
GIVE ME
YOUR HAND.
OH, GOD!
HELP!
WAIT, SIR,
OPEN THE GATE, PLEASE.
PLEASE.
HELP US.
PLEASE!
BLOODY HELL.
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON.
GO, GO!
JESUS.
PLEASE.
COME ON!
HURRY.
COME ON.
I'M SORRY,
I DROPPED THE KEYS.
WAIT! PLEASE!
DON'T LEAVE, PLEASE!
GET MORE HELP!
I GOT THEM.
WHICH ONE IS IT, ROSE?
THE SHARP ONE,
TRY THE SHARP ONE.
HURRY, JACK.
OH, NO.
IT'S STUCK.
HURRY.
HURRY, JACK!
HURRY!
I GOT IT, I GOT IT!
GO! GO, ROSE!
GO, GO!
JACK!
JACK, COME ON!
MOVE, MOVE!
Crewman:
KEEP ON ROCKING.
OARS IN PLACE.
GET AN OAR UNDER IT.
Murdoch:
WOMEN AND CHILDREN ONLY,
DAMN YOU.
Crewman:
HOLD IT, HOLD IT.
GET THESE DAVITS CRANKED IN.
THEN GET THE FALLS HOOKED UP.
Murdoch:
STAY BACK.
Child:
HELP ME.
KEEP GOING UP.
Murdoch:
STOP PUSHING!
STAY BACK!
WILL YOU GIVE US
A CHANCE TO LIVE,
YOU LIMEY BASTARD?
I'LL SHOOT ANY MAN WHO TRIES
TO GET PAST ME-- GET BACK!
BASTARD!
GET BACK!
WE HAD A DEAL, DAMN YOU.
YOUR MONEY CAN'T SAVE YOU
ANY MORE THAN IT CAN SAVE ME.
GET BACK.
Crewman:
WOMEN AND
CHILDREN ONLY!
TOMMY, NO, TOMMY...
BASTARDO!
OH, NO, OH, NO...
OH, NO, TOMMY...
NO, WILL!
STAND BACK, DAMN YOU.
I HAVE A CHILD.
Cal:
CLEAR A PATH HERE.
PLEASE, I HAVE A CHILD.
PLEASE, I'M ALL SHE HAS
IN THE WORLD.
GO ON.
STEP BACK,
STEP BACK, I SAY.
PLEASE.
Woman:
HERE, GIVE HER TO ME.
GIVE HER HERE.
THERE, THERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
MR. ANDREWS.
OH, ROSE.
WON'T YOU EVEN
MAKE A TRY FOR IT?
I'M SORRY THAT
I DIDN'T BUILD YOU
A STRONGER SHIP,
YOUNG ROSE.
IT'S GOING FAST.
WE HAVE TO MOVE.
WAIT.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU, ROSE.
AND TO YOU.
MR. GUGGENHEIM.
THESE ARE FOR YOU,
NO, THANK YOU.
WE ARE DRESSED IN OUR BEST
AND ARE PREPARED TO GO DOWN
AS GENTLEMEN.
BUT WE WOULD
LIKE A BRANDY.
CAPITAN.
CAPITAN,
WHERE SHOULD I GO?
PLEASE.
Crewman:
CAPTAIN!
CAPTAIN, SIR.
RIGHT, THAT'S IT, THEN.
GOOD-BYE, WALLY, GOOD LUCK.
SO LONG, OLD CHAP.
AND SO THEY LIVED
HAPPILY TOGETHER
FOR 300 YEARS
IN THE LAND
OF TIR NA NOG
THE LAND OF ETERNAL
YOUTH AND BEAUTY.
THERE'S NO TIME!
CUT THOSE FALLS.
CUT THEM, CUT THEM
IF YOU HAVE TO.
Crewman:
I NEED A KNIFE.
CUT HER LOOSE.
CUT THOSE BLOODY FALLS.
GENTLEMEN,
IT HAS BEEN A PRIVILEGE
PLAYING WITH YOU TONIGHT.
WE HAVE TO STAY
ON THE SHIP
AS LONG AS POSSIBLE!
COME ON!
Jack:
THIS WAY.
OVER THE RAIL!
COME ON... JUMP!
COME ON!
Jack:
I GOT YOU-- JUMP!
I'VE GOT YOU, MISS!
JACK!
Jack:
COME ON!
Cal:
GET BACK!
NO! YOU'LL SWAMP US.
YEA, THOUGH I WALK THROUGH THE
VALLEY OF THE SHADOW OF DEATH...
YOU WANT TO WALK A
LITTLE FASTER THROUGH
THAT VALLEY THERE?
ROW!
PULL TOGETHER!
Priest:
HOLY MARY, MOTHER OF GOD
PRAY FOR US SINNERS NOW AND
AT THE HOUR OF OUR DEATH, AMEN.
HAIL MARY, FULL OF GRACE
THE LORD IS WITH THEE.
THIS WAY.
BLESSED
ART THOU...
Jack:
COME ON.
COME ON!
I SAW A NEW HEAVEN
AND A NEW EARTH
WHEN THE FIRST HEAVEN AND THE
FIRST EARTH HAD PASSED AWAY...
...AND THERE WAS NO MORE SEA.
Woman:
HELP ME!
IT'LL BE OVER SOON.
IT'LL ALL BE OVER SOON.
Priest:
AND HE SHALL DWELL WITH THEM
AND THEY SHALL BE HIS PEOPLE
AND GOD HIMSELF
SHALL BE WITH THEM...
JACK...
THIS IS WHERE
WE FIRST MET.
AND GOD SHALL WIPE AWAY
ALL THE TEARS FROM THEIR EYES
AND THERE SHALL BE
NO MORE DEATH.
NEITHER SHALL THERE
BE SORROW OR CRYING.
NEITHER SHALL THERE BE
ANY MORE PAIN
FOR THE FORMER WORLD
HAS PASSED AWAY.
BLOODY PULL FASTER, AND PULL!
Man:
HANG ON, MISS TRUDY!
HELP ME! PLEASE, SAVE ME!
Woman:
HELP!
Jack:
HOLD ON REAL TIGHT!
GOD ALMIGHTY!
Crewman:
GET THOSE BREAKERS IN!
KEEP THEM IN!
WE HAVE TO MOVE!
GIVE ME YOUR HAND,
I'LL PULL YOU OVER.
Rose:
I CAN'T!
COME ON,
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
I'VE GOT YOU.
I WON'T LET GO.
COME ON, I'VE GOT YOU.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, JACK?
I DON'T KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW!
Jack:
HOLD ON!
Rose:
JACK!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
Man:
HELP ME, PLEASE,
SOMEONE HELP ME, PLEASE!
Woman:
PLEASE HELP! HELP!
HELP! HELP!
THIS IS IT!
Rose:
OH, GOD, OH, GOD!
HOLD ON!
OH, GOD, OH, GOD, OH!
THE SHIP IS GOING
TO SUCK US DOWN.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH
WHEN I SAY.
KICK FOR THE SURFACE
AND KEEP KICKING.
DO NOT LET GO
OF MY HAND.
WE'RE GOING
TO MAKE IT, ROSE.
TRUST ME.
I TRUST YOU.
READY? READY?
NOW!
JACK! JACK!
JACK!
JACK.
JACK! JACK!
NO!
JACK!
ROSE!
GET OFF HER!
JACK!
SWIM, ROSE!
I NEED YOU TO SWIM!
KEEP SWIMMING!
IT'S SO COLD!
SWIM, ROSE!
COME ON... HERE...
KEEP SWIMMING...
COME ON.
HERE, GET ON IT.
GET ON TOP.
COME ON, ROSE.
STAY ON IT,
STAY ON, ROSE.
JACK.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT NOW.
Crewman:
RETURN...
THE BOATS!
THE BOATS ARE COMING BACK
FOR US, ROSE.
HOLD ON JUST
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
Crewman:
RETURN THE BOATS!
THEY... HAD TO ROW AWAY
FOR THE SUCTION
BUT NOW THEY'LL BE COMING BACK.
Woman:
COME BACK!
FOR GOD'S SAKE!
PLEASE!
HELP US!
COME BACK!
FOR GOD'S SAKE!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IF WE GO BACK,
THEY'LL SWAMP THE BOAT.
THEY'LL PULL US RIGHT DOWN,
I'M TELLING YOU.
KNOCK IT OFF--
YOU'RE SCARING ME.
COME ON, GIRLS--
GRAB AN OAR, LET'S GO!
Man:
ARE YOU OUT
OF YOUR MIND?
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NORTH ATLANTIC!
NOW, DO YOU PEOPLE WANT TO LIVE
OR DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND A ONE OF YOU.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
IT'S YOUR MEN
OUT THERE!
THERE'S PLENTY OF ROOM FOR MORE.
AND THERE'LL
BE ONE LESS
ON THIS BOAT
IF YOU DON'T SHUT
THAT HOLE IN YOUR FACE!
Woman:
COME BACK!
Man:
HERE, TAKE THIS ONE.
Lowe:
NOW BRING IN YOUR OARS
OVER THERE
AND TIE THESE TWO BOATS
TOGETHER AS WELL.
NOW MAKE SURE
THAT'S TIED UP
NICE AND TIGHT.
RIGHT, LISTEN TO ME, MEN,
WE HAVE TO GO BACK.
I WANT TO TRANSFER
ALL THE WOMEN
FROM THIS BOAT
INTO THAT BOAT
RIGHT NOW
AS QUICK AS
YOU CAN, PLEASE.
LET'S GET SOME
SPACE THERE.
MOVE FORWARD AND AFT.
IT'S GETTING QUIET.
IT'S JUST GOING TO TAKE THEM
A COUPLE OF MINUTES
TO GET THE BOATS ORGANIZED.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU
BUT I INTEND TO WRITE
A STRONGLY WORDED LETTER
TO THE WHITE STAR LINE
ABOUT ALL THIS.
I LOVE YOU, JACK.
DON'T YOU DO THAT.
DON'T YOU SAY YOUR GOOD-BYES.
NOT YET,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
I'M SO COLD.
LISTEN, ROSE...
YOU'RE GOING
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO GO ON
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE LOTS OF BABIES
TO WATCH THEM GROW.
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE AN OLD...
AN OLD LADY WARM IN HER BED.
NOT HERE.
NOT THIS NIGHT.
NOT LIKE THIS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
I CAN'T FEEL MY BODY.
WINNING THAT TICKET, ROSE
WAS THE BEST THING
THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
IT BROUGHT ME TO YOU...
AND I'M THANKFUL FOR THAT, ROSE.
I'M THANKFUL.
YOU MUST... YOU MUST...
YOU MUST DO ME THIS HONOR...
YOU MUST PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL SURVIVE...
THAT YOU WON'T GIVE UP...
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS...
NO MATTER HOW HOPELESS.
PROMISE ME NOW, ROSE...
AND NEVER LET GO
OF THAT PROMISE.
I PROMISE.
NEVER LET GO.
I WILL NEVER LET GO, JACK.
I'LL NEVER LET GO.
Crewman:
RIGHT AHEAD, SIR.
Lowe:
OARS!
DO YOU SEE
ANY MOVING?
NO, SIR.
NONE MOVING, SIR.
CHECK THEM.
BRING THAT
OAR UP HERE.
CHECK THEM, MAKE SURE.
THESE ARE DEAD, SIR.
NOW GIVE WAY.
AHEAD EASY.
CAREFUL WITH YOUR OARS.
DON'T HIT THEM.
IS THERE ANYONE ALIVE OUT THERE?
CAN ANYONE HEAR ME?
WE WAITED TOO LONG.
WELL, KEEP CHECKING THEM,
KEEP LOOKING!
IS THERE ANYONE ALIVE OUT THERE?
CAN ANYONE HEAR ME?
♪ AND IT'S UP SHE GOES. ♪
♪ UP SHE GOES. ♪
JACK?
JACK.
JACK, THERE'S A BOAT.
JACK?
JACK.
JACK!
THERE'S A BOAT, JACK.
JACK?
COME BACK.
COME BACK, COME BACK.
HELLO!
CAN ANYONE HEAR ME?
THERE'S NOTHING
HERE, SIR.
COME BACK.
I'LL NEVER LET GO.
I PROMISE.
COME ABOUT!
1,500 PEOPLE WENT INTO THE SEA
WHEN TITANIC SANK FROM UNDER US.
THERE WERE 20 BOATS
FLOATING NEARBY
AND ONLY ONE CAME BACK.
ONE.
SIX WERE SAVED
FROM THE WATER
MYSELF INCLUDED.
SIX... OUT OF 1,500.
AFTERWARD, THE 700 PEOPLE
IN THE BOATS
HAD NOTHING TO DO BUT WAIT...
WAIT TO DIE, WAIT TO LIVE...
WAIT FOR AN ABSOLUTION
THAT WOULD NEVER COME.
OH, SIR, I DON'T
THINK YOU'LL FIND
ANY OF YOUR
PEOPLE DOWN HERE.
IT'S ALL STEERAGE.
Woman:
HIS HAIR IS
REDDISH BROWN.
REDDISH BROWN,
REDDISH BROWN
AND A WHITE BEARD.
Woman:
ISN'T THERE ANOTHER
PASSENGER LIST?
THERE'S
NO OTHER LIST.
PERHAPS HE'S ON
ANOTHER SHIP.
WE'RE DOING
ALL WE CAN, MA'AM.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I EVER SAW HIM.
HE MARRIED, OF COURSE,
AND INHERITED HIS MILLIONS
BUT THE CRASH OF '29
HIT HIS INTERESTS HARD
AND HE PUT A PISTOL
IN HIS MOUTH THAT YEAR
OR SO I READ.
CAN I TAKE
YOUR NAME PLEASE, LOVE?
DAWSON.
ROSE DAWSON.
THANK YOU.
WE NEVER FOUND ANYTHING ON JACK.
THERE'S NO RECORD OF HIM AT ALL.
NO, THERE WOULDN'T BE,
WOULD THERE?
AND I'VE NEVER
SPOKEN OF HIM UNTIL NOW.
NOT TO ANYONE
NOT EVEN
YOUR GRANDFATHER.
A WOMAN'S HEART
IS A DEEP OCEAN
OF SECRETS.
BUT NOW YOU KNOW THERE WAS
A MAN NAMED JACK DAWSON
AND THAT HE SAVED ME
IN EVERY WAY
THAT A PERSON CAN BE SAVED.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
A PICTURE OF HIM.
HE EXISTS NOW ONLY IN MY MEMORY.
Man:
Keldysh, Keldysh, Mir 2
on our way to the surface.
Brock:
YOU KNOW I WAS SAVING THIS
FOR WHEN I FOUND THE DIAMOND.
I'M SORRY.
THREE YEARS I'VE THOUGHT
OF NOTHING EXCEPT TITANIC
BUT I NEVER GOT IT.
I NEVER LET IT IN.
♪ EVERY NIGHT IN MY DREAMS
I SEE YOU, I FEEL YOU ♪
♪ THAT IS HOW
I KNOW YOU GO ON ♪
♪ FAR ACROSS THE DISTANCE
AND SPACES BETWEEN US ♪
♪ YOU HAVE COME TO SHOW
YOU GO ON ♪
♪ NEAR, FAR, WHEREVER YOU ARE ♪
♪ I BELIEVE THAT
THE HEART DOES GO ON ♪
♪ ONCE MORE,
YOU OPEN THE DOOR ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE HERE IN MY HEART ♪
♪ AND MY HEART
WILL GO ON AND ON ♪
♪ LOVE CAN TOUCH JUST ONE TIME
AND LAST FOR A LIFETIME ♪
♪ AND NEVER LET GO
TILL WE'RE GONE ♪
♪ LOVE WAS WHEN I LOVED YOU,
ONE TRUE TIME I HOLD TO ♪
♪ IN MY LIFE
WE'LL ALWAYS GO ON ♪
♪ NEAR, FAR, WHEREVER YOU ARE ♪
♪ I BELIEVE THAT
THE HEART DOES GO ON ♪
♪ ONCE MORE,
YOU OPEN THE DOOR ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE HERE IN MY HEART ♪
♪ AND MY HEART
WILL GO ON AND ON. ♪
♪ YOU'RE HERE,
THERE'S NOTHING I FEAR ♪
♪ AND I KNOW
THAT MY HEART WILL GO ON ♪
♪ WE'LL STAY FOREVER THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOU ARE SAFE IN MY HEART ♪
♪ AND MY HEART
WILL GO ON AND ON. ♪