[instrumental music playing]
[Rich] Yeah so, we try to patrol
this shit hole once every hour.
Ah, make sure all the doors are locked,
tenants aren't bitching.
Oh, there's the washrooms over there.
Yo, Danny, my man!
[Danny] What up Richie boy?
[Rich] Well, not much. Just
showing the new girl around.
Hey.
Hey, New Girl.
[Rich] Hey, catch you later?
[Rich] Break time.
Hello?
[knocking at door]
[rattling]
[peeing]
[cell phone dialing]
[mom] Hello?
Mom? Are you coming?
[mom] Oh, was I supposed to pick you up?
It's okay, I'll get a cab.
[Betty] Bye.
[friend] [laughs] Here you go Michelle!
So... how did you meet up?
[Michelle] Oh, we met at
a study abroad in Florence.
It was so romantic.
-[friend] Wow.
-[Michelle] Yeah.
-[friend] That's so cool.
-[Michelle] Yeah and actually
[Michelle] we just went
back on vacation last year
and he proposed, there.
Like, right on the bridge
we had our first kiss on.
[friends] Awww...
[Michelle] It was really nice.
[friend] So? Who made the first move?
[Michelle] Um... It was me actually!
-[friend 1] Wow.
-[friend 2] Nice! Girl power!
-[Michelle] Yeah.
-[friends] Yeah,
You gotta put yourself out there.
[Michelle] Oh totally, yeah.
[friends] Cheers!
[Michelle] Thanks so much for coming.
[message alert]
[message alert continues]
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[knocks] Yo!
Me and Anton are heading
to Demis for some drinks.
You want to join?
Sure.
[Rich] So Danny, this is the new girl.
Betty, Danny. Danny, Betty.
Hey, new girl.
Hey.
[Rich] So, you drink often?
Like every weekend probably.
[Rich] Every weekend?
-[Betty] Yeah.
[Rich] Try every day!
I mean, what else are you
going to do in this shit job?
You want a chaser?
Fuck no, chasers are for pussies, right?
[Rich] Fuck yeah!
[laughing and tapping]
[Betty] I can't find my phone.
[Rich] Check your purse.
[Betty] It's not in here!
[Danny] Is she gonna be all right?
[Rich] She had too much to drink.
[Betty] I found it!
I found it.
[Betty chuckles]
[Danny] Where does she live?
[Rich] Betty, where do you live?
[Betty] Where do I live?
[Rich] Yeah where do you live?
[Betty] Birchmount and Ellesmere.
[Danny] It's on the way.
I'll uh, I'll give her a lift.
[Danny] Come on, I'm giving you a ride.
[Betty] What?
[Danny] I'm giving you a ride. Come on!
[Betty] Can you take my bag?
Thank you. Oh, thank
you. You're a gentleman.
[Betty] You're good guys.
-[Danny] Just over here.
-[Betty] Okay.
-[Danny] Yeah.
-[Betty] We're going to your car?
[Danny] Yeah. Hold on to her.
[Betty] I'm sorry.
[cell phone rings and vibrates]
Hello?
[mom] Hey Betty, it's mom.
Listen I can't make it to
our mani-pedi date today.
I'm still up at the cottage with Will.
Uh, yeah, sure.
[mom] Thanks Betty. Love you!
[crunching]
[whirring]
[beep] Rich. Over.
Rich!
[exhales]
[Betty] Hey. Um... you
guys can't do that here.
Seriously, you have to go.
[girl] Get a life.
[boy] Bitch.
[Rich] Yo, Betty, what's up? Over.
[Betty] Fuck you, Rich. I'm going on break.
[hip-hop music playing]
[door closes]
Danny?
-[Betty] Hey.
-[Danny] Huh?
[Danny] Where are we going?
-[Betty] We're gonna take you home.
-[Danny] What?
[Betty] Yeah!
-[Danny] No.
[Danny] I'm taking you home.
[Betty] No, I don't
think that's a good idea.
-[Betty] Watch the curb.
-[Danny] Where?
[Betty] Watch the curb. Okay.
-[Betty] There you go. Okay.
-[Danny] What are you doing?
[Betty] I'm gonna take
you home. [both chuckle]
[Danny] You're not doing a good job
[Betty] You're, you're not
doing a good job of standing.
-Oh, hang on right there, okay?
-[Danny] Oh!
[Betty] You okay? You're
gonna... [Danny] After you.
-[Betty] No, that's where you're sitting.
-[Danny] Don't do it.
[Betty] Watch your head.
-[Danny] Ow. My head.
-[Betty] Watch your...
-[Betty] Watch your head, please.
-[Danny] Why'd you hit my head!
[Betty] Are you okay?
-[Danny] No.
[Danny] Betty! Betty!
[Betty] What's your address?
[Danny] Take me to a dance party.
[Betty] I'm gonna take you home.
[Danny] I thought you were cool.
-[Betty] I am cool.
-[Danny] Woohoo!
Dance party! Ouch. Shit.
[chuckles]
-[Danny] Can I ask you a question?
-[Betty] Okay.
[Danny] Does your back hurt?
What?[chuckles]
[Danny] Boobies. [both laugh]
[Betty] Do you wanna see them? [laughs]
Yes! [laughs]
[Betty] Okay don't, don't
look. Don't look. Don't look.
[Betty] Okay.
[Danny] Wow.
[Betty] Are you sleeping?
[chuckles softly]
[sexual moaning from video]
[Rich] Oh yeah! Right in your face!
[moaning continues]
[Rich] Hey, Anton,
you got any hot pics of your mom?
[Anton] Shut the fuck up.
[Rich] How about you, Betty?
Show us a little nip please.
[Anton] Yeah, show us your boobs.
[Betty] Shut the fuck up, Anton!
[Anton] Sorry.
[knocking]
How's it going?
It's going.
What's up?
Just, just chilling.
At the strip mall.
-[Betty] Sounds fun.
-[Danny] Were you winning?
[Betty] I don't know. [both chuckles]
Uh, I was looking or the washroom.
[Betty] What?
-[Danny] The washroom.
Oh, I think I found it.
I'll be, I'll be right back.
[laughs]
[Danny] Don't look at me. I'm peeing.
That was good.
[Danny] Was it?
-[Betty] Yeah.
[Danny] Do you wanna hang out?
Come smoke with me.
Right now?
-Yeah, are you busy?
-No.
-[Betty] Don't tell, Rich.
-[Danny] You don't tell, Rich.
I've seen him...
I've seen him smoking pot.
And then I... I think that he, uh...
goes out to the back dumpster with Anton
and they blow each other.
[laughter]
Yeah?
That's my theory.
Wow. And then you just watch?
I don't watch.
Your face looks like you watch.
I think, I think about it.
I think about my theory.
Cause like... Anton,
there's just like, so
much hair for him like,
bury his claws into you know. It's like...
[both laugh]
I don't want to see it.
-[Betty] It's in your head now.
-[Danny] It's in my head! Get it out!
[Danny] Anton stop! Leave him
alone! Leave him alone Anton!
It's a party!
It's a blow job party.
We should have a makeup party.
A make out party?
Makeup. Makeup. Makeup.
Oh, like for your cheeks?
Yeah.
Where else do you put makeup?
[Betty] Like I'd do your makeup?
You can do my makeup.
And you just get 12 of your friends
and... we'll bring some chips,
pump some JT.
You'll do it?
[Betty] Yeah.
[Danny] Yeah!
-[Betty] Yeah, okay.
[Betty] Wow, it echoed.
-Did you hear that?
-[Danny] Don't leave me hanging.
[Danny] Okay, give me your digits.
Can I get your digits?
You? Yeah!
[Danny] Boom.
[Danny] And nice and cool. Feels great.
Um, all Avabon products
are free of harsh metals
and toxic chemicals.
Um... and they're,
and they're safe for you.
Uh so, uh, oh, oh, also,
uh, there's a 90 day guarantee,
uh, if you don't like it,
you get your money back.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I didn't make any sales...
but... it's a start.
Do you wanna get a drink?
You look like you need one.
-Yeah.
-[Betty] Really?
-[Danny] Yeah!
-Yeah, okay.
Um, let me just... finish up in there.
[music playing in stereo]
[Danny] Maybe I'll Karaoke tonight.
Maybe.[chuckles]
-Yeah?
-Maybe.
You can carry a tune?
I can, I got a few jams in me.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
[Betty] Do you wanna do a duet?
I don't know.
I think, I think you
need to prove it to me.
You just said you were good.
-I need to prove it?
-Yeah.
No, I said I had some jams, but...
Well, lets make a PB & J
with those jams, come on!
-Jam it out?
-Let's go!
[grunts]
Okay. Let's do it. Let's do it.
It's time. Let's kill it.
["La Bamba" playing]
♪ Para bailar la bamba
♪ Se necesita una poca de gracia ♪
♪ Yo no soy marinero soy capitan ♪
♪ Soy capitán Soy capitan
♪ Bamba-bamba Bamba-bamba ♪
[cell phone vibrates and rings]
[grunts and chuckles]
Yo.
-Hey.
-What's up with you?
You look like shit.
I'm hungover and it's my birthday.
Okay, calm down. It's not a big deal.
I mean, I fucking work on my
birthday, what else are we gonna do?
[Rich] Hey, listen, I'll call up Anton
and after our shift we can go for
some birthday beers. Sound good?
[Betty] Okay.
[knocks and chuckles]
[sighs]
[music playing in stereo]
So, how old are you turning?
Twenty.
The big two-O.
Did you get any good gifts? From the rents?
Not really.
Speaking of gifts.
You got me a present?
[Rich] Me and Anton
got you a little something
Thanks, guys.
[giggles]
That'll tide you over on the late shift.
[laughs]
[Anton] It's a vibrator, for your pussy.
[both laughing]
[Rich] Okay, I got a good one.
Wet pussy! [laughs]
You're such an asshole.
[Rich] Okay, your turn.
Right up here.
[Betty] Big dick! [both laugh]
Hey, don't worry buddy, I
think you have a nice dick.
[both laugh]
Do you do this all the time?
[Rich] Yeah, of course.
What would you do if
one of these girls was like,
"Yeah, baby, like, let me in your car"?
Well, it would probably be pretty
uncomfortable for you cause, I'd fuck her.
Yeah, but seriously though,
guys don't turn down pussy.
[vibrates]
[sighs]
[vibration continues]
[camera clicks]
[water dripping]
[instrumental music playing]
[engine revs]
[knocks]
Hi. How's it going?
It's all right.
How's the uh, Avabon stuff going?
Did you need help with another party?
I'm okay.
I've got enough people.
Well, if you change your mind,
I'm usually free like weekdays before six,
or I could probably
like take a day off even.
Cool.
I think I'm okay. Thanks.
So, did you get any text messages lately?
Scram. Back to work.
[car door opens] Bye Danny.
[Danny] Bye.
[car door closes]
[instrumental music continues playing]
[door closes]
[typing]
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct singing]
♪ A foot fetish. Say what ♪
-Got a foot fetish...
-[Betty] Rich.
-[Rich] What?
-[Betty] What the fuck did you do to the computer?
[Rich] What computer?
The computer in the security
booth that has a picture of me on it.
[chuckles]
There's a computer in the security booth?
Look, I get it, you
think you're being funny.
You think this is hilarious
to have some big old
titties on the computer.
Ha-ha, funny, look at Betty.
It's not.
[chuckles]
There's a picture of you?
[Rich chuckles]
-Fuck you, Rich.
Fuck you Anton. You guys
can just go fuck each other I quit.
[Rich chuckles softly]
[door closes]
[thud]
[laptop crushing]
[sobs]
[whimpers]
[breathing heavily]
[Betty] Danny!
[hip hop music playing]
[Rich] Yo, Danny, my man!
[Danny] What up, Richie boy.
Not much, just showing the new girl around.
Hey, new girl.
[radio playing]
[Betty chuckles softly]
-[Danny] Just over here.
-[Betty] Over there?
-[Danny] Yeah.
-[Betty] We're going to your car?
[Danny] Yeah. Hold on to her.
[door unlocks]
[footsteps approaching]
[kisses]
[claps]
[grunts]
[Danny] Yeah, you like that slap?
[Celine] Baby, I gotta go to work.
[groans]
[both chuckles]
[Danny sighs]
[Celine] What are you doing this weekend?
'Cause I was thinking,
that we should start
looking for a new apartment.
What? Our place is fine.
And I still have some
credit card debt left.
Well, how much do you have left?
I don't know.
What?
[whispers]
-[Celine] What?
[Celine] Danny, what are you saying?
Twelve g's. I have twelve g's left.
Well, how are you gonna pay it off?
Babe, I'll take care of it.
[Celine] Okay, 'cause I want my apartment!
-Well, That's the dream.
-A new bed and a dishwasher.
[Danny] Okay.
Carpet, no. Wood floors.
Babe.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
[car door shuts]
[indicator ticking]
[engine whirs]
-[Frank] Hey.
-[Danny] Hey. [sniffs]
[Danny] Just, uh...
finishing up the polishing
and then I will count up
the bottles and should be good to go
[Frank] Cool. Great, thank you. Thank you.
[Frank] This is for you.
[Danny] Whoa, what's this?
That's your severance pay.
We're closing tonight.
This is our last night.
-Shit.
-Yeah.
Are, are you, are you okay?
-Yeah sure. Yeah, I'm fine uh...
-[Danny] Shit.
You know this place is a
part of my life. But I'm good.
[Frank sighs]
Shit, Frank. Uh...
I wanna thank you for
everything you've done.
Yeah, sure.
And maybe we can have a
drink and you can go home early?
Yeah, let's, yeah, let's do that.
-What'll you have?
-Just a, just a beer.
[Frank] You want a beer?
-[Danny] Yeah.
[Frank] Beer it is man. [both chuckles]
[sighs]
-One for you.
-Thank you.
[clattering]
Toast. Cheers to you, my friend.
[Rich] Fucking balls dude.
-[Danny] Yeah, man.
-[Rich] That sucks.
So, I guess, you're out of a job, eh?
Um, yeah.
Maybe I could... roll with you.
You know. Work with you on Intellcom.
Busting down doors.
Kicking in heads.
-Freeze, Miss.
-Uh, I'm sorry sir.
Put down that super dollar bag,
I have pepper spray.
[chuckles]
Man... as much as I would love that,
that's a no-can-fucking-do.
What?
Yeah, we just hired this new chick.
-Lame bro.
-Yeah.
[spits]
Ah, fuck.
[door opens]
[Celine] Hurry, we're gonna be late.
-Love you.
-Love you too. Have a good day at work.
[car door shuts]
[indicator ticking]
[hip hop music playing in stereo]
[crunching]
[cell phone dialing]
[man] Hello, Cold Stone Real
Estate, how can I help you?
I'm calling about the
Executive Assistant job posting.
[man] What's your name?
Daniel Mendoza.
[man] Do you have any
Executive Assisting experience?
No, but I do...
[man] We're only accepting
candidates with previous experience.
I'm sorry.
[ball bouncing]
[tire screeching]
[engine stops]
[car door closes]
[door unlocks]
[hip hop music playing]
[bottle cork pops]
[hip hop music continues playing]
[gulps]
-[Danny] Where are we going?
-[Betty] I'm gonna take you home.
[Danny] What?
-[Betty] Yeah!
[Danny] No. I'm taking you home.
[Betty] No, I don't
think that's a good idea.
-[Betty] Watch the curb.
-[Danny] Where?
[Betty] Watch the curb!
[water flowing]
[scrapping]
Morning! How are you?
I'm okay.
Thanks for the water and stuff.
Do you want some eggs?
No, I'm not hungry.
Are you sure? I can make
you uh, like a sandwich.
No, I'm okay.
Do you have my keys?
Um...
Yep, there, on the table there.
[sighs]
[oven beeps]
[oven starts]
[voicemail] You have one new message.
[woman] Hello, this is a
message for Daniel Mendoza
from CITC Visa.
Mr. Mendoza we've noticed that you
haven't made your minimum payments
for the months of March, April or May.
Please call us at your
earliest convenience.
We can be reached at 905-768-1.
[sighs]
[brushing]
[Danny] Listen, I think my bar tending
skills absolutely translate to sales.
[interviewer] Do you have
any product sales experience?
Like retail?
No, but...
I'm a very good communicator
and... a fast learner.
[water rustling]
[cell phone vibrates]
[Danny] Hey Mom.
You need your car today?
I'm at the Bluffs.
Oh, oh, okay. Okay, I'm coming.
Shit, that's today.
[engine revs]
[car door closes]
[sales woman] If you really
just moisturize it and dab it,
on your forehead. Yes, under the eyes.
Yes, any problem areas you might have.
-[guest] You see this?
-Oh, yes.
And it's not greasy, do you feel that?
-I need this.
-Oh, yes.
-Yes, yes.
-Some cream right there.
Oh, yes and then you just dab it.
[sales woman] The
technique of this, is dabbing.
Because this, this finger doesn't
have many muscles in it. It's very weak...
Did you get to, to try
our body, our body line?
-[guest] No.
-[sales woman] Oh my goodness,
you didn't try our body
line yet? Oh my gosh.
Yes, if you take a look at our package.
Yeah, the packaging is
actually, is actually all recycled.
Yeah, we use recycled plastic. We're all
about natural. Yeah, touch it, feel it, yeah!
[sales woman] But ladies,
I have some good news,
I just wanted to tell you, -[guest] Okay.
Our kits right now are
two for the price of one.
So you get two bottles
of the serum for $79.99.
That's the price of one kit. Yeah.
Yeah, because you are friends and family,
I will give you that
two for the price of one.
You guys are special,
you guys are beautiful,
I want to make you even
more beautiful and radiant.
-[guest] I'll take one.
-[sales woman] Yeah?
Me too. Me too.
[sales woman] Oh, Two!
Got a light?
[sniffs] [sighs]
[sales woman] Are you Danny?
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
[sales woman] Tita talks
a lot about you at church.
[both laugh]
All good things I hope.
Oh Danny. [both laugh]
[sighs] Oh man.
[exhales] You're a bartender?
Yeah. You?
I do Avabon full time.
How's that going for you?
[sales woman] Good.
I think I'm going to clear
60 g's in sales this year.
[Danny] What?
[sales woman] It's lucrative.
You looking for work?
Yeah.
I could totally hook you up with a
license. It's only two hundred bucks.
-I don't know.
-Listen,
[sniffs]
Avabon's amazing.
I'm my own boss, so the hours are flexible,
I, I meet a ton of people,
and I make commission on everything I sell.
[Danny] Hey Laurie.
It's Danny.
It's been a while.
Things are well, thanks.
Yeah, I have a few questions for you.
Do you have friends that like makeup?
Yes? Well, well... this is your lucky day.
I've become an Ava Baun
certified beauty advisor
and I'm looking for new party hosts
to receive a complimentary
Ava Baun gift bag.
You're not interested?
It's a free makeup bag.
Seriously?
Ah, okay. [chuckles]
Well, give me a call if anything changes?
[instrumental music playing]
[Danny] Hi. Sorry,
are you interested in, uh... makeup at all?
[woman] No, I'm fine.
[Danny] You're okay?
-[woman] Thanks.
-[Danny] Do you want a, do you want a flyer?
-[woman] No.
[Danny] You're okay? Okay.
Thanks, have a nice one.
-[Danny] Avabon...
-Ava Baun.
-Avabon, yeah.
[music continues playing]
Uh, sorry, uh...
of course, you don't need makeup.
You ladies are very pretty.
You obviously don't need makeup.
[Danny] No?
-[woman] Not yet. [chuckles]
-[woman] Maybe next time.
-[Danny] Okay.
-We'll think about it first.
-Yeah.
[Danny] Yeah, maybe
I'll come by like next week.
Hi, there.
Uh, are you interested in,
uh, a premium skin care?
[Danny] No?
-[man] I don't know.
They're all very naturally,
they have like lotions.
Okay, take care, thanks.
[Rich] What's up man?
-[Danny] Yo, yo.
Fuck, I'm tired.
Man, these long shifts are killing me.
Samezies.
Oh, yeah.
Here's 40.
I'll get you the rest next time.
Cool.
Hey, do you know any women,
who like lotions and shit?
Lotions?
Yeah, lotions. I'm doing this...
direct sales initiative thing.
Let me think.
Betty maybe?
[Danny] Betty?
[Rich] Yeah. She's a girl.
Come smoke with me.
Right now?
-Yeah, are you busy?
-No.
Then, we have the...
jo-jo-ba moisturizing lotion
[guest] Jojoba.
[Danny] Sorry?
-[guest] Jojoba.
-[Danny] Jojoba.
-[guest] Uh-huh.
-[Danny] Okay.
[Danny] Jojoba? Oh this!
-[guest] Yes.
[Danny] Jojoba. Yes. Jojoba.
-[woman] I have a question.
-Okay.
[woman] Do you have
any without perfume in it?
Without perf... Uh, uh...
No, none of the products
have perfume in it.
[woman] Well, the one I...
This smells like it has perfume.
-[guest] Yeah.
-[Danny] Oh!
[Betty] That one does too actually.
-Oh, well it's...
-[guest] What do you think? Can you smell that?
[guest] Definitely perfume. There's
definitely perfume in this. Definitely.
Do you wanna get a drink?
You look like you might need a drink.
[chuckles]
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Yeah?
-Yeah, yeah.
Okay I'm just going
to finish in the kitchen.
♪ Para bailar la bamba
♪ Se necesita una poca de gracia ♪
I want some Sambuca.
-[Danny] Okay.
-Can I get some Sambuca?
[Betty] I wanna do Sambuca!
I'm going to get the check.
[Betty] No.
You have to get a shot
with me at, at midnight.
Why?
It's my birthday at midnight.
-It's your birthday?
-It's my birthday.
It's the day I was born.
All right, yeah.
-[Betty] Yeah?
-Yeah, let's do shots.
Excuse me.
-Okay.
-[Betty] Excuse me.
[Betty] Bar wench.
Hi, can I get, uh, Sambuca?
-[waitress] Two?
-Two.
-So how old do you turn?
-I'm turning 20.
I'm turning 20.
-Twenty!
-Yeah.
-Cool.
-How old are you?
Older. I'm 31.
[Betty] You're 31?
Oh, my god. Thank you.
You have...
a cherub angel face of a baby.
-Okay.
-Plucked...
from the heavens far, far too soon.
-Okay.
-[Betty chuckles]
What's your, what's your sign?
-What's my sign?
-Yeah.
I'm a Leo.
Like a tiger?
No. Like a lion...
What? [chuckles]
I'm a Gemini.
All right. Oh, look it's
time! Twelve o'clock.
-[Betty] Is it shots time?
-Shots time!
-Let's do it.
-H.B.D.
Happy Birthday.
Whoo!
-[sighs]
[Danny laughs] Okay, okay.
Just...
your hands going to be over there,
and mine's going to
be, just right here, okay?
Oh, come on. Do you have to?
-[Danny] Betty.
-You don't need to do this.
[Danny chuckles] Okay, no.
[Danny] Come on! Betty. Quit it.
Look, we're almost home.
We're going to get you home soon.
[windshield rubbing]
Do you want me to blow you?
[Danny] No.
-[Betty] Are you sure?
-Yes. I'm sure. That's...
There will be no blowing tonight.
It's okay, if you want to.
No! No. No. Betty.
[Danny] We're almost home.
-Can you pull over?
-Are you okay?
[Betty] Can you just pull over?
Are, are you... Just,
just give me a second.
-Are you going to puke?
-[Betty] I just need to get out of the car.
Okay, just one second.
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[Danny] Betty?
Betty?
[car beeping]
[car door closes]
[softly] Betty!
[car beeping]
[car door closes]
[exhales]
[Celine] Where were you?
[Danny] Rich's birthday.
-[Celine] Good night.
-[Danny] Good night.
[kisses]
[voicemail] You have
reached the voice mailbox of...
Daniel Mendoza. [beep]
[Celine] Hi baby, uh. My shift ended early
uh, so you don't need to pick
me up. I'll just meet you at Demis.
[Danny] Hey babe.
[kisses]
I went to Demis today.
And they were closed.
Really?
That's weird.
Well, why were they closed?
[Danny] I don't know.
[Celine sighs]
-What do you mean you don't know?
-I don't know.
What happened, Danny?
They shut down.
Okay, how long have
they been shut down for?
Look I...
I didn't want you to get worried, okay?
I didn't... Like, I'll take care of it.
-Danny, how long have they been shut down for?
-I'll take care of it!
Why don't you tell me?
Three weeks.
What have you been
doing the past three weeks?
I've had, had...
[sighs]
I've had interviews.
Okay, where have you had interviews?
-Different sales positions.
-What do you mean?
I'm working on this...
I'm working on this, thing right now.
It's called Avabon and its this direct
sales initiative kinda thing.
I don't even know what
that is. What's direct sales?
-Do you make any money off of it?
-Yeah.
Eventually.
This lady at church,
she's making 60 k a year.
Well, have you made any money off of it?
[Danny] No, of course not. I just started.
Danny you have debt to pay.
And you're spending all
day playing basketball?
[chuckles]
[Celine] Danny, I need you to try harder.
It's like beauty products.
Like, they do lotions and...
and things like that.
Did you want a flyer too?
No, okay. That's okay. Thanks.
[custodian] Excuse me, do
you have a permit to do that?
I don't. No. no. no.
-You're not allowed to do that.
-Okay.
-[custodian] Sorry.
-Okay, no problem.
-[custodian] You have to have a permit to do that.
-Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, babe!
No, things are going great.
Yeah, it was a piece of cake!
It's going good. It's
going real good. Yeah.
Hey, we should uh, we should celebrate.
I'll take you out to dinner tonight?
Yeah
Okay, great!
Okay, bye.
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[Danny] So wait, you want the pizza?
-[Celine] I don't know.
-[Danny] Okay.
Yeah, I want the pizza.
-You want the pizza? Okay.
-Yes, I want the pizza.
[Danny] Okay, okay.
And then maybe after if you have
room, we can go, we can go lobster.
Are you serious?
[cell phone vibrates]
[Celine] What the fuck?
-What is it?
-What the fuck is this?
-I don't know, what is it?
-Who is she?
May be it's a wrong number.
[cell phone vibrates]
"Danny you likey?"
Ah!
Babe, look, calm down, okay.
I don't know what this is. It's, it's...
-Just take me home.
-Look it's clearly a mistake, okay.
Just take me home!
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
[commentary on TV]
[sniffs]
[inhales deeply]
[commentary on TV]
[turns switch on]
[turns switch off]
[indicator ticking]
[dog barks]
[women laughing]
[doorbell rings]
Celine.
Celine! [doorbell continues ringing]
Celine!
[softly] Celine come
out! [knocking at door]
Cel...
Danny, you have to go.
My sister doesn't want to talk to you.
Andrea come on, just let me talk to her.
-[Andrea] She doesn't want to talk to you.
-It will be really quick.
-Come on, just let me go...
-You're being too loud, you have to go home.
Just let me in. [door closes]
[knocking at door] Andrea.
[staring engine]
[Rich] How much was the tow truck?
-[Danny] Three bills.
-[Rich] Shit.
Thanks for the lift.
No worries.
I got to pop by the plaza
for a minute. You cool?
Cool.
[exhales]
I'll be back in two seconds.
Got to talk to a tenant.
Cool.
[car door closes]
[sighs]
Shit.
[knocks]
Hi. How's it going?
It's all right.
[Betty] How's the, uh, Avabon stuff going?
Did you need help with another party?
I'm okay.
I've got enough people.
Well, if you change your
mind, I'm usually free...
like weekdays, before six
or I could probably
like, take a day off even.
Cool.
-I think I'm okay. Thanks.
-Cool.
[Betty] So have you gotten
any interesting texts lately?
[Rich] Scram.
Back to work.
[Betty] Bye Danny.
[car door closes]
Women.
[breathing heavily]
[Danny] Rich.
Woah. Is that Betty?
[Danny] She sent them to me.
I don't know what to do.
Dude! What are you doing?
[sighs]
Don't do that
What happened?
-Celine saw it.
-Shit.
Was she pissed?
Yeah, she took off.
Fuck. What are you going to do?
I don't know, bro.
Those are some pretty hot pics though.
Look, can you talk to Betty?
[Rich] Yeah, don't worry man.
I'll take care of it.
[Danny] How's it going?
-Danny I can't talk right now.
-How you holding up?
-Danny, please.
-Just give me a second, please.
Just a second.
Just, look I'm, I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-Seriously, I can't do this right now.
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything.
I, I just... look, I'm
sorry that it happened.
Okay? I...
And I want to make it better.
I just, I just lost the
car. I just lost the car.
And, when I do get the car back
let's look at apartments.
-Danny, please.
-Okay?
Lets look at apartments
and then, and then...
I'll make you laugh again,
when I blow in your ear. And
look... Just tell me what to do...
-Danny I have to go.
-Tell me what to do,
-so I can make it up.
-I have to go.
[ball bouncing]
[voicemail] You have one new message.
[Betty] Danny, you're a fucking asshole.
I hate you.
[crying]
Fuck you Danny.
[beep]
[slow music playing]
[soft music playing]